Chapter 501: I Have Lost the Ability to Be Fooled

With Nagakin being freed up, the remaining warriors of DarkStar were quickly taken care of. The protective shield formed a large battle ring where death was the only way out. The surviving mercenaries dragged their injury-riddled bodies and gathered at the center of the battlefield.

Han Xiao took a headcount, and the original hundred or so hired mercenaries had been reduced to less than thirty survivors. With his gaze sweeping past Herlous, Sylvia, the Volgas, and Feidin, he heaved a sigh of relief. At least all of his forces were intact.

The Machinery Army was scattered all over the place, and when he instructed the mercenaries to retrieve the machines, many of them immediately started grumbling.

With the strong winds previously, who knows where your machinery flew to? We just finished a battle, and you cannot go too far and command us!

Despite their complaints, all the mercenaries still followed his orders obediently.

While not everyone witnessed Han Xiao using Ames' Character Summon Card, respect could clearly be seen in the eyes of the mercenaries who saw it.

Han Xiao picked his ears and looked a little irritated.

These darn mercenaries, complaining when I only asked them to pick some stuff up. Players are still the most professional. As long as I reward them, they enjoy whatever suffering I throw at them. They are so much better than these mercenaries; I truly miss them.

Herlous took a step forward and handed Sherman's cannon over. "Spoils of war. For you."

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled as he held onto the firearm in his hands. After taking a glance at the firearm, he stripped it down and nodded as he observed the internals of the firearm. "This cannon isn't too bad."

According to the introduction on the interface, the name of the cannon was the [Triple Core Photon Loop Cannon]. This was a weapon that enjoyed a Cannon Master's Specialty, and any Cannon Master who equipped the weapon would gain a bonus effect. The blueprint was rare, and having the weapon on hand saved Han Xiao the trouble of gambling for blueprints. Han Xiao would be able to derive the blueprint of the [Triple Core Photon Loop Cannon] from the weapon itself. This cannon came just at the right time as Han Xiao needed a light energy firearm at the moment. While he was not a Cannon Master, he would be able to equip the weapon with his Mechanical Force. It is just that the bonus stats granted would not be comparable to a Cannon Master.

A Cannon Master was a long-ranged damage dealer, and players welcomed Cannon Masters in all dungeons. Cannon Masters were an important part of the traditional triangular formation, which included a main tank, ranged DPS, and crowd control.

Han Xiao had also played the Cannon Master before, and apart from firing cannons, the Cannon Master would fire more cannons. While the DPS of a Cannon Master was acceptable, it was far too singular and lacked variation. Although it was pretty fun to fire cannons all day, one would get bored easily after playing it for a long time. Of the three Mechanic classes, Han Xiao preferred the Machinery Master, which was far more agile.

Stowing the cannon away, Han Xiao looked at Sylvia and saw that she did not have many injuries. However, when he turned around to look at Feidin, he realized that Feidin was covered in blood all over as though he had been through a miserable battle.

"Are you alright?" Han Xiao asked.

Chen Xing immediately became anxious. Recalling Feidin's usual demeanor, she hurriedly forced out a warm smile. "I... I am alright. It's just that I met an enemy..."

Sylvia immediately interjected. "That's right, I personally saw you being defeated, and that enemy was truly much stronger than you. I was worried for your safety, and it is truly great that you are fine. How did you defeat the enemy?"

Chen Xing's smile froze up immediately. She hated the fact that she could not stuff Sylvia's mouth up before zipping it up tight. Of all the possible times, you just had to ask me this question now. Aren't you trying to push me to my death?

An idea suddenly sprouted in her head, and she said with a cough, "Er... I didn't defeat him. The enemy was a Grade B Super, and I was almost killed by him. You also know that I do not specialize in battles. Thankfully, a sudden typhoon swept us up and separated us, thus saving my life."

"You are truly lucky." Sylvia lamented.

No one doubted her words. After all, they all accepted that their luck was not as good as hers.

"That's right, you are truly lucky," Han Xiao said as he slapped her heavily on her back, forcing her to cough incessantly as a '-1' damage popped up above her head.

Feeling the pain in her back, Chen Xing suppressed her frustration and forced out a smile. Seeing that Han Xiao did not doubt her words, she heaved a sigh of relief. She was finally able to fool Black Star.

Han Xiao then called for Nagakin, who was by the side, and grabbed onto Chen Xing's shoulder, not allowing her to escape.

Chen Xing squirmed around uncomfortably and said, "Can you let go of me?"

"Stop acting." Han Xiao rolled his eyes. "You can't fool me."

Chen Xing burst out into cold sweat and tried to look for a loophole in her words. However, she just could not spot any.

She obviously did not make any mistakes!

"You are wrong; I am Feidin." She tried to explain his doubts away with a smile.

Han Xiao raised an eyebrow and whispered by Chen Xing's ear, "I've said before, if you truly escaped, you wouldn't want to meet me."

Chen Xing's heart pounded.

At this moment, Nagakin walked over and Han Xiao patted Chen Xing on her shoulders with a smile. "Stop struggling. With a Grade A Super here, it's impossible for you to escape. I don't think you want to be beaten up by him, right?"

Chen Xing grit her teeth and stopped pretending. "How did you recognize me?"

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao had a face of helplessness. The interface had already exposed her identity, and it would be impossible for him to be fooled even if he wanted to. He could not possibly feign ignorance and play along with her, right? He was also in despair!

Chen Xing no longer had any tricks up her sleeves, and she could not think of a way to escape. Glaring at Han Xiao hatefully, she fantasized about a hundred different ways of how she could torture Han Xiao to death.

Since she had already been discovered, she might as well give up the control of the body. It was better than being forcefully suppressed by others.

Feidin's consciousness returned, and after doing a couple of stretches, he shook his head with a smile. "I knew that you would be able to recognize me."

"You are truly lucky. Even after she took control of the body, she did not destroy your consciousness," Han Xiao said with a tinge of envy. The Luck Glow was truly overpowered.

Feidin chuckled in response. "It is actually pretty enjoyable to communicate with her. I understand her well, and she is also completely aware of my thoughts. We can also understand how the other party thinks..."

"I will have to congratulate you on finding a soul mate. Why don't you marry her? Then my mission will be complete."

Han Xiao shook his head and suddenly froze in place.

Wait a minute... it can't be right? The perfect completion for Feidin's mission can't possibly be for him to allow her to attack himself!

Feidin pointed at his head and said helplessly, "I shall not convey how she is scolding you."

Han Xiao laughed dryly and released his grip, distancing himself from Feidin. He then grabbed Sylvia's hair to clean his hands. All of a sudden, he did not feel like being too close to Feidin.

While chatting casually, Han Xiao looked at the time, and it was about time for Ember to return. At that moment, Han Xiao noticed a serious problem. While the fight was over, the protective shield was still up and isolating the region. If he was not able to leave, he would not be able to surround Ember according to his plan.

This problem could only be solved by the Noriosse financial group. The protector was definitely watching nearby, and Han Xiao felt that it was necessary for him to have a good conversation with the protector.

Together with Nagakin, Han Xiao found the protector and displayed his intention for the protective shield to be opened. Without even thinking about it, the protector rejected Han Xiao's request.

"There is still a member of DarkStar alive, and he is rushing back. If you do not open the protective shield, we won't be able to deal with him," Nagakin said.

"I know," the protector replied indifferently. "Thus, I will not open the protective shield before the enemy leaves. All of you can stay here until I have confirmed that this battle is completely over."

"Are you trying to protect someone from DarkStar‽" Nagakin flew into a rage.

"My responsibility is to protect Noriosse. Should I open up the protective shield so that all of you can continue to destroy the city? I don't wish to see anyone making trouble on Noriosse. After this incident is over, our financial group will seek compensation from Godora."

The protector's eyes narrowed. Since he could not save Anur, he had no choice but to give up. However, that did not mean that he would be on the side of Godora. The protective shield must not be opened no matter what. This was the bottom line of the upper echelons in his financial group. His financial group did not wish to see any other superior fighters of DarkStar perish there.

Chapter 502: DarkStar's Shock

While Noriosse did not wish to provoke both parties, there was no need for them to accede to the demands of both parties completely. While this action of theirs might result in conflict with Godora, it was not too serious and within an acceptable range.

The financial group still intended to seek compensation from Godora. With an important figure of DarkStar dead, Godora would be more willing to compromise in other areas. Furthermore, it was impossible for DarkStar to make any form of compensation, but Godora, being a lawful civilization, would definitely be a 'good person' and keep to the rules.

While Nagakin still wanted to persuade the protector, Han Xiao stopped him and did not say another word.

Han Xiao could tell that it was impossible for the financial group to back down and could only give up his plan to surround Ember. While it was a waste that his previous disguise had lost its effect, Han Xiao was used to the situation changing at any moment in time. At the very least, everything went pretty close to his plan.

Since we can't fight, this mission is almost over, and we won't be chased anymore, Han Xiao thought to himself.

Looking up at the sky, a black cloud could be seen floating above him, and Ember's figure could be seen. He had finally rushed back.

Looking at the miserable battlefield through the protective shield, Ember was visibly shocked. With his gaze sweeping over the battlefield, his eyes were suddenly fixed on Anur's corpse, and the shock on his face turned into fear!

Perhaps it isn't completely useless to bait Ember back. Allowing him to see Anur's corpse and dealing him a psychological blow isn't too bad either.

A few minutes earlier...

Ember followed 'Anur's' instructions and sped toward the battlefield. He was looking forward to diving into battle so that he could make up for the mission that he failed.

With Teacher's speed, it is impossible for any enemy to struggle free from him, and it will be impossible for Black Star to escape like before. We can finally get rid of him today!

Thinking about that, Ember was full of anticipation and excitement as he charged over joyfully.

However, the scene before him was completely different from his expectations! He never could have imagined that his undefeatable Teacher would be defeated and even killed!

The instant that he saw Anur's corpse, Ember was completely stunned, and a chill ran up his spine.

How was it possible for Anur to be killed!

Ember immediately took out his communicator and dialed Anur's number.

Du du du...

The few seconds of waiting felt like forever, and when the call finally went through, the image displayed on the screen was not that of Anur but Han Xiao letting out a maniacal laughter.

"Are you surprised? Are you shocked‽"

Ember was indeed shocked. "Why is it you‽"

"Oh, do you not like my handsome face?" Han Xiao chuckled before changing his face to that of Anur's. Sending a flying kiss, he continued. "How about this face?"

Ka-cha!

The screen began to crack.

Ember had almost shattered his communicator in rage. His final hope had just been destroyed!

Anur was really dead!

Numerous emotions filled his heart. Disbelief, anger, panic, grief...

If the enemy could take Anur out, it means that he was also in danger!

"I am the only one left. I cannot stay behind to fight and let all of our soldiers die here!"

Ember gritted his teeth and escaped on his black cloud.

The situation needed to be reported to the upper echelons. Escaping as he reported the situation to his superiors, the news that he reported set off an explosive commotion within the upper echelons of DarkStar!

The upper echelons of DarkStar had been prepared to hear a report of the mission being accomplished but never expected to hear such a nightmare instead.

None of them had expected that Anur would die in this mission, which they had been certain would succeed. Sending out two Calamity Grade Supers at once, all of the upper echelons felt that the mission was a guaranteed success! However, this piece of news had completely disrupted their plans.

The forces of DarkStar had been waning over time. During their peak, DarkStar had eight Calamity Grade Supers, and Anur was one of them. He was a highly-respected figure in the organization. However, the battles over the years had injured and killed the majority of these experts. Before that day, only two of those eight figures had remained, and Anur had been one of them. Apart from those two figures, all the other Grade A Supers were new faces who they were grooming.

Losing such a figure was definitely a huge blow to DarkStar. The rate at which Calamity Grade Supers were groomed could not keep up with the rate that they were being killed at. In the organization, Calamity Grade Supers were already extremely rare.

In less than a minute, the upper echelons of DarkStar gave an emergency order to Ember.

"Give up on the mission and leave Noriosse immediately. We will send a fleet to pick you up. After losing an important member of the organization, we cannot afford to lose another one!"

Originally, he had been the one giving chase, but the roles had been reversed, and he was now the escaping party. Ember was indignant about his loss, but he had no choice and could only swallow his indignation. Turning off his communicator, Ember escaped at top speed and did not dare delay for a second, afraid that the enemy may catch up to him.

In truth, it was impossible for Han Xiao and the others to leave the protective shield. Those from Noriosse wished for Ember to scram as quickly as possible, and Ember did not know that there was no one chasing him.

An hour later...

Ohm!

The protective shield was retracted, and the golden pillars returned underground. Noriosse had finally retracted the protective shield.

This also meant that the financial group was certain that the battle was over. Their surveillance showed DarkStar's fleet picking Ember up before leaving immediately, and everyone from the financial group heaved a sigh of relief. While they had a few thousand battleships around Noriosse, it was best if they did not engage in battle.

With the troops chasing after him retreating, Han Xiao knew that Nagakin's mission was completed. When Godora sent their reinforcements, the mission would be concluded. Getting rid of an Anur was already a good bargain for them.

Despite the battle being over, the effects of the battle had only just begun to show. With a Grade A Super from DarkStar dying, Godora would definitely pay close attention to this event, and the entire Shattered Star Ring would have their eyes on this news. While countless people were dying every single second, there were differences between people. The death of a Calamity Grade Super was naturally far more significant than the death of an ordinary individual.

Furthermore, with him using Ames' abilities, Ames would definitely be very curious.

However, none of that was important at the moment. Dealing with the members of the Noriosse financial group was what they needed to face. After Han Xiao and the others were freed from their predicament, they were immediately requested to meet the upper echelons of the financial group.

The financial group was getting ready to settle their scores, and they had to give Noriosse a suitable amount of compensation.

Chapter 503: Effect and Plan

The protector took everyone to another city on an aircraft. In the middle of the city was a skyscraper. Even in the iron city that was filled with buildings, the skyscraper stood out like a middle finger being pointed to the sky.

At the peak of the skyscraper was a helipad protected by a transparent cover. The cover gradually opened up, and the aircraft landed on the helipad. From the helipad to the interior of the building, numerous soldiers were lined up orderly by the side. Han Xiao and the others followed after the protector and entered the top level of the luxurious skyscraper.

A man was seated on the sofa with his back facing the crowd who had entered the room. He was looking at a wall of holographic screens with the scenes of the battlefield being displayed on them.

"Look at what you have done on my planet."

After pressing a button, the sofa turned around on its own to face Han Xiao. After seeing his appearance, Han Xiao felt that he looked extremely familiar. All of a sudden, Han Xiao remembered seeing a picture of this person before him.

A couple of days ago, he had still been playing a cat and mouse game with Aesop. Aesop had requested for him to steal an accessory. After he asked Phillip to make a search, Han Xiao had found out that the accessory was something that the head of the Noriosse financial group had purchased his wife. The person in front of him was the head of the financial group. Just what was he called again?

"Rockfess. I am the owner of this planet," the man said with a calm voice. "I know who you are. Nagakin from Godora, Wilsander from Floating Dragon, and Black Star also from Floating Dragon."

Because he belonged to Floating Dragon on the surface, the Black Star Mercenary Group was deemed a part of the Floating Dragon army. Han Xiao was not too bothered by this as the status of being part of Floating Dragon had always brought him more benefits than disadvantages. Allowing his mercenary group to be tied together with a gigantic faction was extremely helpful to the growth and fame of his mercenary group.

"I have roughly understood what happened, and I am uninterested in the battle between Godora and DarkStar. However, your actions have resulted in damage to my planet, and Godora has no rights to deploy their army in my territory. I require an explanation from all of you and suitable compensation. My subordinates are currently calculating the exact damage, and we shall negotiate the details after they are done."

Rockfess did not give the two a chance to interrupt and spoke without allowing anyone to refute him.

"I will report this matter to headquarters, and Godora will compensate your losses. Black Star is only a mercenary who I hired, and his actions were part of my request. Godora will never shortchange our friends, and Godora will compensate you on his behalf."

With Anur being killed, Nagakin was in an extremely good mood. For an official of his level, taking action would definitely result in destruction, and there would definitely be people to clean up after them. He had never thought about escaping from paying compensation before.

Because Rockfess had extremely good connections and had a pretty good relationship with a couple of civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring, Godora was not willing to offend him either.

"Don't worry, I never intended to seek compensation from him." Upon hearing that, Rockfess looked toward Han Xiao with a smile, and his tone became gentler. "Give my regards to Ames."

He actually isn't asking for compensation? Han Xiao immediately felt goodwill toward Rockfess, "You know Ames?"

"Hahaha, who in the Shattered Star Ring doesn't know of the Dragon Emperor?" Rockfess said with a laugh. "I have dealt with Floating Dragon a few times. I heard that Aesop wanted you to steal something of mine, but you caught him instead. Haha, well done."

Han Xiao came to a realization. It turned out that Rockfess knew Aesop. No wonder there was such a prank.

However, Han Xiao did not think that it was strange at all. After being alive for so many years, Aesop was a legendary figure, and his connections were extremely deep with his friends being scattered all over the universe.

With Aesop's abilities, the figures whom he befriended were naturally those with authority and power. Since Ames had taken Aesop back, Floating Dragon would definitely receive a huge boost, and their hidden forces would definitely be expanded.

In truth, Rockfess' warm attitude was not entirely because of Aesop. He had always been supplying resources to Floating Dragon but had rarely requested anything in return, treating it as a form of sponsorship. Rockfess was not the only financial group that was doing so, and there were at least twenty different financial groups sponsoring Ames. When Ames first built Floating Dragon Island, she had released a notice that she wanted money, and numerous financial groups had swarmed over to give her money immediately. After so many years, there were many financial groups that still maintained their sponsorship status. If not, with Floating Dragon's horrendous management situation, it would have been impossible for them to support all the maintenance, repairs, and other expenses.

Behind every one of the four beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring were numerous financial groups. A powerful organization would always draw a large number of willing sponsors; thus, these powerful beings never needed to be afraid of going broke. Many of the financial groups in the universe were past the stage of accumulating wealth, and if they were not able to convert their wealth into influence or something useful, their wealth was no more than a useless string of numbers. Investing their wealth into such organizations that housed powerhouses was the best option for them.

For someone like Ames, it was no longer her asking others for money but others taking the initiative to offer her money. Whether or not so wanted to accept the money was dependent on her mood.

As long as one became sufficiently powerful, many problems would be taken care of easily. At the same time, however, one's actions and words would also take on more responsibility.

In the later versions, a few unions would have the right to cooperate with the financial groups to obtain resources and funds. The impact of the players' presence in Galaxy became deeper and deeper, and there were more and more avenues for both parties to interact. The influence that they had on the world was extremely dynamic and realistic, thus allowing the players to remain passionate about the game.

"I heard about your arrival as soon as you stepped onto Noriosse. Meeting you in person, you are even more powerful than in the legends."

Rockfess took the initiative to reach out, and Han Xiao shook his hand. Smiling without saying a word, a thought suddenly surfaced in his head.

His plans for Version 2.0 would require a large amount of gold. To hold millions of players in his mercenary group, the hardware of his mercenary group must have an all-round upgrade, and all of that required money.

If he could mimic Ames and find sponsors, it may be much easier on his wallet.

Because Han Xiao was used to being a lone wolf in his previous life, he only had a vague understanding of deals between the guilds and NPCs. However, Han Xiao had never given it a try himself, and he needed to earn all of the money required for his plan. At this moment, a new idea sprung up in his mind. Perhaps the influence of a faction may be larger than I think.

Until then, Han Xiao's core business had been to earn the player's money to upgrade himself and his faction. However, could he improvise a little and get the NPCs to give him money while harvesting the money from players?

With this flash of inspiration, a new and exciting plan began to form in his head. While the plan was not feasible for the time being, it would greatly increase the benefits that the players could give him once Version 2.0 was unveiled. Of course, that was predicated on everything going according to his plan.

"Your Excellency Rockfess," Han Xiao said, "I actually have something that I wish to request and hope that we can find some time to discuss the matter."

"Alright, I will give you my personal number." Rockfess nodded. "After this matter is over, we can talk about it in detail."

A conclusion was made regarding the matter of compensation—Godora would be in charge of paying for all compensation. Rockfess then arranged for a completely safe stronghold for them to stay in. Before the reinforcements from Godora arrived, they were all required to stay there.

Aroshia met up with Alvin and the others. Alvin was extremely thankful that he had managed to escape death, and the Teleportation Mage left immediately after receiving his payment. He did not wish to have any relationship with those unlucky people.

Over the next few days, the news of this great battle began to spread rapidly, and the headlines of the various news outlets were getting more and more exaggerated.

The details of the battle were not leaked, and the various articles only reported a small portion of the battle and the outcome. While the infamous DarkStar was not the most powerful organization on the list of evil organizations within the Shattered Star Ring, it was the most radical one. It had destroyed many civilizations within the Garton Star System and caused countless citizens to lose their homes. However, there was rarely news of a head-on battle with DarkStar as they usually snuck into the various civilizations stealthily.

This time, a powerful member of DarkStar had died in the eyes of the public, and it was a truly joyous occasion.

With the news spreading, Han Xiao received multiple notifications of his Renown stat increasing on his interface. Just like before, his Renown stat increased in various Star Clusters, and his Renown level had reached [Slightly Famous] in most regions. In the Garton Star System, where he was most active, his Renown level had already reached the level of [Well Known].

In the eyes of most galactic residents, Ames' strength was the only supporting pillar for the whole of Floating Dragon. However, her subordinates did not have much fame and rarely took action outside of Floating Dragon. In this respect, Floating Dragon was far inferior to the powers of the other three beyond Grade A Supers. The other three beyond Grade A Supers all had numerous experts under their charge with their soldiers being the elites of the elites. However, Ames only had a couple of little cats as her subordinates.

For the organizations of the other three beyond Grade A Supers, even if they did not have their leader, their organization would still be a tyrannical existence.

During the previous incident when Ames smashed up DarkStar's mothership, the majority of the focus had been on Ames' strength as well as the new member of Floating Dragon, Black Star. However, the news this time had shown Black Star's strength, and many of the galactic residents and organizations had the same thought.

Ames finally has a capable officer. Sigh, it truly isn't easy!

Godora was clearer about the details of the entire event. According to Nagakin's report, the intelligence division of Godora's War Bureau immediately placed a greater importance on Han Xiao. Together with the incident when they captured DarkStar's mothership, this was the second time that Black Star had dealt a blow to DarkStar. Thus, he could be said to be on Godora's side. Furthermore, Han Xiao had also aided Nagakin in killing Anur and gave them a huge aid.

After fighting together with Han Xiao, Nagakin also treated him with great importance.

In those few days, Han Xiao had specially built up his ties with Nagakin. This was also the reason behind him accepting this mission. Building up ties with Nagakin meant that he would have a direct channel to the upper echelons of Godora.

After waiting for a few days, the Godoran fleet arrived at Noriosse, and the entire event was finally over. Nagakin took Alvin to the pier where Godora's gigantic fleet was waiting.

Before he left, Alvin took the initiative to shake hands with Han Xiao. "You saved my life, and I owe you a favor. If you need my help, I will definitely do my best to aid you."

Nagakin also expressed his thanks toward Han Xiao. "It is truly a pleasant experience to work with you, and the War Bureau will pay you your reward. I hope that we have the chance to work together again."

Han Xiao smiled. "Don't worry, we will meet again very soon."

Nagakin was stunned for a moment and thought that Han Xiao was only being polite. He then boarded the ship with Alvin, and the fleet quickly disappeared into space.

[Nagakin's request] has been completed.

You have received 5,800,000 Experience, 240,000 Enas, +850 Relationship with Godora Faction.

Godoran Civilization: Respect (3190/6000)

+30 Nagakin Favorability

+30 Alvin Favorability

Adding close to 2,000 points of faction favorability and raising my relationship with Godora to Respect. This isn't too bad.

Originally, Nagakin would have been crippled, and Alvin would not have survived. The fates of these two individuals had been changed by him, so DarkStar would definitely pay more attention to him. Who knew what kind of a reaction they would have?

"Where are we going?" Herlous asked, and everyone looked at Han Xiao.

Han Xiao stroked his chin. Before the new version was released, he had two targets. The first was his advancement. With his advancement being complete and him being freer, it was time to work toward his second target—prepare for Version 2.0. This was a huge project.

"Let me meet Rockfess first."

Chapter 504: Getting Investments

"So, what request do you have, Black Star of Floating Dragon?"

Han Xiao was once again seated in Rockfess' luxurious property, but this time, it was a private meeting between the two of them. They were seated face to face with the servants serving them tea.

After a couple of pleasantries, Rockfess went straight to the point.

"My time in precious. Please let me know if you have any requests."

Han Xiao put down his glass and leaned forward. "I shall be straightforward then. My mercenary group is the Floating Dragon's Field Team, and we have been operating for a year and a half. It is time for my mercenary group to expand. With the prestige of Ames on my shoulders, I cannot continue to have little battles and skirmishes. Blades and Sky Ring should be the target of my Black Star Mercenary Group. The stronger the Field Team, the stronger Floating Dragon will be. Thus, I need some funds to support me. I want to build a stronghold that belongs to my mercenary group and not rent a temporary gathering point."

His preparation plan for Version 2.0 was to expand his camp before pulling all the players from Planet Aquamarine into his mercenary group during the Mutation Disaster. Both Godora and DarkStar would be his competitors, and Han Xiao wanted to give the players a third choice. Apart from the original 'righteous' and 'evil' path, Han Xiao wanted to provide the path of 'neutral'.

As such, there was a huge problem that he faced. In order to contain thousands or millions of players, the size of his camp would have to be greatly increased. If not, he would not be able to attract new members.

The most important factor to attract players was benefits. Even if Bun-Hit-Dog's program was able to brainwash a large number of spectators to be attracted to mercenary groups, it would be difficult to sustain their interest for a long time. Thus, it was key for him to provide players with missions and resources. With regards to this, Han Xiao already had a plan. He had created the mercenary group so that he could be the middleman to distribute the missions and form the bridge between the players and clients. At the same time, he would be able to borrow the almost endless mission resources to groom his own faction and keep players in his camp while building up the reputation of his mercenary group.

Apart from taking advantage of the mercenary groups, he also intended to make use of NPC resources to bring him more benefits.

Other than the resources given by missions, another important point was the special produce of a faction. On top of attracting investments, class knowledge, and skills, producing machinery would be his specialty. However, it would be impossible for him to fulfil a large order alone, and he had to consider the problem of mass production. He needed to form his own assembly line and build a factory of his own. With his current knowledge and skill, he would be able to just about create an assembly line.

Thus, the second problem would surface. Where should he place the assembly line? After accepting so many players, his mercenary group would need a large, fixed gathering point that was akin to his faction's Main City. If not, he would not be able to incite a sense of belonging in all the players. Only after building up his own Main City would his forces look like a proper army. However, the location, security, resources, and functions of this gathering point were all problems.

As such, the third problem surfaced—transport! With the members under his charge exploding in numbers, going out on missions would be a problem. It would be ridiculous for the players to rent a ship whenever they wanted to travel, and it was not beneficial to attracting the players to his Main City. He needed to have a spaceship that belonged to his faction. If not, he needed to come to a long-term agreement with some Galactic Travel Agencies.

These were only the fundamental problems, and there were still many more little problems that he would face along the way, such as finding a stable supplier for materials, contacting a construction company, and so on. Expanding his faction was akin to expanding the operations of a company. If he wanted to expand his scope of influence, he had to prepare many things in large quantities, and that all required money.

Together with the reward from Nagakin, Han Xiao had about 500,000 Enas left. After a series of calculations, Han Xiao truly found his entire wealth to be pretty pathetic, and his heart would ache if he had to fork out the expenses required for his faction to expand. Thus, he decided to meet Rockfess and talk to him about the matter of investment.

"Expanding the scale of the Field Team..." Rockfess' eyes narrowed. "Is this Ames' order?"

"You should understand that Ames would never bother about such affairs," Han Xiao replied. "I am the one in charge of the Field Team, and this is my own plan."

"I knew that it wasn't her idea," Rockfess said with a smile that did not seem like a smile. "How much money do you want?"

"How much are you willing to give?" Han Xiao threw the question back.

Rockfess immediately changed the subject. "Up until now, I have provided nine sponsorships to Floating Dragon, a total of about 24,000,000, and this will not be the final figure. I intend to keep sponsoring Floating Dragon. Jenny and I can be considered old acquaintances, and the benefits that she brings me are the reason that I will not waver in my investment. Enjoying the prestige of Ames, I am able to earn a profit that is to my satisfaction."

After saying those words, he kept quiet and looked at Han Xiao with a smile, obviously waiting for Han Xiao to say what sort of benefits he could provide.

Through investing in Floating Dragon, he gained the acknowledgement of Jenny and enjoyed a portion of Ames' influence. He then borrowed the influence for political activities or negotiations. It was equivalent to exchanging his investment for influence and to use influence to make money. The amount of money that he was able to make definitely exceeded his initial investment. Such returns could only be gained if he invested in the headquarters of Floating Dragon. Why should he make an investment in Floating Dragon's Field Team? Furthermore, this was Han Xiao's personal plan. He would only provide money if it was Ames' plan; Black Star did not command such respect.

Han Xiao smiled and suddenly said, "I believe that you have my information in your hands. If that's the case, you should know that I have a bunch of undying warriors under me."

"Yes." Rockfess nodded. "I have also noticed that they are not with you right now."

"They are natural born mercenaries, and their numbers far exceed your imagination. I know all of them, and expanding my mercenary group also includes expanding my numbers. I do not need to hire any other mercenaries on the market. With your investment, I will be able to rapidly expand my forces and become a large mercenary group. At that time, I will give you satisfactory benefits. Even if you have Jenny's approval, you will require the appearance of Floating Dragon's troops to help you persuade the other party at times, right? What about a large mercenary group willing to accept your private hire at no cost?"

Han Xiao selectively revealed some details of his plans. In order to persuade others to invest, he would naturally have to paint a picture of the possible benefits. While the stock market existed in Galaxy, a mercenary group was far from entering it. Thus, he naturally did not have the right to gain something without risking anything of his own.

He was not afraid of revealing the existence of players. The players would enter the galaxy eventually, and they would then be exposed to everyone. Since Galaxy was currently going through an update, even if he told Rockfess some information, the other party would not be able to do a thing because it was impossible to find any players for the time being!

This was his new plan. Allowing the NPCs to recognize the potential of players and attract their investments.

At that moment, he was only testing his idea to see the feasibility of his plan.

Rockfess fell into deep thought and did not say a word. Han Xiao's suggestion did indeed interest him. Helping Floating Dragon build up their Field Team might be a good plan. While Black Star was a member of Floating Dragon, he did not trust Black Star enough to invest without any worries.

Han Xiao thought that he would have to wait for a long time. However, Rockfess made a decision less than ten seconds later.

"I will not invest."

"What a pity." Han Xiao shook his head. "You missed out on an investment that could bring you endless benefits."

At that time, Rockfess added, "However, I can give you a loan. 4,000,000 Enas and a three-year limit. On account of Floating Dragon, I will give you a simple interest plan. If you return the money within a month, I will not charge you any interest. Paying me back after one year and before two years, I will charge you a ten percent interest. More than two years and before three years, twenty percent interest. Above three years, forty percent interest. These are my conditions."

Han Xiao's mouth twitched. This interest rate was truly explosive. If he exceeded three years, it was enough to make his pants explode. It was no different from borrowing from loan sharks at that rate. Furthermore, this was on account that he belonged to Floating Dragon. If not, it would have been impossible for Rockfess to lend him any money.

Being rich is truly...

"Alright, I agree."

Han Xiao nodded. He was not worried about paying back the loan. Version 2.0 would be launched within a year. As long as the players returned, Han Xiao would probably count money to the point that his brain would cramp!

Not to mention returning the loan, even if he wanted to buy the whole Noriosse financial group... cough cough, he still would not be able to afford it.

Rockfess took out his communicator and sent him a contract. With both parties signing their names, the contract became legally binding. In the majority of the civilizations, this contract would be protected by the law. In his previous life, there had been a few guilds that did not wish to repay their debts. This had caused their Favorability to plummet with all these civilizations, and their upper limit of Favorability with those factions was set to 2,999 points. It meant that they would never be able to reach the level of [Respect]. On top of that, their personal Trust level was also reduced, and they would not be able to borrow again. In serious cases, they even ended up as fugitives.

If a guild wanted to take out a loan, it required a great deal of effort to raise the Favorability with a faction. If they did not return the money, it was akin to throwing away all of that Favorability. Any guilds with foresight would never permit such an action, which was akin to shooting themselves in the foot.

Han Xiao did not have the intention to do so either.

Ding.

Han Xiao received a notification of an incoming transfer. Taking a glance, the amount of Enas in his savings increased to 4,581,010.

Rockfess had given him the money without any fuss. For a wealthy merchant who would spend 7,000,000 Enas to buy an accessory, such a small investment was nothing to him.

However, to Han Xiao, this was a large sum of money.

"Let's work well together."

Standing up, Han Xiao shook Rockfess' hand and left the luxurious property under the lead of the butler. He returned directly to the inn, where Herlous and the others were waiting. After supervising Sylvia's homework for a while, he went back to his room.

I was really able to get an investment. If seems like the influence of a faction is truly greater than I thought. With money on hand, I only need to choose a place, and I will be able to construct a large camp. Er... which planet would be better? It cannot be too far away from Planet Aquamarine but has to be tightly connected to the galaxy...

Du du du...

Just when he was in thought, his communicator rang, and Head Butler Jenny called. Her expression was unfriendly, and she immediately interrogated Han Xiao when he picked up the call.

"Rockfess already informed me that you sought a loan from him. Why didn't you inform me beforehand?"

"Jenny, would you have agreed?"

"Don't call me Jenny, you should call me Head Butler. And, of course, I don't agree." Jenny's tone was strict. She had never believed in expanding, and setting up a Field Team was an unnecessary expenditure to her in the first place. Ames would never require a powerful army.

"Then why should I tell you?" Han Xiao replied. He understood Jenny's personality. She was an individual who wanted extremely tight control of business and finances. She would never agree to the expansion of the Field Team. While they belonged to the same faction, there were clashes in their ideals and responsibilities.

Of course, the main reason was because Jenny did not trust him enough. After all, he was a mercenary who had joined Floating Dragon midway.

"I command you to return the loan," Jenny said in a tone that brooked no argument. "Without my permission, you are not allowed to accept any form of funds!"

Chapter 505: Location of the Base

Jenny's attitude was extremely forceful, and she looked as though she would not let Han Xiao off if he chose to defy her. However, the Great Mechanic Han was not afraid of her, and it was impossible for him to return the money.

He then briefly explained the benefits that his actions could bring Floating Dragon, and without bothering whether Jenny accepted his words or not, he hung up.

This action of his frustrated Jenny greatly. Her desire for control was great, and for Han Xiao to take a loan without getting her approval made her feel as though her position of Head Butler was being challenged. She had also begun to suspect Han Xiao's 'loyalty' at the same time. Ames had never been bothered with the management of Floating Dragon and handed everything over to her to handle. Thus, the majority of the consequences brought about by Ames' actions were usually settled by her. She possessed a great deal of authority, and Ames also trusted Jenny greatly. Furthermore, most of the members in Floating Dragon would also submit to Jenny's authority.

Black Star had joined Floating Dragon a year ago and had always been extremely low profile. However, this sudden action of his had immediately incited that sensitive nerve of Jenny's and made her raise her guard. Deep within, she did not trust any other subordinates of Ames, and because she was Ames' kin, she felt that only she and Ames were insiders while the others were outsiders.

After Han Xiao cut off the line, Jenny made a call of complaint to Ames without any hesitation. She explained everything that had happened to Ames and added her own opinions. She felt that Han Xiao's Field Team had too much freedom and needed to be controlled. It would be best to transfer him back to the headquarters of Floating Dragon and remove the Field Team completely. She felt that since Floating Dragon wanted to maintain neutrality, it was sufficient for them to be Dragon Guards. There was no need for them to have an armed force operating outside.

Under normal circumstances, Ames would not reject her proposal. However, Ames unexpectedly rejected her.

"You are too nervous. It is just a bit of money, and there isn't a need to make a huge fuss out of the matter. I trust Black Star; he is someone reliable. Since I gave him the right to operate freely, as long as he doesn't become a wanted fugitive, you don't have to inform me. If there isn't anything else, I am hanging up."

"But..."

Ka-cha.

Ames hung up the line, and a stunned Jenny was left behind. She held onto her communicator with a dazed look. She had never imagined that Ames would reject her flatly. This was something that had not happened before.

Because Han Xiao had caught Aesop, Ames' trust in him had increased tremendously. While her trust in Han Xiao could not be compared to the trust that she had in Jenny, it was far more than the trust that she would have in an ordinary subordinate.

Without Ames' approval, Jenny realized that she could not do a thing to Han Xiao. Exasperated, her veins began to bulge, and her body trembled slightly with anger. Taking a deep breath, she took off her spectacles and shut her eyes. After rubbing the bridge of her nose, she gradually regained her cool. When she opened her eyes again, her eyes were filled with solemnness.

Ames' rejection had made Jenny feel a huge threat to her position.

Han Xiao naturally did not know that this small conflict would make Jenny misunderstand that he was trying to fight for favor with her. However, even if he knew, he would not have been bothered. After all, the money required for his Version 2.0 plan was more important.

The version update would take less than a year, and it was important for Han Xiao to use this time to find a place and build his base. Han Xiao would not choose a deserted planet and would definitely build his base on a flourishing planet. He would then be able to enjoy the NPC resources of the planet and use the geographical location to make up for the lack of NPCs in his base.

After searching for a long time in the Garton Star System map, he finally chose a planet in Godora's territory called Planet Golden Gate. It was very near to Juberly Hub, and he would be able to easily arrive at the star zone where Planet Aquamarine was located. This meant that transportation would be extremely convenient. On top of that, the planet was sufficiently prosperous, and from a player's perspective, all the necessary features were present. There were shops, entertainment outlets, missions...

There were two reasons behind Han Xiao's choice. Firstly, his Favorability with Godora was high, so it was easier for him to get things done. Furthermore, he would be able to enjoy a discount. Secondly, he would be able to lower his expenses on setting up weapons. A powerful fleet would definitely be stationed within Godora's territory, and DarkStar would not dare create trouble there. After getting rid of Anur a while back, Han Xiao had decided to place safety as a priority.

Furthermore, since they were in Godora's territory, they would be able to filter out the players who joined DarkStar. With the Germinal Organization as an example, Han Xiao did not wish for there to be a bunch of spies in his base.

Among all of the planets, Planet Golden Gate was the top choice.

After choosing his target, Han Xiao did not delay any further and left Noriosse.

Because Risda had joined their group, the Blacklight Stealth became their new ship. Its speed was extremely fast and movements agile. They no longer had to worry about being surrounded by enemies.

Planet Golden Gate was not a large planet, but because it was situated near Juberly Hub, it was very prosperous. Planet Golden Gate had plenty of different cities, and setting up a base there required the purchase of a permit. With the Renown of the Black Star Mercenary Group being sufficiently high within the Garton Star System, together with the fact that their relationship with Godora was pretty good, there was no problem in the application of the permit.

After spending a large amount of money, Han Xiao managed to buy a piece of land, and the efficiency of settling all the paperwork was extremely high. With the sheer size of the universe, land was abundant, and it was unbelievably cheap for an ordinary immigrant to purchase a house.

With the current wealth in his hands, Han Xiao did not have any intention of building a large main city yet. He did not have enough people or money. He only needed a fixed base for his Mercenary Group.

As for the design of the base, it had to be sufficiently big. Apart from providing a large number of players with a region to hang out, he needed to leave space for military factories. On top of that, he had to ensure that the roads are well designed and regions demarcated so that the players would not get lost in the base. Most importantly, the base had to be impressive and sufficiently high class.

With the sheer scale of the construction, Han Xiao naturally did not intend to do so himself. He contacted a construction company to build the place according to his designs. From the construction to the purchase of materials and transportation, every single aspect required a large amount of wealth.

While he was starting to build his first base, Ember had returned to the headquarters of DarkStar. At that time, the upper echelons of DarkStar were having a meeting to discuss the incident on Noriosse.

In the mysterious headquarters of DarkStar, ten or so individuals were gathered in a hall. Some were present physically while others joined the meeting through a holographic projection. Their faces were all hidden as they sat on a circular table.

Everyone in the room was at the highest level in the DarkStar organization. There were some Calamity Grade Supers, fleet commanders, logistics directors, intelligence agents, research staff, and the leader in charge of all affairs.

The majority of their identities were secret and not privy to outsiders. At this moment, the atmosphere was extremely heavy. With the traitor alive, all of their identities could be exposed, and they were all in a terrible mood.

Ember was also in the room. After reaching the Calamity Grade, he had the right to be present in that room. From time to time, the other members seated at the table would look at him with an unfriendly gaze.

Because of his mission failure, all of them had to endure the risk of being exposed, so they could not help but blame Ember, the only one who had returned alive.

Noticing the gazes of the others, Ember knew that he was in the wrong and could only remain silent.

Beside him was an empty seat.

That seat had belonged to Anur.

With his respected teacher dead, every time he saw this empty chair, Ember would be reminded of Han Xiao. The flames of rage would then burn, and he would spend a great amount of effort to suppress it.

After a long period of silence, the leader of DarkStar opened his mouth. "Anur died in combat, and the traitor was saved by Godora. This mission was a complete failure."

"Before the traitor gained access to the top-secret intel, I froze his authority," the person in charge of intelligence said with a hoarse voice. "The intel in his hands is only a small portion. This is the only good news."

"Is the traitor aware of the mutation virus?"

"No, he isn't aware about our plan. This requires a higher level of authority."

"That's good. This is an important step in our plan, and nothing can go wrong. It won't be too long before the virus spreads, and Godora will be forced to send out a great deal of manpower to protect the affected civilizations. We will be able to seize the initiative..."

The leader of DarkStar then paused and changed topics. "I am extremely disappointed in the outcome of this mission. Not only did we let the traitor escape, we had even lost a Calamity Grade doyen. Ember, you have truly let me down this time."

Ember clenched his fists and said with difficulty, "Something went wrong in the mission."

"You are trying to say that as long as something goes wrong, you won't be able to handle it?"

Ember noticed the chill in the leader's voice and lowered his head without answering.

At this moment, another member spoke up. "This was your first mission after becoming a Grade A Super. To think that the outcome would be so embarrassing! Aren't you ashamed? I truly wonder if you have the right to be in this room."

The one who spoke was another respected Calamity Grade who had even more influence than Anur. He was the vice leader and the right-hand man of the leader.

Ember's clenched fists tightened, but he did not retort. After becoming a Calamity Grade Super, he had been full of ambition and pride. However, this mission had ended in complete failure, so he was starting to doubt himself.

"I saw the mission report. Godora's Nagakin joint hands with a mercenary to kill Anur. That mercenary is called Black Star." The DarkStar leader changed the topic and did not allow the others to continue blaming Ember. It was sufficient to warn him, and it was not necessary to humiliate him.

"Kill him!" Ember said without hesitation.

"He is Ames' subordinate, and I do not wish to have a conflict with someone like the Dragon Emperor before the start of our mutation virus plan," the leader of DarkStar said. "I will make that mercenary pay the price, but not now."

"He has caused us to suffer losses over and over again, and he is an enemy whom we must eradicate. We cannot wait any longer!" Ember could not help but retort. He wished that he could reduce Han Xiao to ashes in front of him.

The one in charge of intelligence said calmly, "According to my intel, Black Star is building a base on Planet Golden Gate. That planet is within Godora's territory. If we want to get rid of him, we will have to send a large fleet. To incite such a huge battle with Godora at this important stage, do you want to ruin the organization's plan?"

"This is worth it!" Ember grit his teeth and insisted on his view.

"Enough!" The leader of DarkStar interrupted Ember. "From now on, cease all other activities on the outside until the mutation virus spreads. I do not wish to repeat myself. The meeting shall end here."

All the upper echelons did not say another word and went offline. Those who were there personally left the meeting room. Only Ember was left in his seat with a look of indignation. Looking at the empty room, a trace of anger flashed through his eyes.

Chapter 506: Mass Production Design, Onset of the Disaster

On Planet Golden Gate of the Garton Star System, the Black Star base was rapidly being constructed as Han Xiao had contracted a professional construction company. In the galaxy era, the efficiency of constructing buildings was extremely high and almost everything was automated. Building a foundation, mixing cement, laying the walls, laying the lines, and so on were all jobs that could be completed quickly. As long as the raw materials were present, the construction team would be able to construct a building identical to the blueprints in a short amount of time.

Ten or so days went by in a flash, and a metal base rose up from the ground. This base was enough to house seventy to eighty thousand people. Its size was sufficiently huge, and its geography was simple. According to the blueprints, the base was separated into a few different sectors. However, the facilities were not up yet, and the base was only an empty shell.

The funds that Han Xiao currently had on hand were pretty abundant, and he did not have to be so restricted. He needed to build a factory assembly line, equip his base with weapons, and build a main system to control the entire base. All of those facilities needed to be built by him, and the main expenditure would come from the resources.

Following which, he had to solve the problem of transportation. Buying a spaceship was far too costly, and he was prepared to strike a deal with some Galactic Travel Agencies. He wanted to rent their spaceships long term. After deducting those expenditures, he would still be left with about two to three million Enas.

The problem with transportation was not urgent, and he would only require it when the players returned. Han Xiao had to first forge an assembly line. The assembly line was a requirement for him to build up an army, and he needed the relevant Advanced Knowledge and High-End Knowledge. Han Xiao had learned the majority of the Advanced Knowledge, and his huge capital allowed him to purchase new High-End Knowledge.

He instantly used a few hundred thousand Enas to buy the High-End Knowledge of the Armed Branch, [Huge Duplex Machinery Technology]. This knowledge was one of the requirements for him to build battleships and other Super large machines. He then followed the knowledge groups in his memory and merged the relevant key blueprint, [Automated Mass Production Plan]. It was not only the blueprint for an assembly line, it was also the core of an army. As long as the raw materials available were sufficient, the assembly line would be able to automatically manufacture the weapons, and it would save Han Xiao both time and effort. The only thing it did not save was money.

The assembly line was a special type of blueprint that could not be constructed on its own. If it was a player who attempted to do so, the player would need to first activate the assembly line blueprint and leave it in the active state before using the blueprint of another machine. This was the process to create a machinery assembly line, and it was like a form of combined skill.

The construction process of every assembly line had some differences. For example, the construction of cavalry and black panthers required a different production process. Thus, the assembly line of every different machine would have to be constructed individually. The raw materials required for every machine were different, and the sheer cost of the raw materials from the assembly line was enough to make a player's wallet fall into despair. If not, there would not be the saying that the Army Style was the most money burning strategy in the game.

Han Xiao's current Army Style was merely second-rate with his main focus being low cost. He was truly some distance away from the true Army Style. The main reason was that he did not have too much money to burn in the past. With sufficient funds on hand, he could finally start with his plan to create an army.

After all, the strength of a Mechanic was directly related to their wealth.

The specialty of Han Xiao's [Ordnance Engineer] subclass was [Military Machinery Enlightenment], and it lowered the cost of building an assembly line while raising the quality of the created product.

Apart from creating a large mechanic army, the other motive of an assembly line was to forge the equipment that players were willing to purchase in bulk. At that time, he would be able to sell that equipment in bulk and use the money earned to create more equipment...

He could then open up a few different outlets with one shop becoming two, two becoming four, four becoming eight, eight becoming a listed company, gathering funds from being a listed company, then selling his stocks, then letting his subsidiary company be listed, then from just collecting interest he could... Cough cough, this was roughly what he meant. Just thinking about it, the Great Mechanic Han felt his mood brighten up.

The higher a machine's grade, the more complex its assembly line would be. Even with Han Xiao's current assembly speed, he needed a few days to complete a single assembly line. Thus, it was important for him to carefully consider which assembly lines he should build. After a long period of consideration, Han Xiao decided to place his focus on low grade machines. His level was truly too far ahead of the players, and the low-grade machines to him were just right for the players who were around level 60.

As for the high-grade machines, there was no need to create an assembly line at the moment. Han Xiao was currently level 116, and because of the Noriosse incident, Han Xiao had not had the chance to have an all-round upgrade of his core machines. Building a base was a long-term project, and Han Xiao finally had the time to upgrade his equipment.

Because of the reward from killing Anur, the amount of experience that he had in the interface had increased to 300,000,000. He first upgraded his [Automated Mass Production Plan] to the maximum level to reduce its cost to the minimum. He then gambled to obtain a large variety of low-grade machines and chose a few suitable blueprints to form an assembly line. With his understanding of the Mechanic class and the players, he was certain that the machines produced would definitely be useful.

Constructing an assembly line was a huge project, so before that, he built a main system for the base and got Phillip to manage the base. The very first assembly line that he wanted to set up was an assistant type machine. Allowing an AI like Phillip to operate those assistant type machines would definitely be extremely effective.

Following the blueprint that he had left behind, Phillip began to command more and more assistant type machines to complete the different districts of the base such as new furniture, security doors, equipment, and instruments. Han Xiao no longer needed to personally supervise those tasks.

The preparation for Version 2.0 required everyone to stay in the base for a long period of time. Herlous did not care and trusted that Han Xiao had his plans. As for the others, they cared even less. The Volga brothers and Sylvia were okay with following Han Xiao for anything. Feidin would not leave before suppressing Chen Xing completely. Risda was extremely patient. After waiting for a long time, he was not bothered about this little delay. He also did not mind letting Han Xiao use his body.

Wilsander returned to Floating Dragon, and the only ones left operating on the outside of Floating Dragon were Han Xiao and his crew.

Han Xiao was very clear that Floating Dragon was definitely aware of him constructing a base on the outside. Since Ames had not said anything to him, Han Xiao understood that Ames was silently allowing him to expand the armed forces. This trust that Ames had in him truly made him feel grateful.

Because of the base, Han Xiao's core members temporarily stopped accepting any new missions, and only the Sunil Division was still active. This piece of news spread through the galaxy very quickly, and the news of Han Xiao constructing a base made many organizations misunderstand something. They all felt that this was a signal.

Does the Dragon Emperor finally want to mimic the other three beyond Grade A Supers and strengthen her armed forces‽

All along, Han Xiao's 'Floating Dragon Field Team' had only existed in name, and few organizations had paid any attention to them. However, this action of his made many organizations and powerhouses fearful as they paid close attention to Han Xiao.

The construction of the base proceeded slowly but steadily.

As time passed, all of the mutation sources that DarkStar had stealthily placed in the planets began to awaken.

"... it's like this. In two days, there have been over 2,700 violent incidents globally, and over 100,000 people have been affected. This is only the information that we have managed to find out. The intel department has investigated the identities of all those who burst out in violence. They come from all different occupations and are spread all across the different cities. There wasn't a single sign of violence before the incident took place, and there isn't any pattern to the violence. Currently, the majority of those who broke out in violence are being detained by the enforcement agencies of the Six Nations and are undergoing investigation."

A member of the intel department read the report. Bennett sat on the chair with his brows furrowed. He looked a little older than he had two years ago.

After Han Xiao's departure, Planet Aquamarine had begun to stabilize socially. The Six Nations were resting and had stopped fighting wars with each other. The refugees also had a place to go.

But over the past few days, violence had broken out in many different regions, and the sheer number of these incidents had immediately drawn the attention of the Six Nations and Bennett.

"Sir, we have collated all of the information and noticed something in common..." the intel officer said with an obvious fear in his voice.

"Speak," Bennett said with a deep voice.

"All of the incidents can be split into three groups with the time of the violence in each group happening within a ten second interval in a few hundred different locations around the world as though they had all come to an agreement beforehand. However, after checking the records, these people did not contact each other in private..."

A solemn look could be seen in Bennett's eyes. This situation was too unusual!

The intel officer was sweating profusely. "Furthermore, the locations of the events also include a few of our Sanctuaries. Many refugees that we have taken in also broke out in violence."

"How are the body conditions of these refugees?"

"Their bodies heated up when we detained them, and they are unconscious. The result of the doctor's check was that their brain activity was far higher than usual, resulting in their organs being overly excited. According to the information from our informants, this is also the same as those who were detained by the Six Nations."

"All of them fell unconscious?" Bennett said with a tinge of shock and fear. "Is this a kind of virus that can spread?"

"It doesn't spread to everyone. A small portion of the refugees were awake when they were detained. They were able to clearly describe the entire situation, and their testimonies are shockingly identical. They all said that they felt a sudden outburst of anger and the urge to destroy some items to vent their anger. Our doctors have checked the bodies of these conscious individuals but did not find anything strange. The temperature of their bodies also went back to normal, and it was as though everything was normal. Thus, we have already quarantined these individuals, and they have not shown any signs of violence for the past eighteen hours."

"Is quarantining them really useful? The groups of people in the three waves of violence are completely different, and the violence took place without any signs at all. If this is truly a virus that cannot be detected, I'm afraid that the number of infected individuals will be..."

Thinking about that, Bennett could not help but take in a breath of cold air with his expression ugly. He had a feeling that this matter was not that simple.

"The war is over, and peace has finally been restored to the world with great difficulty. Why would something like this..."

All of a sudden, he thought of Han Xiao and the prophecy of a calamity that he did not believe. However, the scenario before him was actually extremely similar to Han Xiao's words!

Could it be that Black Phantom's words were true‽

Clank!

Bennett suddenly stood up, pushing his chair over. As he hurriedly put his coat on, he left the room.

"Prepare the plane, I am going to Black Phantom's Sanctuary Three!"

Chapter 507: The Arrangement Comes into Effect

The chopper slowly landed on the helipad of Sanctuary Three. Bennett finished adjusting his collar, holding onto his hat as he stepped onto land. He looked down and saw a peaceful and harmonious sight as far as the eye could see; there were no incidents of violence happening at the moment. On the helipad stood a group of people in black clothing. The current head of the Sanctuary Three, Huang Yu, was there with his subordinates.

"If you needed something, you could have called, sir. There's no need for you to have come personally, " Huang Yu respectfully said.

Bennett waved his hands, indicating for Huang Yu to lead the way as he replied, "I need to see a few people. The situation is urgent, could you gather them for me?"

"I'll convey your intentions. They will be waiting for you in the meeting room."

This delegation walked all the way to the core area of the Sanctuary. After navigating through the complicated passageways, they arrived at a meeting room. Bennett left his bodyguards outside, walking into the meeting room with Huang Yu. Sitting inside were three women—Hila, Aurora, and Emerald Grass. The three of them looked toward the newcomers as they walked in, their attention focused on Bennett.

"Sir." Hila remained impassive, slightly nodding her head. Because Aurora had not been turned into jam, Hila did not walk the extreme path. While she remained cold to everyone, toward someone like Bennett, she would still show the minimum respect.

"Cut the nonsense. I still have two more sets of experiments to perform today. Why have you gathered us?" Emerald Grass got straight to the point.

Bennett had a serious expression as he took out a few reports concerning the recent riots, sharing them with the trio as he spoke calmly. "Roughly a year ago, you guys first reported abnormal sightings. At that time, I did not notice it before, but right now, the matters seem to be connected to the strange sightings you have seen. Your group are the elites personally picked by Black Phantom himself, and with his ability for disaster prediction, I would like to hear your thoughts on this matter."

Because the trio were elites that Han Xiao had personally asked Bennett to take care of, he did not limit their freedom. Before Han Xiao left, Hila had always spoken of wanting to travel the world with Aurora after her body had fully recovered. However, Han Xiao had been gone for over two years, and Aurora's body had long recovered, yet Hila continued to stay within the Sanctuary.

Bennett naturally would not chase them away.

Aurora's Esper ability allowed her to sense lives, and the huge surge of life force that she had detected that vanished after a few days had allowed her to memorize the 'scent' of that lifeform. This was one of the functions of her ability, to record life signatures. The signatures were like a unique brand, allowing her to differentiate between each lifeform.

While the huge life signature was short lived, Aurora discovered that the scent of that particular lifeform was spreading, with increasing numbers of lifeforms having that particular scent on them. It did not differentiate between plants or animals.

Aurora spoke in a timid voice, slowly explaining what she had felt. Bennett's face grew graver as he listened.

If this is a sort of virus, then hundreds of millions of people could be infected in this world... that's not right. If we include the various flora and fauna, then the infected amount will truly be terrifying!

Aurora looked at everyone, hesitating for a moment before mustering her courage and pointing at Huang Yu. "He has that smell on him as well."

Huang Yu's face blanched. He immediately felt around himself, exclaiming, "I... I don't feel it!"

Bennett clapped a palm on Huang Yu's shoulder, his energy pervading Huang Yu's body through his fingers. However, even after going through a few rounds, he let go and sighed. "I could not sense anything out of the ordinary. What sort of virus is this? While I don't know the reason, it seems like only Aurora can tell apart who is infected or healthy."

Everyone turned to look at Aurora. She trembled, before blinking her large eyes as she nervously stuttered, "I... I can really be of help?"

Bennett had the urge to give out a benevolent and encouraging smile, but due to the pressing situation, he simply had no mood to do so. He could only solemnly nod.

Aurora seemed to be extremely happy to hear that. She had always been under the protection of others and had been looking forward to the day that she could return the favor.

After flipping through the report, not only did Emerald Grass not show any hints of shock, her face even revealed some form of fanaticism as she exclaimed, "I was right, my instincts were right! Indeed, my entire year of research has not been wasted!"

The moment she spoke, everyone immediately looked over, their expressions those of shock.

"What do you mean?" Bennett asked.

"Follow me." Emerald Grass immediately stood up, walking straight out. The rest could only follow her from behind.

After passing through the security perimeter, the group reached Emerald Grass' lab. Even the sentries did not dare linger around that place. They were afraid of inhaling any strange poisonous mist, leading to a coma or nervous disorder. If they were even unluckier, they might even experience a loss of ability in their procreation tool.

Emerald Grass brought the company to an open-air greenhouse, where many plants were being cultivated. Because the Esper ability of Emerald Grass was the control of plants, her medicinal raw materials were mostly planted by herself. Within this cultivation ground existed just one type of plant, which grew out fan-shaped green leaves from the ground. Its appearance could not have been more ordinary, and if it was placed in the wild, nobody would give it another look.

"This is the Rhodes Fan Leaf. It has a harsh growth environment and is extremely difficult to artificially cultivate. Because of that, it is an endangered species that has a small number of living specimens around the world. However, its extreme rarity does not indicate a high value. In fact, the Rhodes Fan Leaf has no medical function, and its only purpose is to be ground into a paste that can be eaten after cooking... provided you're a herbivore. In short, there is close to no value in cultivating this plant."

Emerald Grass simply introduced the plant, leaving everyone at a loss.

"But you still cultivated so many of them? Why did you bring us to see this?" Bennett asked.

At this time, Aurora stretched out her finger, curiously touching one of the fan blades. Suddenly, her eyes widened, and she exclaimed, "These plants are all uncontaminated by the smell!"

Bennett was startled. His face lit up with joy as he understood the meaning behind it.

"Your hypothesis is correct. A year ago, some of the plants gave me the impression that they were spying on me. This attracted my attention, and after searching through many areas, I found that this plant is the only botanical life that does not develop this spying sense. I don't understand the nuances behind the spying, but I realized that the Rhodes Fan Leaf can neutralize them, so I started to cultivate this plantation. However, the Rhodes Fan Leaves are too difficult to cultivate, and the seeds are scarce. These fans are all that are present at the moment." Emerald Grass confirmed everyone's suspicions.

"Have any clinical trials been held yet?"

"I've only experimented on botanicals for now. By extracting the juice of the Rhodes Fan Leaf and adding a few extra ingredients, I've produced a medicine that can inhibit the spying sense of plants for a period of time."

"Great, we have no time to waste. There's no knowing when the riots will take place. In a bit, I'll get someone to send over those rioters who have been isolated. You are to test if the inhibitor drug works on them."

Bennett was very decisive. During this time of chaos, he could not afford to care if there were repercussions from such a drug. He instead felt relieved that Emerald Grass could come out with such a countermeasure. At least they were much better than compared to the Six Nations, which were still at a loss.

"That's okay. However, there's something I need to warn you beforehand. Because of the rarity of the Rhodes Fan Leaf, the production of the drug is limited to small amounts. Furthermore, the collection of the plant's juices at any one time cannot be past a certain limit, or else the plant will die, reducing a potential source of supply. Every cultivated stalk comes from great difficulty."

Emerald Grass shrugged in response.

In the previous timeline, Emerald Grass had only managed to escape from the Bell of Death Island when the Mutation Disaster had completely blown apart. It was only after a long period of research that she finally came out with the prescription of the inhibitor. However, in this timeline, Han Xiao had freed her from the Bell of Death Island well in advance, allowing her to research. Han Xiao had changed the storyline once again, allowing her to invent the inhibitor when the Mutation Disaster had only just begun to rear its fangs. The impact was huge.

While the inhibitor drug could not eliminate the Mutation Disaster and could only provide temporary containment, this was one of the rare few methods to use against it. In the past timeline, the devastated Six Nations had fought red-eyed for possession of Emerald Grass, wishing to obtain the recipe for the drug.

However, Emerald Grass was now based in Sanctuary Three, under the protection of Bennett. Whether this would attract the covetous glances of the Six Nations was yet to be confirmed, but the initial reason behind Han Xiao, who was currently far away in space, gaining Emerald Grass was because of this scenario. He wanted Sanctuary Three to be the first to manufacture the inhibitor, which would attract a swarm of players to the Sanctuary. He had foreseen this from the very beginning.

Aurora had also been saved by him. Her Esper ability was able to distinguish those infected and was an important factor in changing the story. Because the mutation virus was extremely latent, everyone would begin to grow suspicious of each other after the disaster occurred. Everyone would be worried about their friends suddenly turning into enemies, but Aurora could at least prevent such a problem from plaguing Sanctuary Three. This would also attract more people toward Sanctuary Three to seek peace of mind...

Under the influences of Han Xiao, Bennett and the others could react to the issue well in advance. The Great Mechanic Han had long set the scene for Version 2.0, and the effects were gradually emerging.

After everyone had left the greenhouse, Hila suddenly asked, "If this was the disaster that he foresaw... do you think he will keep his promise and come back?"

Everyone paused mid-step. There was not a single person present who was not closely related to Han Xiao. Every time that they mentioned this Black Phantom, their facial expressions would turn complicated.

"Maybe..." Bennett could only sigh.

Black Phantom had mentioned that he would venture into outer space to find a solution to solve the disaster, but there had been no news from him for a good two years. They could not fathom just what Han Xiao had come across during his journey in space. To them, space exploration was something shrouded in mystery. It represented a higher, grander world, one that was the 'real' world. It stirred the curiosity within people, making them wish to take this step.

Every time they looked up into space, they would inevitably think of Han Xiao. However, they had no way to contact him.

At that point, even Bennett no longer held much hope.

Even for Hila, she felt that the chances were slim. She pulled out the key that Han Xiao had given her beforehand, weighing it in her hand. Her eyelids drooped, covering the glow in her eyes.

Maybe... he was never coming back.

Far away in space, Han Xiao did not purposefully monitor the situation of Planet Aquamarine. He had long known of the evolution stage for the Mutation Disaster, and he did not personally take another look to confirm. Time was money, and wasting time was equivalent to wasting money. This was something unacceptable to him!

In Version 2.0, the players would only return after the Mutation Disaster had completely blown up. Han Xiao calculated the time and estimated that around a month or two before the new version was launched, signs of the Mutation Disaster would start to show, and the virus would leave its incubation period to infect and evolve into a calamity.

This was the important stage for players to enter interstellar travel. There were only so many chances in life. If one grabbed hold of the opportunity, one would soar into the sky. Han Xiao followed the prescribed order to carry out his plans without any anxiety.

Following each objective on Han Xiao's prepared list being struck off one by one, the date also drew ever closer.

Chapter 508: New Version, New Phase

The stars were shining brightly, and the rivers of light lit up the pitch-black universe. Every twinkling star was immeasurably far away, and every star represented a race, a civilization, a dream. It was like a landing plane flying past a brightly lit city, forming both a majestic and lively sight.

Looking through the spaceship's window, the contours on Planet Golden Gate gradually became finer and clearer. Spaceships of all different shapes and sizes could be seen taking off and landing on this Godoran colony. It was as though the prosperity of the planet could be spread out in the sky, and those looking from afar could also feel this sense of prosperity.

This was a type of middle-sized, long-distance spaceship. It was a commonly seen model with its exterior made from a grayish allow. Its hyperdrive engine was also a common one, and it had an inferior grade electromagnetic shield. The official selling price of the spaceship was around 750,000 to 900,000 Enas, and a second-hand spaceship would be about thirty percent cheaper. If one had good ties with the factory that manufactured the spaceship, it could even be purchased for 170,000 Enas. On the spaceship, there was a bright yellow royal crown decal, and this was a spaceship for rent belonging to the Royal Crown Galactic Travel Agency.

This Travel Agency had just signed a long-term loan contract for thirteen spaceships with the Black Star Mercenary Group a month ago. The rental fee was far lower than the selling price of the spaceship, but it still was not cheap.

At that moment, this spaceship, which temporarily belonged to the Black Star Mercenary Group, had a few dozen mercenaries on it and was flying toward Planet Golden Gate. They were the mercenaries who had recently been hired by the Black Star Mercenary Group a few months prior.

During his one year of preparation, after Han Xiao completed the construction of his assembly lines, he had made use of his fame to hire a few hundred freelance mercenaries to build up the strength of his mercenary group and increase the NPC resources of his mercenary group. The new members were then restructured into different teams to make it easier to command them.

Herlous and the others alone would not be enough to deal with the Mutation Disaster. Presently, Han Xiao no longer needed to restrict the size of his mercenary group, so the more the merrier. The Great Mechanic Han would never be stingy in investing in his mercenary group. With a large stack of bills in his pocket, Han Xiao would not feel good if he did not spend any money.

"Black Star suddenly gathered all of us. Are we going on a large mission?"

"We are Floating Dragon's force in name. Could it be that the Dragon Emperor has an order for us?"

"I tried asking around, and nobody knows what Black Star wants. Even the officers aren't sure."

"All the others have arrived already, and we are the latest. I hope we didn't delay anything."

As the mercenaries were chatting, the spaceship landed at the port nearest to the base. Stepping out of the spaceship, dozens of mercenaries disembarked, and not too long later, they stopped in front of a gigantic base. The base was built on an octagonal plot of land and was surrounded by automatic cannon towers made from alloy walls.

The style of the base was like a gigantic metal castle with its shiny black exterior reflecting the sun's rays. Numerous metal buildings were joint together with ten or so cone shaped rooftops pointing toward the sky, looking like they were fries in a box. The buildings were all angular, and they had the precision of a machine. Apart from the grayish metal color, white and red paint could be seen extending out along the edges of the buildings to add some color to the otherwise heavy base. Together with the blue indication lights that were scattered all over the base, the entire base had a high-tech feeling to anyone who walked in.

This was the result of one year of hard work. Black Star's first base!

All the mercenaries came in front of the door, and a complicated identification panel popped out on the interface. After they were all verified that they belonged to the Black Star Mercenary Group, the door of the base began to slowly open, and a voice sounded from the interface.

"Identification complete, hum... Welcome back, hum..."

"Phillip, how's your day?" a mercenary joked with the interface.

"Currently working, hum... Cannot chat casually, hum..."

All of them then walked into the base. The interior of the base was not complicated. The center of the base was a large empty space with bridges leading toward the different regions of the base. It was like a beehive, and this middle region was called the 'mouthpiece' by the mercenaries.

The base was truly too large. Even a million people would not be able to fill it up completely, and the mercenary group only had a few hundred people at the moment. Thus, the interior of the base was extremely spacious.

These mercenaries walked toward the main hall while chatting, their voices echoing in the large hall.

When they entered the main hall of the base, they saw that a few hundred people were already waiting there. They were all waiting silently with the atmosphere solemn. These merrily chatting mercenaries immediately stopped their laughter and chatter and gathered behind the other mercenaries.

The few hundred people in the main hall were the present members of the mercenary group. They were clad in different kinds of armor and had either melee or ranged weapons on their backs. They were tall, short, fat, skinny, human, and beast; however, they all had something in common. They were all emanating the sharpness of an elite warrior, and every single one of them had survived hundreds of battles.

In front of the crowd, Black Star's officers were standing in a row with their backs facing the crowd. Herlous was clad in a light blue armor, Aroshia was glowing all over, the three Volga brothers looked as though they had been made from the same mold, and three other new officers who joined a few months ago. As for Feidin and Sylvia, they were standing further away.

At that moment, the metal ground that was in front of the crowd opened up, and a human figure rose up on an elevator. His black overcoat fluttered in the wind, and he had a necklace made from compressed orbs. Furthermore, he was still wearing a pure black mask that covered his face.

It was Han Xiao.

After a year, Han Xiao had changed his outfit into something more striking, and he had mimicked the Germinal Organization leader in wearing a mask. He felt that he was more handsome this way.

I am someone who owns his own property after all, and my coolness factor should go up a little at least. Furthermore, this black mask is actually equipment.

The moment that he appeared, everyone's gaze was immediately fixed on him.

"Is everyone here?"

Han Xiao's gaze swept over everyone present. He had hired these mercenaries personally, and Floating Dragon's reputation was truly useful. The majority of those present were lone wolves with pretty impressive combat prowess. They were all extremely reliable. All of the mercenaries before him could be split into three different categories. The first category would be mercenaries who did not belong to any mercenary group before this. The second category would be those who belonged to the Sunil Division. The third category would be a 'War League', which one of the new officers had brought with him.

After the base was constructed, Han Xiao did not stay in the base but took the time to visit other planets and hired three new officers based on his memories. These were characters who had been famous in his previous life.

Sehrinde, a Sunil Grade B Pugilist. He was dressed in a white hood. While the material of the hood seemed soft, it had a defensive inscription inscribed in it. His face was hidden under the shadow of the hood, and two large blades could be seen hanging on his waist. He would be able to unsheathe those blades at any time, and when Han Xiao first met him, Han Xiao had almost thought that he had come out from a certain popular assassination game.

He was another Grade B Super who belonged to the Guardian Faction of the Sunil civilization. When Fernas left Sunil, Sehrinde did not leave together. Sehrinde had a quiet personality, and his personality was just like his swift and queer Pugilist subclass. He was like an assassin hidden in the darkness and a sharp contrast to Herlous' open Pugilist style.

With Herlous making the introduction, Han Xiao had managed to find the lonesome Sehrinde and issued an invitation to him. As the reputation of the Black Star Mercenary Group grew, more and more Sunil Supers became willing to join Black Star. It was safe, and they could earn a lot of money. It could also be said that Han Xiao was offering them protection. Under Herlous' persuasion, Sehrinde had accepted Han Xiao's invitation and begun working together with him.

Presently, the Sunil Division was led by Herlous and Sehrinde.

The second new officer was Ginette Colin, a female space human. She was a Grade B Cannon Master and carried various kinds of heavy firearms all over her body. The thick layer of machinery covered her tall, sexy figure. It was her creed to worship firepower over anything else.

Ginette was a pretty famous lone wolf mercenary. In Han Xiao's previous life, she had joined Sky Ring Army and become a famous leading figure of the army. Han Xiao had spotted her name when he was going through the list of freelance mercenaries and thus decided to pull Ginette into his mercenary group while she was still alone.

The process naturally had not been an easy one. Ginette had an explosive temper and cursed at both the heavens and the earth. She did not even place Floating Dragon in her sights. Han Xiao had thus come up with a small plan and purposely intervened in one of Ginette's missions. With the both of them on opposing sides, they had naturally ended up fighting. After Han Xiao beat her terribly a couple of times, Ginette had finally submitted and joined the Black Star Mercenary Group.

Han Xiao had promised to provide her with heavy firearms at a low price. With Ginette's hobby of collecting all different kinds of weapons, she had immediately accepted his proposal.

The third officer had an even greater origin. He was a main character class figure. Han Xiao had spent a great deal of effort before finally being able to con him into joining. Just like how he had conned Herlous back then.

Harmon Rockfall Sonodin. He was a Luhan Beastman and was more than three meters tall. His entire body was covered in hair, and he looked a little like a bear. His appearance was still pretty adorable, but he actually belonged to a clan of ferocious fighters. The Luhan Beastmen had their own civilization, and it was located in a different Star Cluster. Their governance method was an alliance system between all the different tribes. Harmon was one of the candidates for the next tribal chief of the Rockfall Tribe.

While the Luhan Beastman was a galactic civilization, they preserved their battle loving, boorish, and warlike tradition. When the tribe wanted to decide the next chief, they would not vote for the new chief peacefully but settle it with a battle. All the candidates would be chased out from their mother planet and sent to random planets. They would have to train themselves up in the galaxy and also build up their own 'War League'. When the designated time arrived, they would then take all of their troops back to their mother planet to participate in the battle to determine the chief. In other words, it was similar to the fight between princes for authority.

Harmon was a main character, and his storyline was to aid him in snatching the position of tribal chief. When he was conning Harmon, Han Xiao had activated this mission. This mission was simple and violent. He had to fight from the start to the end. After the players completed this mission in his previous life, the process had become a dungeon, and they would be able to gain a Dungeon Crystal from doing daily missions at the Rockfall Tribe. Thus, Han Xiao could remember the mission clearly.

The way to hire Harmon was naturally to agree to an ancient ceremony and become part of his War League. Harmon was not alone, and he brought the subordinates in his War League, dozens of powerful Luhan Beastman, to join the mercenary group.

Harmon had the strength of a Grade B Super, and his Esper ability was very simply to strengthen his body and cause the muscles on his entire body to expand.

While his Esper ability was extremely singular, Harmon was proficient in many different weapons and was a warrior with exquisite battle techniques. Han Xiao had taken a look at Harmon's attributes before, and Harmon had six rare subclass that belonged to the [Warrior] class.

The addition of the three new officers provided the mercenary group with fresh blood. Han Xiao had more and more capable subordinates under him, and the rewards that his faction could give out had also increased greatly.

Currently, the highest mission reward that Han Xiao could give out was 1,000,000 experience, and his Daily Reward Limit was over twenty times that. This meant that if he issued a faction mission, he could give out more than 20,000,000 experience to the players. Hiring NPC characters was all to better attract players.

Opening up his communicator, Han Xiao looked at his mercenary group's introduction.

Black Star Mercenary Group

Credibility Rating: 1,018 (High)

Scale: 417 members

Grade D: 47

Grade C: 359 members

Grade B: 11

Missions Completed: 82

Main Activity Area: Colton Star Cluster

History:

[Sunil Defense Battle]

[Silver Rescue Operation]

[Capture of Purple Gem Civilization's Head Of Rebels "Pilipelapa Wasasa"]

[Battle of Noriosse]

[78 more missions... (Expand/Collapse)]

Creator: Black Star—Han Xiao

Creation date: Galaxy Calendar Year 688, 02 October

Summary: A medium sized mercenary group with a good name and very high credibility. Completed hiring missions with high ratings multiple times. Work together with many large-scale mercenary groups. Field Team under the Dragon Emperor. Base is located on Planet Golden Gate. Mercenary captain Black Star aided Godora in killing a Calamity Grade Super in Noriosse. Reliable.

Today is the day of Version 2.0's release. I have waited almost a year for this day. My manpower should be sufficient.

Han Xiao nodded in his head.

Over the past year, Han Xiao had done many things and made ample preparations. He had constructed a total of twenty-three assembly lines, and his 4,500,000 Enas had almost all been spent, with only about 1,100,000 Enas remaining. The majority of his money had been spent on materials, and his assembly line had been churning out equipment without stopping. His warehouse already had a mountain of equipment at the moment.

The loan had already exceeded the first interest free year. According to Rockfess' requirement, he would have to start paying interest if his loan period was more than a year. Han Xiao was waiting to earn a huge sum of money from the players.

His experience on the interface had already fallen below 100,000,000 points, and Han Xiao was still level 116. He had spent all of his experience on gambling for blueprints and raising the level of his skills. He was currently in dire need of experience points. He still had a Mission Completion Card in his hands, and if he had sufficient experience points, he could even advance directly and charge to level 140. It would be a lie to say that he did not look forward to that.

Keeping his thoughts to himself, Han Xiao looked at the mercenaries present and said, "I have gathered everyone today for a large-scale mission. My home planet is undergoing a calamity, and their sights are only limited to that of their planet. They aren't able to see what we can see, and we are their only hope."

The mercenaries all began looking at each other.

Black Star's home planet?

That backward planet called Planet Aquamarine?

"I will fight for you just like you will fight for me." Harmon hammered his chest with his fist.

"I will be by your side just like before," Herlous proclaimed.

All the mercenaries in the hall also began to express their support.

Looking at the time, it was about right.

Han Xiao opened the interface and waited quietly.

After a short wait, a new notification appeared.

Version 2.0 is now open.

Fetching data... Fetching data done!

Player Forum Open

Welcome to 'Galaxy' Version 2.0!

After preparing for such a long time, Version 2.0 is finally here!

Han Xiao's eyes glowed as he walked toward the door.

A few hundred elites followed behind him majestically.

"Let's go!"

Chapter 509: The Players Return, Eruption of the Mutation Disaster

On Planet Aquamarine, the Southern Continent was experiencing intense summer heat. The scorching sun was high in the sky, and heatwaves could be seen rising from the ground.

The instant that Version 2.0 was released, the originally empty plaza of Sanctuary Three had suddenly been overwhelmed with people. In just a few seconds, that originally spacious plaza had become packed with people.

Before the new system patch, because of the [The Last Bastion] mission that Han Xiao had left behind and Galaxy Times' analysis of Version 2.0, millions of players had gathered in Sanctuary Three and chosen to go offline there. The moment that Version 2.0 launched, the log-in point for those millions of players was naturally Sanctuary Three.

Millions of heads were bobbing up and down, looking around curiously.

"Is it Version 2.0 already?"

"There don't seem to be many changes."

"Eh, the upper level limit has increased, and our experience can be used to increase our levels. It seems like this is the new version indeed."

"Aren't there any other changes? I truly want to try taking a dump in the game."

"Pants Taking Off Club, please have some self-respect."

All the players began chatting among themselves and opened up the interface to check their stats. Apart from the raised level cap, there did not seem to be any other changes to their stats.

But very quickly, some players realized that the status of a certain mission had changed. The mission status of [The Last Bastion] had changed from 'frozen' to 'active'.

This was the Prize-Pool Mission that Han Xiao had left behind before his departure. The mission requirement was to protect Sanctuary Three as preparation for the Mutation Disaster.

And now, this mission had actually been activated!

Does this mean that the 'calamity' in the mission hint has already begun?

All the players immediately became excited. Owing to Black Phantom's 'blessings', they did not manage to participate much in the previous Main Storyline. This time, there was finally something big for them to do!

Right, the NPC who issued this mission was Black Phantom... oh, he's now called Black Star. Is he still in the universe?

The moment they thought about Han Xiao, many of the players could not help but feel envious of the professional players who had been taken away by him. They had managed to enter the universe a step earlier and were miles away in terms of equipment and experience.

When the players were still observing their surroundings, a broadcast was suddenly made from the Sanctuary.

"Will all Inhumans stay where you are! I repeat, all Inhumans stay where you are!"

Very quickly, a large number of guards surrounded the plaza with their expressions filled with doubt as they looked at the large number of players nervously.

The Inhumans had disappeared from the entire planet for almost a year, and their sudden appearance had truly frightened the managers of Sanctuary Three. Bennett had hurriedly sent people over to control the situation.

At the same time, the players of Sanctuary Three received a mission.

Remain on the Spot

Mission Introduction: During your time away, many things have happened on Planet Aquamarine, and they are currently facing a threat that could wipe out their civilization. Remain where you are and wait patiently for the relevant person to explain the situation.

This was only a small mission, and the reward was not large. The players also wanted to know what was going on, and thus, they all stayed in the plaza. At the same time, it was also because they were surrounded by guards. Who knew whether they would end up being attacked if they chose to leave? None of them wanted to lose Favorability with the Sanctuary at the very start of Version 2.0.

Not too long later, Bennett rushed over. Looking at the huge wave of players, a trace of joy could be seen in his eyes.

He remembered what Han Xiao had said to him before leaving for the universe. Han Xiao had told him that the Inhumans would be a core strength to fight the calamity. With the Inhumans appearing again, while he did not know the reason for their appearance, their appearance was extremely timely. They truly needed manpower at the moment.

Bennett took out a loudspeaker and said, "Planet Aquamarine is currently facing a never before seen calamity, and we urgently need your help..."

He quickly described the situation, and the players found out that it had been over a year since the previous version. Just a month ago, a strange phenomenon had spread across Planet Aquamarine and become a calamity that covered the entire planet.

Planet Aquamarine called it the 'Mutation Disaster'.

It had already been a month since the outbreak of the Mutation Disaster, and the entire planet had been thrown into chaos. The regime of the Six Nations had almost collapsed in a short month.

No one knew the reason for the calamity, but they were certain that it was because of some type of virus which they called the 'mutation virus'. Many different living beings—be it humans, beasts, and even plants—had been infected by the virus. However, the appearance of the virus could not even be detected, and no one even knew how to virus was spread and who was infected with it.

Before the outbreak of the virus, all the infected individuals would be no different from usual, but the moment that the virus broke out, the infected individual would display unusual desires that included but were not limited to killing intent, destructive tendencies, anger, grief, craziness, lust, hunger, thirst, and so on. A usually weak individual could be transformed into a murderer who killed without blinking. An ordinary person might suddenly squat down and crazily eat up the sand beneath their feet before dying. A conservative and virtuous lady could suddenly turn into a lascivious lady.

The most frightening thing was the fact that the infected individual would still maintain their rationality during the outbreak of the virus. This meant that the infected individual was not losing control or acting rashly but being led by their desires to perform such actions.

According to the recollection of those infected individuals, when the virus broke out, all of their desires would come from deep within their hearts and were their true thoughts at that moment. It was as though their personalities had been altered, but they were not able to detect it. During the outbreak of the virus, all the infected individuals felt as though their actions were very normal.

Bennett gave a few examples, and the confused players immediately knew how frightening the Mutation Disaster was.

Maple was where the first large scale outbreak of the virus took place. The infected individuals in the army began to pick up their rifles and shoot their own comrades crazily. The entire army immediately fell into complete chaos. No one knew whether the one opening fire was an infected individual or a defending soldier, and an internal war broke out with tanks, helicopters, and even missiles being used. This battle had caused half of Maple's army to be lost.

The president himself had even displayed severe violent tendencies and wanted to nuke the entire world. Thankfully, the process of launching nuclear weapons was extremely complicated. If the button to activate a nuclear missile was in the president's office, the entire planet would probably have been flattened by now. As for the president, he had immediately been caught after that incident.

Many ridiculous events that would never happen under ordinary circumstances had begun to take place all over the world. It would not have been scary if a single person went crazy. However, if the entire world went crazy, it was akin to a bunch of devils dancing.

No one knew when the person beside them would break out with the virus, and they could not even be sure that they themselves were normal. This fear was extremely frightening, and it was as though the entire world had become their enemy, and they would not dare to believe anyone else in the world.

A month after the Mutation Disaster broke out, the order of society had broken down, and many prosperous cities had become ghost towns. For their own safety, many city dwellers had no choice but to find some place to hide themselves. Depression had become an ordinary emotion, and the view that radiation caused this strange virus had become popular.

As such, countless of citizens began to curse the Germinal Organization war, which had brought them peace. They felt that this was their retribution, and the end of the world had arrived!

After listening to the introduction, many players felt their hearts turn cold. Putting themselves in the shoes of the NPCs, this virus was truly too terrifying. The players had plenty of guesses with regards to the so-called 'calamity' of Version 2.0, but never had they expected that it would be so strange.

Just what was the mutation virus?

All of a sudden, the players fell into a daze. The time in the outside world and game flowed at different rates. In the eyes of the players, only a few short days had passed, but the entire world that they were familiar with was completely different.

Is there a need for the plot to be so exciting‽

"Is this virus incurable?" a player asked.

Bennett shook his head. "Presently, we have found two ways to fight this virus. First, it isn't easy for Supers to be infected, and this is a verified fact. Second, our Sanctuary Three has developed a type of suppressant, and it can prevent the virus from breaking out. However, production is limited. We are trying to grow all the required materials, but the quantity is still far from being sufficient."

As those words were completed, a mission appeared on the interfaces of the players.

Mutation Disaster

Mission Introduction: Planet Aquamarine is suffering from an unprecedented calamity, and it is the responsibility of every being living on this planet to fight the Mutation Disaster!

Mission Requirements: Contribute to the fight against the Mutation Disaster.

Progress: 0/30,000,000

Success Requirements: Complete the mission before the mutation virus becomes complete.

Failure Condition: Collapse of Planet Aquamarine's civilization. All of the survivors being forced to retreat.

Reward: Depends on contribution. (Even if the growth of the virus results in total progress being lowered, the individual accumulated contribution will be counted toward the reward rating.)

The mission requirements for the players were extremely similar to Han Xiao's mission requirements. It was just that Han Xiao's mission included all the planets suffering from the Mutation Disaster. It was obvious that the Great Mechanic Han's mission was more complete.

This was a large Main Storyline that involved all the players. The contribution of every player would be counted toward the mission progress, and the players needed to work together toward this goal.

"We accepted a Main Storyline mission right after coming online? The plot of this version is truly fast!"

"Without any build up and going straight to the point, I like how direct they are!"

"That's not right. The reason that we were able to obtain the Main Storyline mission immediately is probably because we came online in Sanctuary Three. It seems like Galaxy Times' analysis isn't wrong. We were indeed able to come into contact with the Main Storyline more easily through Sanctuary Three."

As everyone thought about this, they were immediately enlightened.

If they were in other locations, there would not have been anyone present to explain the entire disaster to them in detail. Furthermore, Bennett had previously mentioned that Sanctuary Three was the only place that had the suppressant. This meant that Sanctuary Three was the place where the Main Storyline would unfold. It was the mission that Black Phantom had left behind that had guided them there.

He was truly their lighthouse!

With this Main Storyline mission, the players were immediately energized, and they all went forward to ask if they could be of any help. The entire plaza descended into chaos, and Bennett only managed to restore order after a great deal of effort. He then got his subordinates to issue various missions. While the missions were all different, these missions would contribute toward the Main Storyline.

Every type of mission only needed a limited number of players, and a frenzied mess of snatching for mission began.

The large guilds snatched the most missions, and there were some solo players who were not able to snatch a single mission issued by the Sanctuary.

A player could not help but ask, "Can we leave the Sanctuary now? I want to go somewhere else."

"You'd better take a look on the city walls yourself," Bennett said with a helpless look.

The tall iron walls of the Sanctuary blocked the view of the outside. Hearing those words, many players became curious and climbed up the city walls to take a look.

With just a single glance, the players were dumbfounded.

In the surrounding ten kilometers, countless tents had been set up, and the tents were like a gray cloud covering the red earth. It was like a gigantic refugee camp, and all of them stayed outside the Sanctuary, refusing to leave. From time to time, the sound of fighting would be heard. Who knew if the fighting was because of the virus or for the scarce food and water?

"The news of us developing a suppressant has been spread, and countless people come here every day, requesting the suppressant and our protection."

Bennett also climbed up the city walls. Upon looking at the endless sea of refugee tents, he let out a sorrowful sigh.

"However, our suppressant is limited in quantity, and we can only give a small number of refugees the suppressant. As for the others, we can only let them wait outside. With more and more people coming, the number of virus outbreak incidents is also on the rise, and plenty of people die on the outside every day. However, to prevent the Sanctuary descending into chaos, I cannot allow all of them to come in. I can only watch as they die..."

The entire world was helpless against the Mutation Disaster, and only Sanctuary Three had a suppressant. The result was extremely clear. This place had become the holy land for the refugees and their final hope.

In Han Xiao's previous life, everyone had been like headless flies when the calamity broke out. They had all been lost in shock and did not have a target of hope. The situation had been completely chaotic. Now, because of Han Xiao's influence, the refugees of the entire planet had a target. It was Black Phantom's Sanctuary Three, and it was treated as their only hope.

However, the suppressant that Emerald Grass and Aurora had created would only be effective in the short term, and it was not able to purge the virus. Bennett did not know what he should do to solve this calamity. In fact, there was not a single person on Planet Aquamarine who knew what to do. He could not help but think about the reason that Han Xiao had given him before leaving for the universe. Black Phantom had said that he wanted to find a way to solve the calamity. Did this mean that the solution to the calamity could not be found on Planet Aquamarine?

Bennett could only place his hope on Han Xiao.

If he can really come back...

"There isn't another Sanctuary on the entire planet," Bennett said with a heavy tone. "This place is the only Sanctuary."

Chapter 510: Black Star's Return!

At the same time, in the Black Star Mercenary Group's previous temporary base in Juberly Hub, dozens of white lights flashed. The professional players who followed Han Xiao had also appeared. They were Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, Bun-Hit-Dog, and the others. During the update to the new version, they had all gone offline there.

The habit of any professional player was to open up the interface at the very first chance to see any changes to the interface. As professional players, they were most concerned about their stats and equipment.

After confirming the increase in the level limit, all of them looked around and were immediately stunned.

However, the entire base was empty and only a lonely light was lit. The metal walls glowed with a dim white color, reflecting the light. While the entire base was spotless because of the cleaning facilities, the door that was opened and the silent atmosphere made the players feel as though there had not been anyone staying there for a long time.

The items in the room had disappeared, including Black Star's personal warehouse and his machinery modification room. If not for the fact that even the furniture was gone, they would have thought that a thief had broken into the house.

"Why isn't there a single person here? Where is my Black Star?" Frenzied Sword asked.

"Who knows how long has passed? It seems like they are no longer here," Hao Tian said in a solemn tone.

"It is also possible that they are all dead," Li Ge said and immediately drew the angry glares of those around him. His consideration had historical reasons behind it. He still remembered that a subordinate guild of their Temple of God had once met the tragedy of their mission issuing location being destroyed.

"Idiots, can't you guys just check on the Faction details?" Maple Moon rolled her eyes at the rest of them. As part of the mercenary group, they were able to check the basic information of the faction and find out the situation of the Black Star Mercenary Group. There was no need for them to guess blindly at all.

However, what the players did not know was that they were only able to see the Faction information because Han Xiao had intentionally added that information into the faction interface. It was so that these players would be able to witness the growth of the mercenary group and build their sense of belonging. From beginning to end, the Great Mechanic Han had only given benefits to the players so that he would be able to snatch more money.

After opening up the faction interface, the players were immediately shocked by the information displayed before them.

"The number of people in the faction had increased, and there are actually over four hundred people. The number of missions completed has also increased. Quickly, take a look at the summary. It is written that the location of the Black Star Mercenary Group's base is on Planet Golden Gate. So, it turns out that the mercenary group has shifted house... but where is Planet Golden Gate?" Frenzied Sword asked.

"That's not all! Look at this! Black Star actually killed a Calamity Grade Super on Noriosse! My goodness, he's too powerful..." Bun-Hit-Dog gasped. He then asked, "Wait... what grade is a Calamity Grade Super?"

At that moment, the players still did not know that Grade A Supers were also called Calamity Grade. They only felt that the name was extremely cool.

In any case, anything above Grade C was something that the players could only look up to.

All of the professional players then fell into a daze. Just what had the Black Star Mercenary Group gone through when they were not around?

Right at that moment, the doorbell to the stronghold suddenly rang and the players jumped up in shock. They then opened up the door, and a three horned snakeman was standing outside the door.

"Are you guys members of the Black Star Mercenary Group?" the snakeman asked.

The professional players looked at each other before nodding.

"I am a captain of the Royal Crown Travel Agency. His Excellency Black Star asked me to send all of you to Planet Aquamarine. Please follow me."

Hearing that, a look of disbelief could be seen on their faces. They could never have imagined that Black Star would send a spaceship to pick them up.

The Mutation Disaster had changed the structure of the entire planet. The rule of the Six Nations was almost collapsing, and the territories of the Six Nations had fallen into chaos with the government losing control.

Because everyone had a chance of contracting the virus, even the government officials were not spared. Officials of all levels contracted the virus, and if the government lost its competent staff, it was as good as losing its strength. Thus, the Six Nations were gradually sliding toward destruction.

The various sectors and layers of society were created by men, and the order of society was what made people submit to it. The justice department, army, economic body, cultural tradition, morals, mainstream ideas, and so on were all there to let people understand the price of going against the rules and thus restricting their own actions. However, the mutation virus destroyed a person's ordinary sense of logic and fear. They would not consider any consequences when the virus broke out, and all of those social structures completely lost their purpose. The social system that seemed to be unbreakable had turned into a fragile vase in a single night.

Primal chaos.

This was the most accurate description of the current state of society.

No living being could be trusted, and only the cold machine was reliable.

After the outbreak of the calamity, the Six Nations had abandoned all of their former enmity. In the face of such a calamity, their individual benefits were no longer important. They had no choice but to join hands, and the upper echelons of the Six Nations were having a video conference at that moment.

"Twenty days ago, we issued a request for help to the Godoran Civilization. Godora said that they would rush here as soon as they can, but they have not appeared after such a long time."

The Mutation Disaster was like a virgin who was wearing a chastity belt. Regardless of how they tried, they just could not get her to open up her doors. The Six Nations knew that it would be impossible for them to deal with the Mutation Disaster with their present technology, and all of their means were ineffective. Thus, they had sent a report of the calamity to Godora and hoped for a higher-class civilization to save them.

However, not a single spaceship had landed thus far, and the upper echelons of the Six Nations were growing anxious. They tried to pester Godora time and time again but would only receive a response from an Artificial Intelligence answering machine.

In truth, the Six Nations did not know that the Mutation Disaster had not only broken out on Planet Aquamarine but all over the Garton Star System. Godora was currently extremely busy as well. Han Xiao had not revealed that this was DarkStar's plot, and thus, Godora was still in the dark and did not treat the Mutation Disaster with great importance.

"Godora's arrival isn't something that we can control. Currently, we have a new situation. The Inhumans who disappeared over a year ago have appeared again."

"This is truly too coincidental. Perhaps they are the ones who brought the mutation virus!" someone said angrily.

The Six Nations had always been suspicious of the Inhumans. Since they were not of the same species, the prejudice and discrimination toward the Inhumans had never disappeared.

"No matter what, the Inhumans are mostly Supers, and they may be able to provide us with some aid. Regardless of who comes to our aid, I only wish to wake up from this nightmare soon. In this situation, I don't even dare meet my wife, afraid that I may lose control and end up harming her," one of the officials said in a depressed tone.

"While Bennett has shared with the world the recipe of the suppressant, only Sanctuary Three is able to produce it stably. He said that he isn't able to give us any extra suppressants, but I do not believe him. They are definitely hiding more suppressants in their warehouses."

As those words were said, all the leaders of the Six Nations fell silent. All of them knew that everyone present had their eyes on the suppressant.

When a calamity occurred and there was only one item capable of fighting the calamity, the meaning of that item far exceeded its own use. In order to obtain the suppressant, everyone had no choice but to be obedient. Even if Bennett did not have other plans, Sanctuary Three had already become the center of the entire world with an endless stream of people rushing toward it.

The Six Nations wanted to control the suppressant and use it to stabilize their citizens and restore order to their regime. However, if they chose to snatch it, the situation that the people of the world had finally adapted to would be broken yet again, and they would face a huge risk. If they were not careful, they might end up causing an outcome that could not be reversed. Was stabilizing their regime more important than the life and death of the entire civilization?

Some of them were not able to persuade themselves while others could. Regardless of which faction they belonged to, they were still in a dilemma.

"If we really want to do it, we have to be fast," Raylen's leader said. "Time waits for no one."

Two days passed by quickly.

The players stayed behind in Sanctuary Three to get used to the new version and participate in the Main Storyline mission.

While the players were many, there was an almost endless supply of missions in the Sanctuary. The missions with the highest reward were naturally the official missions issued by Bennett. There was a limited number of such missions every day, and the other missions could be activated by talking to different NPCs. The endless refugees outside of the Sanctuary had plenty of requests, and they would never be able to finish all the tasks. These tasks that normal people would find extremely troublesome were extremely enjoyable to the players. They performed the tasks with a serious attitude and were extremely passionate about their jobs. Every single player was like a model citizen, and the guards of the Sanctuary seemed to be lacking in contrast.

The vast majority of the mission rewards would award them with [Mutation Disaster] progress. After two days of hard work, the total progress was at 730,000 points. It should have been higher than that, but the destruction caused by the Mutation Disaster every day would lower the total progress. The players needed to continue accumulating progress points. If not, the mission total progress points would keep falling.

While they were not clear about the reason behind the mutation virus, the players did not care. As long as they had the guidance of the mission, they would just follow the guidance and complete the mission.

Because Version 2.0 would give the players a chance to enter the universe, the players knew that this Main Storyline mission was only a single starting plot of the new Version and not the entire storyline. The players on other planets also had similar encounters, facing danger the moment that the version started. It was just that the danger that they faced was all different. Planet Winterfrost faced the funniest storyline. As a planet that the Extinguish Army stationed their troops on, someone had actually launched a punitive expedition against them. How infuriating.

In comparison, the speed at which players on Planet Aquamarine entered the Main Storyline was the fastest. Apart from that, the situation of the plot was largely similar to Han Xiao's previous life.

The forums were as lively as before the update, in fact, even livelier than before. With the new version being released, many players were sharing information, and new posts appeared at almost every second.

Bennett stood atop the city walls and looked down at the clamoring Sanctuary. The figure of the Inhumans could be seen all around, and they took care of his present manpower shortage. Upon witnessing this scene, his furrowed brows loosened up slightly.

"Thankfully, we have the help of these Inhumans. I never imagined that Black Phantom's influence would still protect us." Bennett let out a sigh and muttered with a complicated tone.

Hila was standing behind him and leaning against the wall. Her face was expressionless as she looked at the endless refugee tents.

"Ahhh!"

All of a sudden, a strange cry could be heard from the refugees, and countless individuals had an outburst of the virus. This was the most frightening part of the virus; it could break out at any time.

The refugee camp that was barely able to maintain its order immediately became chaotic. A few million infected individuals became red eyed, and a large battle broke out. The scene was extremely stunning, and the loud commotion was like a deafening tsunami of sound.

A small portion of refugees who did not break out in the virus sat down on the ground while trembling. The guards on the Sanctuary walls were also completely dumbfounded.

Bennett's expression changed, and his arms grabbed onto the edge of the wall. He used so much force that his fingerprints could be seen on the wall.

"With so many people gathering here, the moment there is a collective outburst of the virus, the consequences are dire. When the symptoms of the virus recede, the number of casualties are probably in the millions!"

All of the players stopped their mission at hand. This was the first time that they witnessed a collective outburst of the virus, and they were extremely shocked. There were some who turned on the recording feature.

They had witnessed war before, but the sight of a large gang fight between a few million people was a first. The refugees did not use any weapons and had only used their fists or teeth to fight. They were like extremely bloodthirsty beasts.

"We must stop them. If not, many people will die. Send out all our forces and knock out all the infected individuals!"

Bennett immediately issued an order. Every infected individual deserved the opportunity to be saved. With so many people killing each other before his eyes, Bennett could not watch without doing anything.

Rumble!

Right at that moment, a loud rumbling sound could be heard from afar, getting louder and louder. Looking toward the horizon, countless beasts were sprinting over in a majestic fashion.

The beasts on Planet Aquamarine had also been infected with the mutation virus. Originally, the environment of the wilderness had been extremely dangerous, and it had become even more difficult to survive now. Furthermore, the outbreak of virus between beasts and humans was different. While the infected beasts would become violent, they would form a large herd and move around together. At times, they would fight each other, and other times, they would attack the cities.

The beast tide charged straight into the refugee camp and began a massacre. The refugees were bitten and trampled on by the beasts, and a bloody scene unfolded. It was as though a heavy cavalry legion had charged into a bunch of defenseless commoners.

Pa!

Bennett crushed the corner of the city walls and shouted with anger, "Not good! A beast tide actually came at this moment. Quickly, save them! If we do nothing, all of the refugees will die!"

At that moment, a huge change occurred on all the player's interfaces. The total progress of [Mutation Disaster] fell by 10,000 points in the blink of an eye, and all of them triggered an urgent mission. The mission requirements were to save as many refugees outside the city as possible, with the reward ranging from 50,000 to 200,000. The fewer deaths, the higher the reward.

Furthermore, the total progress of their mission was falling rapidly, and if they did not save the refugees quickly, more than half of their hard work over the past two days would go to waste.

"Quickly, go out of the city and save them!"

"Requesting for a party. Anyone will do. I just need to fill up the party!"

The players in the city immediately became frantic and charged out of the city to save the refugees. After knocking out the infected individuals, they sent them into the Sanctuary.

Apart from saving the refugees, Bennett sent out a portion of players to delay the beast tide. The number of beasts was truly too great, and there were 300,000 beasts at the very least. They would not be able to kill the beasts any time soon and could only stall for time so that they could save as many refugees as possible.

Hila had already charged into the beast tide, and her dark red energy was released without any restraint. One after another, the beasts fell. The players in the surroundings also engaged in an intense battle with the beasts, and they were drenched in the beasts' blood.

Killing was what she specialized in, and battle was already ingrained in her bones. It was an ordinary action to her, just like eating or sleeping. However, Hila truly had a complicated emotion during that battle. She used to be an executioner who killed the innocent ,and this was the first time that she had been fighting in order to save the lives of others who had nothing to do with her.

Rumble!

The entire situation was extremely messy. The refugee camp was sandwiched between the beasts charging in on one side and the players trying to save as many people as possible. Both sides were charging toward the center, and the infected refugees did not know how to escape, still engaged in battle!

Even with Bennett's strength, he also felt that the situation before him was extremely messy. His palms were covered in sweat as he looked at the situation nervously.

"There are far too many beasts, and their attack rate is at least four per second. We cannot tank the damage at all!"

"Dammit! My morale is crushed! My ass has been smashed!"

"Gaps are everywhere, and we cannot block them at all!"

The players who were blocking the beast tide felt completely helpless, and players were dying every second. While they could revive, they needed time to run out from the Sanctuary, and it would delay time. What they needed most was time, and their mission progress was falling every second, causing all the players to get extremely anxious.

Xiu!

Just as the situation was becoming dismal, a deafening roar came from the sky. Despite the chaotic and noisy environment that they were in, everyone could clearly hear the deafening roar, and they all turned to look up at the sky.

A few hundred egg shaped metal pods then descended down from the sky and began burning up like fireballs. It was like a few hundred descending meteors, and their landing location was right at the doorstep of the Sanctuary.

Boom boom boom!

The metal pods landed on the ground and filled the ground with cracks. The next moment, the doors to the metal pods opened, and a person walked out from every single metal pod.

They were dressed in armor and held weapons in their hands. Their styles were extremely varied, and they were obviously guests from outer space who did not belong to Planet Aquamarine. Everyone looked over with curious gazes and immediately knew that these metal eggs were airdrop pods from space.

These uninvited guests were warriors from the galaxy!

Just as everyone wanted to ask about their intentions, a man dressed in black who was wearing a mask waved his arm, and the hundred or so galactic warriors charged toward the beast tide.

Boom!

The galactic warriors displayed their powerful combat capabilities and immediately took over the battle. The previously seemingly unstoppable beast tide seemed to have run into a metal wall!

A few hundred people displayed strength greater than the surrounding thousands of players.

A look of shock flashed through Hila's eyes. She was on the battlefield and could clearly feel their strength. Almost all of the galactic warriors gave her a sense of pressure that was even more powerful than what Bennett gave her. Furthermore, Bennett was the most powerful being on Planet Aquamarine at the moment.

This meant that any single one of those galactic warriors was more powerful than Bennett!

With an unknown force interfering, danger was averted. Only the black masked man remained by the gates of the Sanctuary without making a move. Bennett jumped off from the city walls and walked forward toward the masked man. "Who are you? Where do you come from? Why are you helping us?"

Bennett had seen the captured Godoran Observer before and thus did not lose his cool when seeing aliens.

But the very next moment, his expression, which he tried to keep cool, turned into shock.

Han Xiao raised his arm and took off his mask to reveal his appearance. A smile could be seen on his lips, and he felt as though he was extremely suave.

"It's been a long time Bennett. Why are you so surprised? What, you didn't think that I'd return?"

Bennett's body immediately froze up, and he did not dare believe what he had just seen. His lips trembled, and his look of shock turned into one of crazed joy.

Hila, who was far away, was also shocked.

The instant that Han Xiao took off his mask, almost every player fell into shock. Following which, they burst into joy at reuniting after a long parting, and their morale increased greatly. This familiar figure was like a stimulant that injected all the players with a wave of hot blood. All of them were agitated to the point their scalps turned numb!

"It's him! Black Star has returned!"

Chapter 511: Acting Cool

From Planet Golden Gate to Planet Aquamarine, the entire journey had taken Han Xiao two days. Even when he passed by Juberly Hub, Han Xiao did not personally fetch Frenzied Sword and the others. Instead, he had sent a spaceship under his charge to pick them up so that he could save as much time as possible and quickly return to Planet Aquamarine.

The forums that he had missed were opened once again, and he was extremely clear about the players' actions. When the spaceship reached Planet Aquamarine, the scene of the large virus breakout happening in Sanctuary Three had been posted onto the forums. For the players to face a sudden crisis, this was a piece of good news for the Great Mechanic Han, and he realized that this was an opportunity. After leaving Planet Aquamarine for so many years, it was best for him to appear in an unforgettable manner. As such, he had resolutely dropped down from the sky with all of his mercenaries. This was the most classic way for mercenaries to land.

During Version 1.0, he had left behind the majestic name of 'Black Phantom' on Planet Aquamarine. At that time, his name had resounded throughout the entire planet, and he naturally could not come back silently. This was not because Han Xiao wanted to act in a high-profile manner but because this was beneficial to him for his next plan.

A stunning return would fulfil the 'promise' that he made when he left the planet and also reveal how he was closely related to Version 2.0's storyline. This was a way to build up his own image and attract the players to join his faction. Apart from his own strength being powerful enough to provide them with benefits, his image was also extremely important. It was just like a luxury product. After the accumulation from Version 1.0, Han Xiao was extremely clear that he had the advantage of being familiar to the players.

Most importantly...

Acting cool did not need any money!

Upon seeing the crazed looks of joy on Bennett and the surrounding players' faces, it was obvious that his plan was a complete success. Han Xiao was extremely satisfied.

"You..." Bennett opened his mouth but did not know what to say.

"We'll talk later. Let's first take care of things here."

"Alright." Bennett could only bear with his stomach full of doubts. He was extremely curious about Han Xiao's encounters in the galaxy. After all, he could not watch Bun-Hit-Dog's videos.

"Don't worry, I have handled situations like this plenty of times before. Just hand it over to me." Han Xiao patted Bennett on the shoulders and said with a smile, "I am a professional now."

This was not the first time that Han Xiao had dealt with a beast tide, with the beast tide on Sunil being the most memorable.

Han Xiao was extremely clear about the situation before him. As long as he could get rid of the beasts, they would have more than enough time to knock those refugees out. The problem was that the players were not able to stop the beast tide. However, to his mercenaries, stopping the beast tide was a piece of cake.

One time, he had not been powerful enough and had felt that the wilderness of Planet Aquamarine was extremely dangerous. But after spending a long time in the galaxy, his sights had been set higher, and those beasts on Planet Aquamarine were nothing to him. His strength was sufficient to roam unhindered on the planet.

The Black Star Mercenary Group unleashed their full strength, and a few hundred light cannons swept through the beast tide. Large fireballs exploded all around like missiles being dropped from an airstrike. With every wave of their weapons, the beasts would be cleaved in two and fall under their blades. The commotion of the battle had even covered the miserable groans of the beasts.

Whoosh!

Herlous waved his ten-meter-long Battleship Slicing Blade and spun it around like a cyclone. Any beast that came near him would immediately be cleaved into two, and he was like a meat grinder.

Whoosh!

Sehrinde's speed gave him more than ten after-images, and both his daggers were covered in darkness. Sehrinde was like a flying snake as he weaved through the beast tide, leaving behind a small wound on the surface of the beasts' hides. However, his weapon had already penetrated the beasts' hearts, and while it was only a small wound, the single stab that he made had already caused severe internal bleeding within the beasts.

Every beast that was stabbed by him would collapse to the ground the very next moment. His attacks did not have the slightest trace of killing intent but were extremely violent.

Bang bang bang!

The sound of cannon fire rang out from Ginette, who was like a fortress that had unleashed all of its firepower. All the firearms on her body were extended out, and a full twenty to thirty barrels could be seen. A barrage of cannon fire shot down like rain and destroyed everything in front of her. Her face was already flushed red from the excitement.

To her, the joy from opening fire was one that did not lose to sex.

"Roar!"

On the other side, Harmon let out a roar, and his entire body swelled up. His muscles enlarged like a sponge being injected with blood, and his originally dense hair was split up by his muscles. Arteries could be seen protruding out from all over his body, and he looked like a mini giant wearing a beast fur battle robe. His body was even slightly larger than those beasts. In front of him, the elephant-sized beasts suddenly seemed like slightly larger dogs.

He held onto a black axe that was the size of a door. He launched violent attacks one after another and fought just like a warrior. Very soon, his entire body was covered in blood.

Boom boom boom!

Beast after beast was sent flying by him before crashing onto the ground heavily.

Harmon's battle technique was extremely mature. His actions were violent but also had a strange sense of beauty. It was the perfect combination between strength and beauty. A body strengthening Esper ability and subclasses belonging to warriors. It could be said that he was another kind of Pugilist that was even more violent and brutal.

Many of the players did not have the ability to interfere with the fight and hurriedly began recording the battle instead. They watched to the point that their blood boiled with their excitement being raised to the peak. The strength of those Grade B officers far exceeded the standard of Planet Aquamarine, and it was just like watching a film. Black Star's sudden arrival was too big a surprise, and his method of appearing with drop pods was far too cool! He had literally descended from the sky like the bearer of justice!

Han Xiao observed the situation for a moment before deciding that he did not need to take action. With his current strength, he would be able to give the players an even greater mental shock. However, after some consideration, he decided to give up on that idea. It was better for him to give the players some room for imagination and maintain a mysterious front. Only then would his coolness factor break out of the atmosphere.

A sudden crisis that was extremely difficult to deal with had easily been taken care of by the Black Star Mercenary Group. The beasts had all been killed, and their meat could be dried up to solve the current food crisis. Without the crazy beast tide, the players could easily subdue the refugees who had broken out in illness. After some calculations, less than 100,000 people had died, which was far better than the worst-case scenario. At least, if they were only considering the numbers...

Looking at the small mountain of corpses before him, Bennett could not feel the slightest bit of joy.

The outside of the Sanctuary was in ruins, and Bennett temporarily ignored Han Xiao to command the guards to clean up the battlefield. His personality of dealing with the important matters first was something that Han Xiao admired.

The urgent mission was finally over, and the reward was over 100,000 progress points. All the progress that had previously been lost was recovered. Millions of players surrounded Han Xiao and the others excitedly. Ever since Han Xiao left the planet, only the professional players could enjoy interacting with him, and they had truly been too envious of that. Now that Black Star had finally returned, all the players were even tempted to go forward and touch him.

The players were not foreign toward the Black Star Mercenary Group. After all, Bun-Hit-Dog's videos had plenty of viewers. However, the current mercenary group was obviously different from the last video before the update. Who knew what had happened during the update period? The Black Star Mercenary Group clearly had a few new officers. The players only recognized a few of them such as Herlous and Aroshia. They could not help but study the other mercenaries curiously.

"Their armor is so suave."

"So many Sunils! Are they all working for Black Star now?"

Some players immediately noticed Sylvia. "Woah, that girl is so young and pretty. I give her a 9.5."

"There are so many hairy creatures..." Some of the players felt like puking the moment they saw the Luhan Beastmen, who were much taller than the others. However, Harmon looked over at them with a strange look in his eyes filled with desire and excitement. These players immediately felt their butts tighten and their scalps turning numb as they hid in the crowd.

In truth, whenever Harmon saw someone, the first thought that came to his mind was to pull the other party into his War League. Thus, he would be filled with desire whenever he saw someone. He did not have any strange fetishes.

Many of the mercenaries were pretty repulsive, and in comparison, the presence of attractive men and women was magnified. For example, Feidin immediately attracted the gazes of over half the female players.

"That man is so handsome..."

Feidin noticed the gazes of the female players and looked back at them with a warm, sunny smile. In the eyes of those female players, the world suddenly seemed brighter, and their hearts melted.

"Oh my goodness, he is inhumanly handsome!"

"I... I think I'm in love."

"This old man's maiden heart is about to explode!"

Han Xiao turned around to take a look and felt as though bubbles could be seen above the female players' heads as they overflowed with love. He had never imagined that Feidin would have such a use.

The majority of the female players were more emotional, and their views were different from those of the male players. Between practicality and beauty, they preferred the latter. Thus, the gorgeous Feidin was the Achilles heel of all the female players.

Letting Feidin attract the female players will make my faction more attractive. Bringing him was right indeed. Han Xiao nodded and suddenly felt as though he was like a pimp with Feidin being the most popular courtesan under him.

He usually would not think so much, but after seeing the players, Han Xiao was overjoyed. They were walking wallets after all!

While all the female players were looking at Feidin, Han Xiao did not mind in the slightest. As long as it was beneficial to his plan, Han Xiao would not let his confidence in his own charisma get shaken.

Because Bun-Hit-Dog's 'Black Star' series was done like a television drama, the players of Planet Aquamarine were extremely concerned about the development of the Black Star Mercenary Group. They were excited to find out the stories of these new officers, and their hearts were itching with curiosity.

At the same time, the mercenaries were also observing the players.

"Why are the people in my teacher's hometown looking at us with such strange gazes?" Sylvia's whispered softly. "Do any of you have such a feeling?"

"No, isn't it very normal?" Feidin said.

The players who surrounded Han Xiao opened up a path, and they entered the Sanctuary.

After entering the Sanctuary, Han Xiao observed his surroundings and lamented, "Everything is the same as before I left. I truly miss this place... Wait a second, why is there such an ugly statue here? Who is this statue? Why is it placed in my Sanctuary‽ Huang Yu, Huang Yu! Come out and give me an explanation!"

Not too far from the main gate of the Sanctuary was a tall statue of a human figure. Everyone who walked into the Sanctuary would be able to see it. Han Xiao noticed it the moment he walked in and immediately felt disgusted. This was his Sanctuary, how could there be a statue of someone else in this place? Furthermore, the statue was so ugly.

Huang Yu walked forward with sweat all over his face. While he was the current Supervisor of the Sanctuary, in front of Han Xiao, he subconsciously reverted to his assistant attitude and said carefully, "Your Excellency Black Phantom... that is your statue. It's been too long since you left, so I got people to build it in remembrance."

"It is actually pretty nice." Han Xiao's tone changed drastically in an instant.

The mercenaries looked at the statue before looking at Han Xiao while shaking their heads. What is this? It doesn't look like Black Star at all. This is obviously a statue of an ordinary human. We don't even know what species our captain is.

"Teacher, are you very famous in your hometown?" Sylvia asked curiously.

At this moment, Bennett finally had some time. Hearing that question, he could not help but shake his head. "Black Phantom isn't just famous. He is a legend on this planet."

The mercenaries looked at each other. Legend? They were a little curious about the past of their captain.

"Black Phantom?" Sylvia's eyes widened, and she turned around to look at Han Xiao. "It turns out that your nickname has always been so horrible. I thought that it was an exception."

"Do you think that I have been too lenient with you recently? If you want to copy theory books, you can let me know directly. I can ensure that your next year will be extremely fulfilling."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes and pinched Sylvia's cheeks, causing her to cry out in pain.

After the casual chat, Han Xiao would not forget about the important matters. He then turned around and asked Bennett, "What's the situation now?"

"The calamity that you predicted has happened indeed. Jeez, let's continue this in the conference room." Bennett then looked at Han Xiao and asked, "Right, how did you return?"

Han Xiao then seemed to have remembered something. "You reminded me of something. Wait a moment."

He then took out his communicator and pressed a few buttons.

Boom!

Wind pressure suddenly descended, and a large dust and sand cloud was kicked up.

Shadows began appearing on the ground, which expanded rapidly, covering over half the Sanctuary.

Ten or so spaceships hovered over the Sanctuary and covered half the sun. It was truly a majestic sight.

This was the fleet that Han Xiao had brought with him. He did not want to park them outside the atmosphere and thus summoned and parked them above the Sanctuary!

This commotion was a hundred to a thousand times greater than the drop pods!

The players on the ground looked up with their jaws dropped in shock!

Chapter 512: Reunion

The spaceships floated above the Sanctuary silently like a flying fortress. As those on the ground looked up to the skies, they could only see the enormous base of the spaceship and the light blue glow of the ringed-shaped, anti-gravity stabilizer.

This was not the first time that the players on Planet Aquamarine had seen a spaceship. When Han Xiao left Planet Aquamarine, they had also witnessed a spaceship descending. History had repeated itself. However, this time, it was not a single spaceship but an entire fleet of spaceships!

While spaceships could be seen all around in Bun-Hit-Dog's videos, the visual impact of seeing them in person was vastly different.

The players all raised their heads with looks of excitement, and some of them began recording the scene.

Han Xiao's strength was definitely far greater than before. While he did not take action personally, his ability to command so many powerhouses meant that he must be even stronger than them. The question was, just how strong was he?

The players all tried their Detect on Han Xiao, and the interface was still filled with question marks. The danger level was still [Fatally Dangerous], and it was as though there was a feather tugging on the heartstrings of the players, with the itch seeping deep into their bones. They were all extremely curious about Han Xiao's strength.

Ah ah ah, I really want to know!

Han Xiao turned around to look at the dumbfounded Huang Yu and asked with a calm expression, "You don't have any problem with my spaceship stopping above the Sanctuary, right?"

Huang Yu shook his head vigorously as he wiped away his sweat. It was not that he did not have any problems, but he did not dare to have any problems!

Han Xiao looked at Bennett and said, "Let's go. We can talk as we walk."

"Th—This..." Bennett had a face full of shock. After two years of not meeting Han Xiao, Han Xiao had given him far too many surprises. Just what did Black Phantom go through in the universe?

A sense of hope was lit in his heart. Black Phantom had said that he was entering the universe to find a way to resolve the calamity. Since Black Phantom was back, this should mean that the solution had been found, right?

The large crowd then entered the core district of the Sanctuary.

Han Xiao first settled Bennett's problem and chose to leave the players hanging. There was no need for him to be anxious at all. Anyway, they were not able to run anywhere.

He would first let the impact of his return brew in the players' hearts first. This was like the logic of allowing a bullet to fly for a distance. The Great Mechanic Han had never been an impatient person. Impatience would not allow him to catch worthwhile prey.

...

Han Xiao got the other mercenaries to wait on the outside and only brought the officers into the conference room.

Emerald Grass was already waiting inside the conference room. She sized up Han Xiao with a complicated expression and asked, "You saved me from Bell of Death Island back then, but I don't believe that the reason you gave me was real. I am not the only Pharmacist, but you chose me out of all the Pharmacists. Did you predict that I would be able to develop the suppressant with my abilities?"

"Make a guess," Han Xiao replied.

Emerald Grass frowned. She did not mind being used in exchange for her freedom, but she disliked the feeling of being kept in the dark. She had originally wanted to continue interrogating Han Xiao, but the moment her gaze met Han Xiao's eyes, she felt an immense pressure from his gaze like a large rock being pressed down on her chest.

Han Xiao's aura was far more powerful than before. She could only bite her lips and swallow the words on her tongue.

Bennett cleared his throat before changing the topic. "Just as you've seen, the calamity that you predicted has come true. We call it the Mutation Disaster. I hope that you have returned because you found the solution to this calamity. With Planet Aquamarine's technological level, it is impossible for us to solve this calamity. We aren't even able to detect the virus."

"Describe the situation to me." Han Xiao nodded. Because of his influence, the exact process of the Mutation Disaster was different from his previous life. For example, his previous life did not have Sanctuary Three. While the storyline was different, the core of the matter was the same. As long as the core was the same, Han Xiao was not worried about the storyline being changed.

After spending ten minutes, Bennett briefly explained the current situation on Planet Aquamarine.

"The situation is still optimistic, and I came back in time," Han Xiao said.

Bennett paused for a while before asking, "Just what did you go through in the universe?"

He finally had a chance to ask that question. He wanted to know how Han Xiao had built his own organization, the events that he encountered, his current status and so on. He had a stomach full of questions.

"I am currently a mercenary, and these are my comrades." Han Xiao pointed at his officers who were playing Wayne Cards out of boredom.

That bunch of mercenaries truly could not be serious. They could not be bothered about the situation of the calamity at all. In any case, since their captain was there to deal with everything, there was no need for them to worry at all.

Han Xiao briefly described his experiences, but Bennett was still full of shock when he heard the description. The sheer size of the universe was truly out of his expectations.

While he stayed behind on Planet Aquamarine because of his responsibility, Bennett could not lie to himself. He truly wanted to visit the universe deep down in his heart.

Bang!

At that moment, the door suddenly burst open, and Aurora dashed into the room. Her gaze swept past all the officers and immediately fell upon Han Xiao, who was seated beside the door. With a face full of surprise, she pounced straight into Han Xiao's embrace and hugged his waist tightly.

"You're finally back! I really missed you!"

Aurora was like a little kitten lying down on Han Xiao's chest as she revealed a calm expression. Apart from Hila, she was the closest to Han Xiao and relied greatly on him.

Feeling the warm body in his embrace emanating a mild fragrance, Han Xiao could not bear to push her away and smiled helplessly. He could only allow her to hug him as he stroked her hair and said with a warm smile, "You became... cough cough, you grew up."

Aurora's appearance was extremely different from two years ago. Two years ago, she had been weak and skinny with her skin extremely pale, and she had to move around in a wheelchair. Today, her skin was glowing with radiance, and she was extremely healthy. Her entire head was covered with shiny, golden hair, and she was taller than before. She had charged over like a lively tiger and did not even need a wheelchair anymore.

Her Esper abilities granted her a vigorous life force.

This scene attracted the gaze of all the officers as they stared in shock.

Who is this girl? She is actually so close to Black Star. Could it be that our captain is already married‽

Han Xiao let Aurora hug him for a few more seconds before grabbing her up and asking, "Where's your sis?"

"I brought her along. She originally didn't want to come." Aurora giggled.

Ta, ta, ta!

Hila walked into the room. Looking at Han Xiao, she said expressionlessly, "You are finally back?"

"I am back because of things I miss."

Han Xiao could feel a sense of grievance from Hila and was a little surprised.

Hila did not say another word and threw something over at him.

Pa!

Han Xiao grabbed the key and took a glance. It was actually the key to his secret hideout, which he had passed to Hila before leaving.

"Your key," Hila said.

"No, it's your key." Han Xiao threw it back.

Hila caught the key before throwing at back at Han Xiao. "Since you are back, I don't need this key already.

Han Xiao had given this key to Hila so that she had a hiding place in an emergency. For her to say such words, she obviously meant that she would not face any danger now that Han Xiao was back. While she did not say that directly, that was what she felt.

"Do you truly trust me that much?" Han Xiao raised an eyebrow. "Then why didn't you leave with me?"

"That was my choice." Hila's lips twitched. Her gaze then swept past the officers, pausing slightly when she saw Aroshia, Sylvia, and Ginette.

"I thought that you would be pretty happy when you saw me," Han Xiao said helplessly.

"Who are you to me? Why do I need to be happy?" Hila asked.

At that moment, Sylvia said with dissatisfaction, "Teacher is back to save all of you, how dare you talk to him like that?"

As those words were said, everyone looked over with a strange expression.

Sylvia did not understand what was going on and shrunk back with her voice becoming soft. "Why are all of you looking at me? Did I say something wrong?"

"You can keep quiet." Herlous rolled his eyes. "Come, let's continue playing."

This lass is must be blind. The captain is talking to an old acquaintance from his hometown, what has this got to do with you? It is obvious that this red-haired lady is whining to the captain. Why can't you just remain in the background silently? No one will say that you are mute if you don't say anything.

Knock knock knock...

Bennett knocked on the desk with his fingers and said with dissatisfaction, "Hila, don't create trouble for a moment. We are talking about something important."

"Humph." Hila sat down beside Han Xiao.

She then sent out a faint red colored energy toward Bennett's face. She was dissatisfied with his use of the words 'create trouble'.

The moment she sat down, she began playing with the black mask that Han Xiao had placed on the table. This mask reminded her of the previous Germinal Organization leader. Hila would no longer lose her temper whenever she thought about that man. It had already been two years, and she was far calmer than before. She would not be so easily agitated by past events.

"Cough cough, back to our main topic..." Bennett rubbed his slightly numb face and said with a serious expression, "Do you have a way to resolve the Mutation Disaster?"

Han Xiao knocked on the table slowly, and looking at the expectant gazes of those around him, he smiled. "Yes."

Chapter 513: The Truth of the Mutation Disaster

Bennett's eyes lit up, and he was overjoyed.

"However, I will take time, and I need to invite others over. We can only take things slowly," Han Xiao said. "I have investigated the truth of the virus and its theory.

"While you guys call it a virus, its official name is the Mutation Source. It is a special biological weapon and is extremely rare. The reason for it being on Planet Aquamarine is that someone intentionally placed the Mutation Source on the planet."

As these words were said, Bennett was startled.

The Mutation Disaster was actually created by men!

It was unbelievable!

Just what kind of an organization would want to do such a thing to Planet Aquamarine? With such strength, they must definitely be a powerful organization in the galaxy, and Planet Aquamarine was no more than a backward planet to them. Why must they place such a biological weapon on the planet?

"I know what all your doubts are, and the reason behind it is pretty complicated. It's impossible to explain the reason in a few sentences. You only need to know that Planet Aquamarine has become an innocent chess piece between the battle of two galactic organizations."

Han Xiao then paused for a while and allowed Bennett and the others present to absorb that information fully before continuing.

"I know that the appearance of the mutation virus has led all of you to believe that the mutation source works in the minds of the individuals. All of you are completely wrong. The Mutation Source isn't an ordinary virus—it has a consciousness. It can even be considered a special life form that has only one ability: to influence microorganisms."

"Microorganisms?" Bennett was stunned for a moment. Han Xiao's explanation of the mutation virus was truly out of his expectations. All of the infected individuals showed a change in their personalities and actions, but it was actually unrelated to their minds‽

Han Xiao pondered for a moment before asking, "When you want to eat, are you the one who wants to eat, or is it your body that wants to eat?"

"It should be my body. Why would I eat if it isn't hungry?" Bennett then fell into a short daze and seemed to have understood something.

"This is the logic. Often, the source of your thoughts is actually the needs of your body, not what you want. It is the microorganisms in your body telling you what they want. The microorganisms in your body perform certain actions to send out hormones, and your brain receives the signal. This is where the desire to eat, breathe, and all other basic desires come from.

"You think that your thoughts are controlling your body but many times, it is the microorganisms in your body that is controlling your thoughts.

"Many physiology conflicts that happen in our body is due to the conflict between the needs of microorganisms and bacteria in our body. The health of one's body is also dependent on the reaction of the bacteria in our body. If they are alright, then our bodies will be alright. However, microorganisms do not have any consciousness. Our actions will also influence the microorganisms. We can choose to suppress the desires of our body and end up being unhealthy. While we seem to be an individual, we are actually a complete system.

"The Mutation Source controls the microorganisms in our body, thus controlling our basic desires. It secretes dozens of times the normal amount of enzymes to give our brain an intense stimulus. It is completely unrelated to our thoughts and isn't able to control our thoughts. However, it can influence us on a biological level by using the desire to destroy, sexual desire, hunger, grief, and many other emotions to direct our thoughts and cause a huge change in personality. You may even end up thinking that these thoughts belong to you as you are still your ordinary self during the outbreak of the virus.

"The reason that the virus can't be detected from the infected individual is because the virus doesn't exist! The so called 'virus' is the microorganisms that are necessary for one's survival!"

Han Xiao understood the Mutation Source. After all, he had gone through this mission in his previous life and had a deep impression of the event. At his current level, his consciousness could already exist independently, but the organs that were used to control his consciousness would be affected. What if he wanted to be immune to the Mutation Source? Very simple. He just had to transfer his consciousness into a machine and give up his body and senses. With his consciousness being separated and living in the brain of a machine, it would be impossible for the machine to be affected by the Mutation Source.

Including Hila, those from Planet Aquamarine were shocked.

"So, this is theory behind the mutation virus," Emerald Grass muttered. "What are its exact parameters? For example, how is it spread? What is the strength of its control? Also, what is special about the Rhodes Fan Leaf? Why is it immune to the mutation virus?"

Han Xiao snapped his fingers and called the Volga brothers over. "Show a picture of that leaf to them."

Emerald Grass flashed a picture, and after taking a look at it, the eldest Volga brother replied with a calm tone, "Isn't this the Serene Grass? This is a raw material for Focus Medicine."

Emerald Grass was stunned. "What does he mean?"

"What he means is, this Rhodes Fan Leaf is an ingredient used by Mages. Only a Mage will be able to bring out the effects of this leaf. The effect of Focus Medicine is to let a Mage enter a special state of extreme calmness. All of their emotions will be suppressed, and the various parts of the brain relating to emotions will be temporarily cut off. This is the reason for its immunity. Regardless of how the mutation virus tries to send hormones, the brain will not feel any desire. That is the theory behind your suppressant."

Everyone immediately came to a realization. After a while, Aurora suddenly asked in a strange tone, "Is there really magic in this world‽"

Han Xiao had a face full of helplessness but did not want to roll his eyes. This was considered an extremely ordinary piece of information in the galaxy. The ability for a technological civilization to accept new things was truly weak. Their view of the world was far too narrow, and they really needed to broaden their horizons.

After pausing for a moment, Han Xiao continued his explanation.

"In truth, the Mutation Source will not be spread. It has a main body and could be hiding anywhere on the planet. With the main body as the core, its consciousness will be able to cover a large region. In this region, it is able to detect any life forms and control their microorganisms. It is just like a wide-range Esper ability. Apart from the living beings on land, even the living beings in the ocean will be controlled by it. Also, Supers are resistant to its control and won't be affected easily. However, its range and control strength will increase as the Mutation Source grows.

"The control region of the Mutation Source is actually a new living system. The entire control region is like a large body!

"It has only been a month or so since the first outbreak of the virus. The Mutation Source has only just entered its toddler stage from its infant stage. The messy violence in the entire world is only its subconscious action without any purpose or motive. When it matures, it will also become more intelligent, and its actions will gradually have a purpose. That will be the true calamity, and I will be helpless as well. Thus, time is tight."

Han Xiao did not say another word. Those words had already allowed everyone to understand the seriousness of the problem. Bennett's expression was solemn, and he said with a grave tone, "Then what should we... no, what are you planning to do?"

He knew that he would not be able to solve the problem with his own organization, and the only choice would be to place his hopes in Black Phantom... ah, he should be called Black Star now.

"I have my own plans, but before I set my plan into motion, there is something that I have to do first. I will first bring my subordinates to the place where the materials of the suppressant are grown. Let the Mages under me replace all of you in growing the materials. They will be able to increase the yield greatly." Han Xiao smiled. "We also have to deal with the refugees who were knocked unconscious. Furthermore, there may be more coming in the future. I understand you and know that it is impossible for you to ignore them."

"I knew that you would understand me. We are the same kind after all." Bennett smiled and felt a heavy rock being lifted from his heart. The familiar feeling of chemistry between the two had returned.

On the other side, as Han Xiao was explaining the Mutation Disaster to those in the Sanctuary, his return had been detected by the satellites of the Six Nations. All the images of his return were sent back without anything being missed out.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations were shaken!

They were thoroughly shocked!

Chapter 514: Time to Harvest

Because of the Germinal Organization incident, information relating to Black Phantom was of high importance, and everyone in the various intelligence organizations recognized Black Phantom. The very first intel officer who received the satellite image almost thought that he had seen incorrectly. Han Xiao, who had gone to the galaxy two years prior, had suddenly returned. Furthermore, he had returned in such a shocking manner. Just what was going on?

While over half of the Six Nations' strength had been diminished by the calamity, they had maintained their intelligence networks. The intelligence was sent quickly, and not too long later, a complete recording was being played in the meeting between the upper echelons of the Six Nations. After seeing the recording, all of the upper echelons present remained silent with a heavy atmosphere in the place.

They had always thought that only Godora would come to their rescue. However, Han Xiao had actually brought a fleet and descended out of nowhere. Han Xiao had appeared without the Six Nations making any preparations. The upper echelons of the Six Nations were truly at a loss for words.

"Black Phantom is back, and he's brought an entire fleet with him!"

After going to the galaxy two years ago, they had not heard any news about Black Phantom. However, they had never imagined that Han Xiao would still be alive and actually have such an amazing strength in his hands. The mercenaries under Han Xiao had truly shocked the upper echelons of the Six Nations. With their limited view of the world, they felt that the strength that Black Phantom had once displayed was already at the peak of the world. However, they had never imagined that Han Xiao would bring back a few hundred experts from outside the planet to refresh their understanding of the word 'strength'. Furthermore, he had even brought more than ten spaceships with him!

With just this strength alone, it was more than enough to sweep their entire Six Nations away.

When Han Xiao went into the galaxy back then, they had already been stunned once. The Six Nations also wanted to enter the galaxy, but they did not have the technology to do so. They were not able to construct a spaceship, and Godora would ignore all of such requests. As such, they could only grit their teeth and watch with envy.

They did not know what Han Xiao had done in the galaxy. However, the upper echelons of the Six Nations were extremely clear on one point! Black Phantom's realm had far exceeded theirs!

While the Six Nations had placed great importance on the past Black Phantom because of his contribution to the destruction of the Germinal Organization, they still felt that Black Phantom belonged to the same level as them. Using an analogy, it was like how they were all classmates in the same class. The Six Nations were like students who consistently scored above 90 marks, but Black Phantom was a top scorer who always scored full marks. However, they were still in the same class.

But now, Black Phantom had already become a little genius student who could skip grades. He was like a carp who leapt through the dragon's gate and no longer belonged to the same level!

A few days ago, they had been hesitating over whether they should make a move against Sanctuary Three. Now, they no longer needed to contemplate over this matter. In truth, the upper echelons of the Six Nations heaved a sigh of relief instead.

Thankfully, this fellow had come back in time. If they had not been able to control their temptations and he returned, they would probably have been eradicated.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations no longer dared to have any thoughts about the suppressant, but another thought came into their minds. What if they sought Black Phantom's aid?

Godora still had not arrived, but Black Phantom had returned with a fleet. In the eyes of the Six Nations, both Han Xiao and Godora were galactic organizations that were far superior to Planet Aquamarine. Furthermore, Planet Aquamarine was his hometown, and it was likely that he would help.

Since they could not rely on Godora, why not try Black Phantom?

At the same time, the players in the Sanctuary were excitedly sharing their recorded videos on the forums. The Planet Aquamarine board was refreshed rapidly with Black Star's name being one of the most popular keywords.

There were many different versions of the recording, and they came from all different angles. When the other players who were not on Planet Aquamarine witnessed the majestic appearance of Han Xiao, they were immediately drawn into the video and experienced the feelings of the players in the Sanctuary.

The benefits that Han Xiao had brought in Version 1.0 were still fresh in their minds. With the new version being launched and Han Xiao returning from the galaxy, he would probably bring resources from the new version. This was something that they needed. What kind of new benefits would Black Star bring them? Just thinking about this made all the players excited.

The players who went online in the other regions immediately threw down the missions on hand and rushed toward the Sanctuary. All those who were already on the way to the Sanctuary sped up even faster.

As Frenzied Sword and the others who were travelling saw all the posts, they hated the fact that they could not return to Han Xiao's side immediately and were extremely helpless.

We all followed Black Star from Version 1.0. We were supposed to be the first.

Bun-Hit-Dog's videos were immediately shared rapidly throughout the forums, and the players from other novice planets also came to watch the show.

"His appearance truly makes my blood boil. I feel that there is a chance for this scene to be chosen for the advertisement of the new version."

"The Galaxy Times report was right. There are more storylines for this character, and he has indeed appeared in Version 2.0."

"I wonder if others are able to join the Black Star Mercenary Group like the professional players."

As the players discussed the recent events on the forum, someone then made a guess.

"In Version 2.0, every novice planet will be connected to the galaxy. Could it be that Black Star is the NPC to guide us into the galaxy?"

A couple of people pondered over that possibility and realized that it was extremely likely.

The ten or so spaceships in the air would be the best transport to take plenty of them off the planet.

This guess immediately received great approval from many, many players, who thought that Han Xiao was the key character to take them into the galaxy.

In the core region of Sanctuary Three, Han Xiao got the mercenaries who knew magic to aid the growth of the suppressant's raw materials. With their help, the production of the suppressant was greatly increased.

Currently, the Mutation Source was still young, and the effects of the suppressant were able to last for about three months. When the Mutation Source entered its next phase, a few servings of the suppressant would be required in order to achieve the same resistance. Thus, they greatly lacked resources.

Saving refugees would contribute toward the total mission progress, and Han Xiao's mission also enjoyed the mission progress that the players accumulated. However, if they allowed too many people to stay in Sanctuary Three, not only would the place become crowded, the place would descend into a large mess the moment the suppressant lost its effect.

Han Xiao did not want to let too many refugees to stay in Sanctuary Three, but Bennett definitely would not be at ease. The way Han Xiao saw it, the Six Nations had a large territory and would definitely be able to take care of many refugees.

The Six Nations is definitely aware of my return. Since the Godorans have not arrived yet, it is very likely that they will contact me to seek my help. They should be contacting me over the next few days, Han Xiao guessed to himself.

Sharing the suppressant with the Six Nations was beneficial to the bigger picture. While he did not like the other five nations apart from Stardragon, there were benefits to him protecting the nations of Planet Aquamarine. In his previous life, there had only been a single Emerald Grass. With many subordinates under his charge being able to grow the raw materials of the suppressant, Han Xiao could allow them to aid the Six Nations in concocting the suppressant. This would prevent Sanctuary Three from standing out too much and ensure its safety.

Of course, he would only offer them aid if the Six Nations sought his help. It was too well beneath his status to approach them to help them, and it would lower the respect that the Six Nations had toward him. This was not in line with his plans, and he was confident that the Six Nations would try to approach him.

However, Emerald Grass' suppressant was not the only method to resist the Mutation Disaster. Godora was also a magic civilization, and they had their own medicine. However, Godora's medicine was also in short supply. After all, wasting medicine to protect billions of irrelevant backward planet inhabitants was a waste of their resources. Furthermore, Godora had to take care of more than one planet.

In the storyline of his previous life, Godora only handed out limited quantities of medicine, and the majority of the refugees were not able to enjoy it. Players could also earn money through Godora's missions and use the money to purchase the medicine. From there, they would be able to fulfil the requests of some refugees and raise the total mission progress.

However, with Han Xiao's influence, the supply of Emerald Grass' suppressant was greatly increased, and it was pretty much handed out freely. Thus, Godora's medicine would not seem so important anymore. While this did not seem too important, it was an integral factor in Han Xiao's plans.

Because this was related to the exchange of currency.

The players of Planet Aquamarine were currently using the local currency, which was not recognized in the universe, and Han Xiao needed Enas. The players' money was all earned from NPC missions, and since they were not connected to the galaxy yet, they did not have any Enas at the moment. Thus, Han Xiao's target was actually Godora.

Godora would issue missions to the players, and the reward would be in Enas. Since the players did not need to spend their money to purchase Godora's medicine, this money would be saved. When the players saw the many machines and Advanced Knowledge in Han Xiao's store, together with the fact that spending money would increase their relationship with his faction, it was very clear where these players would spend their money.

Thus, Han Xiao did not plan to sell any machines before Godora arrived, and he would only teach skills and knowledge to earn experience.

Godora still isn't aware that the Mutation Source is actually part of DarkStar's schemes. As long as I reveal that fact, Godora will immediately place more importance on this matter and send people over immediately...

He watched the Mages craft the raw materials while pondering over his next step.

DarkStar planted the Mutation Source because of some strategic plan. As long as Godora doesn't show up, DarkStar will not make an appearance. If I inform Godora now and they rush over, the battle between both their camps will break out, and they will become competitors to snatch the players from me. If I do not inform Godora for now, I will have the initiative and make use of this time to increase the attractiveness of my faction to the players...

The moment that both parties were involved, a battle would definitely break out. The period before this was most beneficial to Han Xiao. He had also witnessed the commotion on the forums. Just as he expected, the influence of his return was slowly brewing among the players, and it was extremely beneficial to him.

Han Xiao thought for a while and decided not to reveal his own information and wait for Godora to make their way over on their own. He had the truth of the Mutation Disaster in his hands as well as a copy of the original Mutation Source. He needed to find the right time to hand it over to Godora so that he received the greatest benefits. This was not the best time, and there was no need for him to be so anxious.

My goal is to let as many players join my mercenary group as possible. However, I cannot let anyone join as they wish. I need to set a barrier to entry. If not, I will look like I am desperate. Things that are too easily obtained won't be treasured.

However, if I want to have enough players, I need to set a suitable entry requirement. The only thing that I can be sure of is that many players want to join my faction at the moment. It is best if I can create some competition. After all, the victors are usually envied, and I will be able to make joining my faction a privilege that only the victors can enjoy. This is the best way to make the players take this chance seriously.

After thinking for a while, Han Xiao came up with a pretty good plan. With Version 2.0 being launched, he had many more things to do.

However, before implementing all of these measures, there was one more important thing for him to do. He needed to harvest a large amount of experience to rapidly increase his strength.

Han Xiao was currently level 116, and the experience on his interface was less than 100,000,000. It had been a year since he last increased his level, and the number of blueprints on his skills interface had increased by a few hundred. He truly had a great need for experience at the moment.

It had been too long since he last harvested the players, and he was itching with excitement.

Chapter 515: With a Single Slash, Your Wallet Will Be Dried Up

All of the players were gathered in the plaza with their heads bobbing up and down excitedly. Just an hour ago, the Sanctuary had announced that Black Star was about to give a lecture in the plaza. Because of this, Bennett had set up a temporary stage in the middle of the plaza.

The influence of his return was still blazing, and the response was overwhelming. All the residents in the Sanctuary had arrived, and the surrounding few streets were also completely congested with people. The area surrounding the stage that had the best view was naturally dominated by all the players.

All of them wanted to hear what Black Star had to say after returning from the galaxy.

Ta, ta, ta!

Han Xiao walked out from the core region with the mercenaries following behind him. The eyes of the crowd lit up and burnt with excitement. Wherever the group went, the crowd would open up the path, and it was like the legendary parting of the Red Sea.

Han Xiao walked up to the stage, and the mercenaries waited by the side. Han Xiao looked around him for a while only to see millions of eyes staring back at him. All of his actions were being captured by those many eyes.

Han Xiao's expression was calm. With his thick skin, he did not know what it meant to be anxious. Raising one of his hands, a compressed orb rolled out from his sleeves and landed in his palm. He then threw it out casually.

Buss!

A blue electric bolt flashed.

Under the gazes of the crowd, the compressed orb transformed rapidly and turned into a mechanical throne. He sat down on the throne slowly, which then floated into the sky, hovering ten meters in the air. Underneath the throne was the blue light being emanated by the anti-gravity stabilizers.

Following which, three identical Void Mirror Images facing different directions appeared behind him.

Up in the sky was the circular formation of the spaceship fleet, and the plaza was right in the center of the circle with Han Xiao in the middle.

His coolness factor was immediately maxed out!

"Holy sh*t! Too handsome!"

"Truly the appearance of a bigshot! I think I have seen the second Dragon Emperor!"

"He is truly too cool!"

With his gaze sweeping past the crowd, Han Xiao cleared his throat, and his voice was spread far and wide with a mini loudspeaker.

"I've returned."

Boom!

Just those simple words of his immediately attracted a large wave of cheers from the residents. As the creator of this Sanctuary, his prestige in this place was extremely high, and he was ridiculously popular. The players were also affected by the atmosphere, and Han Xiao's image was elevated a few notches.

He raised his hands to signal for the crowd to remain silent. Very quickly, the crowd fell to pin drop silence and waited for him to continue his speech.

"Two years ago, I foresaw this calamity and headed into the galaxy resolutely in search of the solution. I promised that, for my hometown, I will return to face this calamity with all of you. Today, I have fulfilled my promise.

"The galaxy is a very dangerous place, and I have only obtained this strength after going through many tribulations. You do not need to know the dangers behind it as that is a pain that I bore willingly in exchange for the ability to face this crisis with all of you..."

Han Xiao selected his words very carefully, and he very simply summarized his experience in the galaxy, looking as though he did not wish to talk more about his experiences. This immediately drew out the imagination of the residents in the Sanctuary.

However, the players began snickering in their hearts. They had already found out about Black Star's galactic experience through Bun-Hit-Dog's videos. Even if he did not want to say it, they were all extremely clear about his experience. Furthermore, they all thought that Black Star was not aware of that.

Many players began looking at each other while raising their eyebrows or winking with a 'we already know' look.

Han Xiao glanced at the players, and the corners of his lips curled up slightly.

He purposely chose to say those words to let the players have a sense of superiority because they thought that they understood him well. The moment that they had such a thought, they would have fallen into his trap. The players would not only recall the videos and have an even deeper impression of him, it would be helpful to conceal his future actions as well.

"We are all in the middle of this calamity, and no one will be able to stay out of this calamity. I am willing to share the knowledge that I have gained in the galaxy to aid everyone's growth so that we can go through this calamity together!"

The eyes of the players began glowing. After waiting for so long, they had finally waited for these words.

We can finally learn some new skills!

After saying a few encouraging words, Han Xiao stowed his throne away as a signal that his speech was over.

The residents of the Sanctuary all dispersed, but the players charged forward to surround Han Xiao.

"It has been a long time, Inhuman warriors. I can feel that all of you are stronger than you were two years ago," Han Xiao said with a serious look, acting as though he really did not know that they were players.

Many of the players could not help but think to themselves, You are obviously the one who had the greatest change!

After saying a few words to make himself look like an NPC, Han Xiao began selling the skills. After such a long time, he could finally harvest those adorable players again, and the joy in his heart was overflowing.

After Version 1.0, the players had become extremely familiar with the interface in Han Xiao's skill shop. Now that they could see his interface again, they truly missed it.

Selling his own skills and knowledge was akin to a teacher imparting skills, and he could set his own price to obtain the player's 'tuition fees'. The skills that Han Xiao took out for sale were mainly Mechanic skills. Furthermore, they were skills that the players would be able to learn on their own as long as they reached a certain level. Since the players' levels were still low, it gave Han Xiao the opportunity to teach them those skills earlier than they should have learned them.

However, Han Xiao would not teach the players skills that were too important such as compression technology, mass production, and so on. The majority of the skills that he taught were to increase their Machinery Affinity, foundational skills, and some unimportant low-level blueprints. Blueprint skills had always been extremely popular.

As for Mechanic Knowledge, apart from the entire set of foundational knowledge—after all, the majority of players had not even learned all the foundational skills—Han Xiao also chose a few not-so-important Advanced Knowledges to teach the players. In the past, he did not wish to teach too many Advanced Knowledges, but now that they were in the new version, Han Xiao naturally did not have as many concerns.

Of course, he was not entirely conning the players by allowing them to learn their future skills early. It was a sort of win-win situation for them. After all, the earlier they learned them, the earlier they could use them. It was the same logic as using a skill first so the cooldown would end earlier...

Since the players wanted to learn something and he provided a full package service that was both cheap and convenient, was it not best for him to monopolize the entire market? There were no antitrust laws to restrict him in this world, and it was truly blissful.

"Woah, there are so many Mechanic skills that I have never seen before."

"Heavy Machine Modification, Advanced Radar technology... There is also more Advanced Knowledge than before!"

The players looked at the interface that was full of skills, and excitement could be seen spewing from their eyes.

It was the new version, and there were so many skills that they had never seen before. After Black Star made a trip to the galaxy, not only did his coolness level increase, the benefits that he provided also increased!

Because the players had reached the max level toward the end of Version 1.0, they could only increase the levels of their skills. Thus, many of them had a large amount of experience in their pockets, and Han Xiao was targeting the large savings in their hands!

With the launch of the new version, the players would not be stingy with their experience for sure, and they were all like wealthy tycoons. The Great Mechanic Han would not rest until he sucked all of their wallets dry!

After setting up shop for just a short while, the experience points on his interface swelled up rapidly with notifications popping up every second. The players began learning the new skills without any hesitation, and they spent their experience generously allowing Han Xiao to earn a hefty sum.

Looking at the experience points being constantly refreshed on his interface, Han Xiao smiled in satisfaction. After working hard for half a year, he was like a farmer who was reaping his harvest.

He had been looking forward to this moment!

The experience points brought about by the players was like an overflowing river, nourishing the dried-up land that was Han Xiao's experience. His experience, which had been less than 100,000,000, shot up rapidly as though it was on a rocket.

200,000,000... 300,000,000...

This was even more efficient than in Version 1.0!

Because of Han Xiao's hard work in Version 1.0, the proportion of Mechanic players in the Sanctuary exceeded thirty percent at the moment. This number was far greater than his previous life, and he had a huge market with powerful purchasing power. Han Xiao would not set the price of his skills and knowledge too high, but it definitely was not low either. As compared to the price in Version 1.0, which had been in the thousands, the current prices would be in the tens of thousands at least. Because he was the only 'company' in this market, there was no need for him to lower his prices and compete in the market. This was the advantage of a monopoly.

As long as a hundred people learned skills from him, it would be a few million experience points for him. From the roughly 200,000 Mechanics, the benefits that he could gain would definitely be far greater than Version 1.0. At the very least, it would be 1,000,000,000 experience points. However, at Han Xiao's level, his expenditure of experience points was also extremely high, and his expenditure in the future would be even greater. As such, there was no such thing as too many experience points.

Only someone like Han Xiao would be able to power level in one go. When the players reached his level, they would need to do plenty of missions before receiving enough experience to level up once. Furthermore, they would still be overjoyed because of that single level up. In his previous life, the tender and young Great Mechanic Han had also been like that. In the end, he had gradually become an old, salted fish. Alas, he had once been an energetic youth but aged as he entered the pugilistic world.

With the current speed, I should be able to obtain sufficient experience to get to level 120 by today...

Once he reached level 120, he would have another Promotion Mission to complete. Thankfully, he still had another Mission Completion Card in his hands, and if the mission was too difficult, Han Xiao was prepared to just use the Mission Completion Card. After all, he had to stay on Planet Aquamarine for the time being and did not have the time to do a mission.

He would need an enormous amount of experience to get to level 140, and harvesting once would probably not be enough. Teaching skills and knowledge was not a one-off event. If a player learned the same skill a second time, it was equivalent to finding a teacher to increase the level of the skill. Thus, Han Xiao would be able to gain benefits for the foreseeable future, and he was extremely patient.

He did not only want a single abundant harvest. He wanted a long-lasting harvest that even his children and grandchildren could enjoy.

His personal skills would naturally cater to the Mechanic players, but Han Xiao naturally would not forget about the other two classes on Planet Aquamarine. Ensuring profits from all avenues was the way to go.

"All the skills belong to the Mechanic class. How depressing!"

Black Star was a Mechanic teacher, and the happiest crowd was naturally the Mechanic players. Their faces flushed red from their joy, and they would burst out in chuckles randomly. The Pugilist and Esper players could only watch from the side enviously. Who told them not to choose the Mechanic class back then? How wonderful it would have been if Black Star was the teacher of their class!

Since they could not learn Black Star's skills, the players from the other two classes opened up the shop interface only to realize that they were actually able to open up the faction store of the Black Star Mercenary Group!

"Isn't this the faction store in Bun-Hit-Dog's videos? It is actually open to us too!"

"Right, I wonder if we can join the Black Star Mercenary Group and become one of them? Maybe we can even be featured in Bun-Hit-Dog's videos!"

"All of these items are grayed out. We can only see them but not buy. Oh, I understand, we can only check on the goods in the faction store but can't purchase them if we don't join."

"Wait, look at this!"

As the players viewed through the faction store carefully, they were immediately overjoyed. In the interface of the faction store, apart from the various equipment being sold, there was actually Pugilist and Esper Advanced Knowledge!

However, the faction store could only be browsed at the moment, and they could only purchase the items in the store if they joined the faction. Furthermore, the requirement for purchasing the Advanced Knowledge of these two classes was a favorability of [Friendly] with the faction. This required 1,000 points of Faction Favorability.

"Black Star, we want to join your mercenary group!"

"How can we join the group?"

The players all began to squeeze forward and bombard Han Xiao with questions. Because Han Xiao had always tried to build his image up together with the videos that Bun-Hit-Dog produced, they all had a good impression of the Black Star Mercenary Group. Seeing practical benefits being placed before their eyes, they immediately wanted to join the mercenary group and could not wait any longer.

"Want to join my mercenary group?" Han Xiao acted as though he was extremely surprised.

After 'thinking' for a moment, he said, "This isn't impossible, but... my members are all elites who have been chosen through strict screening. If your strength can meet the requirement, I welcome all of you to join."

Chapter 516: Feelings Are Not Enough—One Has to Employ a Routine

Elite? Selections?

The moment this statement came out, many of the players immediately thought of the Thirty Second True Men Group that had followed Black Star when he left and immediately felt discouraged.

Could it be that this is another test from Black Star? But your subjects here cannot achieve it! If we could, then we would have gone along with you to the galaxy outside during Version 1.0!

"As long as you can prove your strength by passing through the warriors under me, the doors of the Black Star Mercenary Group will be open to you," Han Xiao simply explained before throwing out the mission that he had prepared beforehand.

_____________________

Selection of Mercenaries

Mission Introduction: Black Star Mercenary Group has been on numerous campaigns everywhere in space, and all their members are strong experts. So long as you can successfully pass their test, one can join Black Star Mercenary Group, becoming an elite mercenary.

Mission Objective: Battle against an arbitrary mercenary.

Reward: 1 Experience, Black Star Mercenary Group Faction unlocked, +100 Black Star Mercenary Group Relationship

_____________________

After frantically reading through, the players burst into discussion.

"Turns out, Black Star is not personally selecting this time."

"The mission does not describe what sort of battle test it will be. Do you think it would be a one on one PVP like before?"

Han Xiao signaled with his eyes, and the mercenary behind carried out a translucent screen that had been prepared beforehand, erecting it at the side. Pointing to the screen, Han Xiao announced, "If you wish to participate in the selection, enter your information here. Phillip will assign a number to each applicant, and this will determine your batch in the selection battles. Pay attention to which one you will be participating in."

The screen lit up, and a blue circle appeared in the middle, surrounded by little particles floating around. It gently bobbed, and the AI started to speak.

"Black Star Artificial Intelligence Phillip, hum... Very glad to be of service, hum..."

Many of the players let out an expression of surprise and moved to input their information such as name, profession, and other particulars. They received a number, which represented themselves, and very quickly, a new interface was soon displayed on the screen. It displayed a new selection process and invited a few hundred numbers onto the arena to take the test.

The screen also displayed the mercenary who was hosting this current selection—Herlous.

After studying it, the players understood the selection mechanism involved. This was not a one on one PVP but one against many. A Black Star mercenary would pit themself against a few hundred players, and all they had to do was persist for a period of time. Once the time was up, if one was not dead and still alive in the arena boundaries, they would have passed the test and could join Black Star.

At the same time, more than one selection would be taking place. The number of people in each selection would also differ, together with their opponent. It was up to chance as to which mercenary of Black Star one could meet. The most important point was, even if one failed the challenge, they could reapply through Phillip. There were no restrictions, and challenges could continuously be handed out.

The players were not suspicious of him at all. All of them felt that this was an interesting challenge, and their fighting spirits were stirred, causing more and more to apply.

Han Xiao was the one who had decided on this challenge method. This was to allow the hundreds of mercenaries under him to help in evaluating the players, since the mercenaries were idling by anyway. Instead of allowing them to play with cards every day to while time away, it would be better to use the time efficiently and save his strength.

This selection was actually just a formality. He was, of course, aware of the current standard of the players. While the more the merrier, he could not just accept every Tom, Dick, and Harry that walked over to greet him. That would be too easy. After all, for the elite factions, which one of them did not have any criteria? As such, setting up a selection was a clever way, which would make players feel that there was a threshold for joining the Mercenary Group. It provided a feeling of exclusivity.

He had thought about it the day before and decided to make this challenge into a daily activity for the players. A mercenary would select dozens to hundreds of players at a time—the specific number would be controlled by Phillip depending on the mercenary's strength. This ensured that the strength of the players would be in an acceptable range for the mercenary, allowing them to easily handle any situations. Phillip, who was in charge of the data of every mercenary, would not make a mistake in this regard.

Each arena had thousands of players, and it resembled a battle royale. In addition to dealing with the Boss—or rather, Mercenary—they also had to prevent themselves from being schemed against, ensuring that they could stay till the end and be among the final survivors. This became a sort of competition.

In actual fact, Han Xiao's original idea was not to have the mercenaries participate but rather to simply allow the players to select among themselves in a grand battle royale. However, the efficiency of recruitment would be terribly low because there would be no one with an overpowered strength like the mercenaries. Thus, every battle would last for a long time. Furthermore, they would not have been able to showcase the strength of the Black Star Mercenary Group.

Moreover, that sort of beast style selection would have raised a sense of dissatisfaction within the players as if they were being looked down on. Thus, Han Xiao finally settled on his current model, using his mercenary group to host a test. Not only did it improve efficiency, it also acted as a lubricant, reducing the probability of player dissatisfaction and making the selection less savage.

The participation of players did not consume any resources, and if they failed, they could wait for their number to be drawn again. This ensured that the threshold to accept players would not be high, which allowed a large pool of players to participate. In addition, the current stage of the mutation disaster only gave the players missions to rebuild a refuge. Therefore, this would bring more flavors to the players' lives. This could be treated as a side dish to the main mission.

As for the selection venue, it was naturally the arena that Han Xiao had built in his Sanctuary. The Pro League had been held there, but now that it was vacant, Han Xiao had claimed it back for his own use. Bennett and Huang Yu had naturally not objected to it.

...

Ten minutes later, players numbering in the thousands flocked to the arena. This was the first selection battle, and even if it did not concern them, everyone chose to head over to spectate, to observe the specific process.

Herlous stood in the largest central ring while hugging his Battleship Slicing Blade, staring hungrily at the players surrounding him. He seemed to be surrounded by howling winds and icy coldness.

The spectating players began to discuss fervently.

"The limit is two minutes. After two minutes, so long as we don't fall out of the ring and aren't dead, we can then join the Black Star Mercenary Group."

"With a few hundred here, holding out for two minutes should be simple task..."

"Simple? Stop joking. Didn't you see the video series from Bun-Hit-Dog on Black Star? This guy is Herlous. He's an extremely strong mercenary from the Black Star group. I think just a slash of his blade can pulverize this arena! Even if you have never seen his videos, you should have experienced the war yesterday, right? Didn't you see him mowing down the beast horde?"

"Nope, didn't see anything. I was dead at that time."

Herlous surveyed his surroundings. Han Xiao's instructions to him were to attack appropriately as he saw fit. If he put forth his full strength, two minutes would be more than enough to wipe the floor with them. Most of the players were still at Grade D, with some having only hit Grade C, a far cry from his current standard.

Seeing the insane throng of Supers, a blaze of fighting spirit was kindled in Herlous' heart. Black Star was indeed not lying to him—this place really held tens of thousands of Supers!

With Planet Sunil currently suffering from a catastrophe, Han Xiao had once sworn to him to bring a human wave more frightening than the current horde from their catastrophe, to solve the Sunils' problems once and for all. Herlous had always believed Han Xiao's words, and upon seeing his promise in the flesh, he was moved to the point that he found his emotions hard to suppress.

Silently, Herlous grasped his Battleship Slicing Blade tightly, lightly nodding.

"The selection starts now, hum..." Phillip's sound droned.

Boom!

The next moment, the majority of players rushed toward Herlous from all directions. A variety of attacks were let loose along the way. The huge numbers on their side gave them assurance, and they decided to tackle Herlous like they would a Boss, outputting as much damage as they muster.

Only a small portion of players did not advance and instead retreated, hiding behind those rushing forward.

Seeing the mass of players rushing at him from all directions, Herlous' expression remained impassive. He raised his blade and spun it around him like a whirlwind, releasing a ring-shaped blade waves around him that shot toward the players, covering almost half the ring. It annihilated all the long-range attacks, and as it approached the pugilists, they could not block the attack, directly being sent flying toward the edge of the arena. Their HP instantly fell about forty percent.

"F*ck me, this AOE is too scary!"

"That was too risky. I almost fell off the ring."

The vanguard players suffered a huge setback, and their facial expressions greatly changed. The small portion of the players who had stayed outside from the beginning and thus escaped the attack were secretly relieved.

Thankfully, we didn't have a hard head and managed to endure the urge to rush forward.

For the players currently, Herlous' strength completely outclassed them. Han Xiao had long guessed that the players would have the mentality of attacking a Boss when they approached this selection battle. Thus, he had chosen to let Herlous handle the first round, giving off an image of invincibility in his Mercenary Group. As for the next few matches, all those mercenaries involved were also in his elite team.

There was no suspense regarding the result. Even if Herlous went easy, this group of players was still cut down effortlessly, one knife for one person.

The players could only change their thinking of clashing head on, instead frantically scrambling in all directions, roaming at the fringe of the arena to try and survive. This appeared to be extremely stimulating.

Then the two minutes were up, less than ten players remained alive. Only when Herlous sheathed his blade did the surviving players realize, as though they had just woken up from a stupor. Expressions of joy colored the faces of the survivors.

"We... we won‽"

The defeated players had expressions of envy and anger. To actually allow such sneaky b*stards to win the prize, was there no justice in this world‽

Out of the hundreds of participants, not even ten people had succeeded. The percentage was low, but this was deliberately done by Han Xiao. He wanted to push down the success rate, to give off the impression that winners would be rare, before gradually allowing the success rate to increase over time.

"Congratulations to those who have passed. Black Star welcomes you. When we go back to space, we'll register you in the Mercenary Alliance. At that time, you will be actual mercenaries."

Herlous extended his hand, shaking it with all the survivors present. This was another of Han Xiao's requirements, to reflect the differential treatment between the two parties.

The survivors were exhilarated as they found out their faction interface had come to live. They no longer needed to find Black Star to browse the faction store, and the items within were no longer grayed out. While they did not possess any Enas to purchase the products, the world of colors was definitely better than one of monochrome gray.

Only the mission [Selection of Mercenaries] for this group of survivors was counted as complete, and they obtained 100 Faction Contribution Points. Having seen Bun-Hit-Dog's videos, they understood that for Faction favorability at the [Friendly] Reputation or below, 100 points could only be bought using 50 Enas. All of them felt that they had technically earned 50 Enas!

The few of them turned ecstatic with joy.

The onlookers were envious, and they keenly noticed a key point in the conversation, which was Herlous mentioning, "Go back to space".

"Does this mean, as long as we pass the test, we will be able to follow Black Star and leave Planet Aquamarine when this storyline ends?"

"We didn't guess wrong; Black Star is indeed the interstellar travel guide that was sent to bring us in Version 2.0!

The eyes of the players lit up, and they all suddenly felt eager to move, unable to wait to participate in the next selection.

The next selections were carried out step by step, and Han Xiao no longer bothered to keep a watch.

Because of the large quantity of players, Han Xiao's timetable showed a great many selection battles each day. A selection battle would be carried out roughly every twenty minutes, and in the numerous rings around the arena, there would be multiple selection battles being carried out. A rough estimate showed that around four to five thousand people would participate each day, with the pass rate maintained at around five percent.

There were over a hundred thousand players in the Sanctuary, and with every player having a chance, this activity could be carried out for a long period of time. A thin stream would allow the water to flow for a longer period. After all, not only was this challenge novel and interesting, the majority of players held on to the mentality that they would be lucky. The Great Mechanic Han had always believed that this sort of mistaken notion greatly helped in his plan, as it allowed the players to willing jump into his pit.

In another few days, the players will adapt to the selection battles. When they get on the right track and the success rates increase, I won't need to worry about it anymore.

Regarding the plans for his faction, Han Xiao had prepared many methods. However, it was not the time to utilize them—this selection was merely an opener.

Furthermore, the difficulty of this selection process would also create a demand for players to get stronger quickly. This would also allow for an increase in his own sales, killing many birds with one stone.

...

From dawn to dusk, the square was crowded with people. After drowning in sounds for the whole day, Han Xiao prepared to pack up.

In just one day, his experience gained broke past the billion mark.

A total of 1.29 billion experience, I haven't felt this refreshed in such a long time... Han Xiao comfortably breathed out, feeling extremely satisfied in his heart. The last time such a large-scale harvesting had happened for him was two years ago before he left Planet Aquamarine. It felt as though a dry desert was welcoming its first rainfall in a long time.

This amount should be enough for me to level up to 120, with some surplus left over.

Opening his interface, Han Xiao was prepared to level up. At this time, a rumbling sound echoed from the sky.

When he raised his head, he saw a new spaceship descending slowly. This was the spaceship that he had sent to fetch Frenzied Sword and the others. They had finally arrived.

Whoosh!

The hatch opened. Frenzied Sword, Bun-Hit-Dog, Hao Tian, and the other players carried jetpacks on their backs as they descended to the square.

The majority of players present recognized this batch of high-levelled players. They all glanced over, with faces of amazement.

"Hey, you guys are back!"

Many people greeted them warmly. This group of players had performed brilliantly in the Pro League and had garnered a lot of fame. Furthermore, they had also gone off the radar for a long time.

Chapter 518: The Bargaining Chip Is the Future

When the two of them entered the secret conference room, the upper echelons of the Six Nations had already been waiting for a while. The gigantic screen in the conference room showed the images of the Six Nations' leaders. This was a long-distance video conference.

The moment that Han Xiao walked in, the upper echelons of the Six Nations began to size him up. Han Xiao then turned around and gave Bennett a look, and Bennett retreated to the side to indicate that he would not be participating in the negotiations.

"The leaders of Stardragon, Hesla, Raylen, Theseus, Maple, and Ordina, I believe that this should be our first meeting. Good evening, gentleman," Han Xiao said with a calm tone.

"Hello, Black Phantom. More accurately, you should be called Black Star now. We noticed you a long time ago, and we are very happy to have this conversation."

The leader of Stardragon replied with an amiable smile. Because Han Xiao had once worked for Stardragon's intelligence agency, their relationship was the best, and the leader of Stardragon was the representative for this conference.

Han Xiao raised his brows. "I know what all of your intentions are. Just be straightforward."

"Bennett understands our intentions, but we would like to have a personal conversation with you. Bennett said that the purpose of your return is to protect this planet and its inhabitants from being destroyed by the Mutation Disaster. You are a person of class, and we truly admire you. Just as you have observed, our citizens are living in threat and worry every day, and we hope to seek your aid through this meeting."

The Stardragon leader did not beat about the bush and got straight to the point.

"What are your requests?"

"We hope that you can help restore our fractured social system and save our citizens who are in danger."

"How do you want me to achieve that?" Han Xiao said patiently.

"After some discussion, we all hope that the Sanctuary can share the recipe of the suppressant and its raw materials with us, and send people to instruct us on the concoction process. At the same time, we hope to obtain a large amount of completed suppressant to solve our countries' immediate needs. We will need to first recover our government building and army before trying to quarantine and save our citizens. As long as we can regain our strength, we will be able to prevent the situation from worsening. In this process, we hope to borrow the strength of your warriors and fleet. We will inform you again of our detailed plan."

"Doesn't sound too bad. You guys delayed contacting me for a day to discuss this plan, right?" Han Xiao said calmly without giving a reply. "Then, what kind of benefits will I gain?"

The leaders of the Six Nations were stunned for a moment. Didn't you come back specially to stop the calamity? Didn't you help the refugees unconditionally? Why are you talking about benefits now?

"Why are you so surprised?" Han Xiao raised his brows. "Isn't this a trade? If there aren't any benefits, don't waste my time."

"This... no one will be able to avoid the calamity, and fighting the calamity is everyone's responsibility. Why would this be a trade? Didn't you return to save the inhabitants of this planet?" The leader of Ordina interrupted.

"Indeed, but that isn't what we're talking about now." Han Xiao folded his arms and continued. "All of you want to borrow my strength to restore your control over your nation. I help you restore stability to your nation, and you give me benefits in return. This is a fair trade. If not, why should I help all of you?"

"Helping us will allow more refugees to be saved. Isn't this a reason?" the leader of Hesla said.

"Everyone has to die eventually, and it is a pipe dream to save everyone on the planet," Han Xiao said. "You've all read my file before and know that I am not an idealist. My goal is to stop this calamity so that this planet will not be destroyed. Regardless of how many people die, I will be able to accept the outcome. Don't make use of this to hold me hostage. I am not Bennett and am not as kind as him. This isn't a chip that you guys can use to get me to do whatever you want.

"The life and death of your regime has nothing to do with me. I can just guard the Sanctuary and wait for refugees from all over the world to seek aid from me. They would not foolishly wait for their deaths in your nation. When all of your regimes are destroyed, I can then support the Sanctuary to become the new and sole ruler of the planet."

Bennett opened his mouth and wanted to say something. He did not have the ambition to rule and did not agree with this point. However, after some hesitation, he decided to watch from the side and trust Han Xiao.

"I don't deny that all of you do indeed intend to save your citizens. However, your biggest motive is to borrow our suppressants and my strength to prevent your regime from collapsing. This is something that you cannot deny." Han Xiao shook his head and said coldly, "Since all of you are pleading for help, make sure you look like you are seeking aid. The one who has the right to make demands is me, not you guys."

The leaders of the Six Nations were both angered and shocked. They had never imagined that Han Xiao would be so straightforward.

"No, I think you are misunderstanding something. You are not as important as you think," Theseus' leader said. "We have already sought aid from Godora, and they will arrive quickly. We are only seeking your aid so that we can save more people. Since you are so impolite with us, we cannot do anything. I hope that you remember that your rejection has caused many people who could have survived to die. They were all killed by you."

Black Star was not their only hope, and the Six Nations were only testing Han Xiao's attitude. In their hearts, they still trusted Godora more.

"We are all wise individuals, so don't bother using such words as a threat. It is no more than a joke. Since you guys talked about being impolite..." Han Xiao shook his head and smiled. "Godora should be very polite with all of you, but apart from providing the knowledge required for the awakening of Supers, what other aid had they given to you?

"Not only did they not give all of you any aid, they even shook the order of society. It was Godora's appearance that caused the war of hundred nations a few decades ago, causing the deaths of millions. Furthermore, the rescue force of Godora still has not arrived, am I right?"

The Six Nations' delegates fell silent.

Han Xiao raised his brows and suddenly changed topics. With a teasing tone, he said, "A few years ago, I helped all of you win against the Germinal Organization. At that time, I did not participate in the meeting between all the upper echelons, but today, you took the initiative to contact me. Why is there such a drastic change in our status in just two short years? Why is there such a huge difference?"

The faces of the Six Nations' leaders darkened, and they felt their hearts being stabbed.

They were only having a negotiation, and they could forget the matter if a consensus could not be reached. But why did he have to pour salt in their wounds!

What a cruel guy!

"All of you can only hug Godora's thighs as though they are your ancestors. Even if all of you don't understand the other party, you still have to coax them with an amiable tone and humble yourselves like their grandchildren. As for me, not only do I understand their civilization, I have even worked together with them before. We have a good working relationship, and I can even contact their upper echelons. Can any of you do that?"

The faces of the leaders were completely black. This was a truth that they all understood. As leaders, how could they be willing not to hold any authority in their hands? However, the gap between the two civilizations forced them to lower their heads.

They did not know about Black Star's achievements in the galaxy, but if Han Xiao was speaking the truth, then Black Star's strength was far more powerful than they had imagined.

Han Xiao knocked on the table and said, "If Godora helps you to deal with the Mutation Disaster, they will definitely depart on their spaceships the very next moment, leaving behind the aftermath of the disaster. All of you will still be citizens of a backward planet, and nothing will change. Hope that Godora will take all of you into the galaxy? You know that this is impossible."

The gazes of the leaders changed, and they all knew that what Han Xiao said was the truth. Godora would save them from the calamity but would definitely not help them to develop. They were all extremely clear about this. It was just like how Godora gave them a Galactic Communicator but locked more than ninety-nine percent of its functions. They could only contact Godora unilaterally but would not be able to understand the galaxy.

Even if the Mutation Disaster was resolved, they would have to clean up the mess on their own. Not only would they be unable to advance, their weak civilization might even regress.

Han Xiao did not stop there and continued, "If you want to talk to me on equal grounds, all of you have to enter the galaxy at the very least. However, your technology is a few hundred years lacking before you can become a member of the galaxy. Are all of you going to place your hopes in a technological boom that would take a miracle to happen? Are you resigned to such a fate?"

"What exactly do you mean?" the Stardragon leader said.

"Don't you understand? Only me. Your only hope is me!" Han Xiao slapped the table hard as he raised his voice. "I am your only choice because I am the only person from Planet Aquamarine who is in the galaxy. Only I am willing to help you develop!"

The leaders of the Six Nations were dumbfounded.

"You, what you mean is..."

"Accept reality. I am not negotiating about disaster relief but about the future!"

Han Xiao placed his arms behind his back as he pressured the leaders of the Six Nations with his charisma.

In his previous life, while the players had managed to complete the Mutation Disaster Main Storyline Mission, they had dragged the mission for too long. When Godora solved the Mutation Disaster, the Six Nations had already collapsed, and there had only been darkness left behind in the civilization. The citizens who had lost their homes could only struggle on for their lives.

Because Godora discovered the player's special potential through the process of fighting the disaster, Godora had set up a stronghold in the almost destroyed Planet Aquamarine to receive the never-ending stream of new Inhumans.

Han Xiao leaned toward protecting the Six Nations. No matter what, it was much better to have a mature regime rule over the place as it would make it much easier for any organization to function on the planet. Planet Aquamarine was a novice planet, and if Han Xiao could construct a base there, he would be able to have an endless stream of players.

Those words of his immediately stirred up a storm in the hearts of the Six Nations' leaders. They all fell silent and began thinking about the pros and cons.

Han Xiao's words had truly moved them. While Godora was powerful, they were aliens after all and not their kind.

Black Star, who was from Planet Aquamarine, was truly one of them!

Even if they did not want to admit it, their rationality told them that this was the only chance for them to change the fate of their civilization.

"What do you want?" The tone of the Raylen's leader was hoarse.

"My words are already very clear, and all of you know what I want. Even if you don't wish to give it to me, I can take it myself."

"Your ambitions are too large..."

"Trust me, the vastness of the galaxy is worth this little sacrifice. You will not regret your choice of purchasing this ticket. You will only regret it for life if you miss this opportunity."

Buzz!

The screen suddenly turned black.

Bennett was still in a state of shock as he asked, "Did they reject?"

"No."

Han Xiao's lips curled up slightly. "They are discussing."

Bennett looked at Han Xiao and said with a complicated gaze, "You have changed."

"I haven't changed." Han Xiao shrugged and casually said, "It's just impossible to understand every side of a person."

Bennett did not reply anymore with his heart in a complete mess. Black Star wanted to become the ruler of the entire planet! Could it be that the motive for his return was not to save people but to rule over the planet‽

He did not know whether Han Xiao's actions were right or not. History had proven the tragedy of gathering authority in a single person's hands many times. He had seen the desolate outcome of far too many ambitious individuals. The source of a disaster was very often an inflated desire.

Time seemed to have passed by very slowly, and after waiting for ten minutes, the screen finally lit up again.

The leaders of the Six Nations appeared and looked at Han Xiao with a complicated gaze.

"As long as you are able to fulfil your promise, we are willing to satisfy all of your requests. We will use all of our strength and listen to your orders.

"We accept your conditions!"

The Six Nations truly did not have much of a choice in this matter. As long as a single regime accepted Han Xiao's proposal, the other nations would fall behind if they did not accept it. Stardragon was the first to display their willingness to submit, and after some discussion, the other five nations also agreed. Black Star had already entered the galaxy, and it was not embarrassing for them to submit to him.

One party was always high up on their thrones and treated them like dogs. The other party was one of their kind and promised to help them. Since they wanted to hug someone's thigh, they would definitely choose the latter.

They did not ask Han Xiao in detail what he could give them because they were extremely clear that they did not have such rights. This was not a fair trade as they did not have any chips in their hands. It was just as Han Xiao had said. Even if they were not willing to give, he could take it himself!

This was just Han Xiao pitying them!

Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief in his heart and was pretty happy. However, he maintained his calm expression and said with a smile, "My men will land in your territories soon and aid you in restoring order."

The leaders nodded.

"Since we have come to a consensus, tell me a small nugget of intelligence first." Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. "Where is the Bell of Death Island?"

Chapter 519: Bell of Death Island (1)

Bell of Death Island was a secret base built jointly by the Six Nations, and they managed it together. Its coordinates were an absolute secret, and one could only enter but not exit. The criminals locked up in it were all special criminals. Some of them were their political enemies, some were traitors of the nation, and some were Supers who broke the law. While the people who were locked up were different, one thing was common among all of them. Their crimes were not simple, and they definitely would not be simple serial killers.

Without having a particular talent, they would not have the rights to be locked up in Bell of Death Island.

Many of the criminals in this place had committed innumerable crimes, and the only reason that the Six Nations had kept them alive and locked them up in this god forsaken place was because of their talents. The Six Nations hoped to wring them dry for all they were worth.

It could also be understood that the Bell of Death Island was a place where the Six Nations kept their talents; the place was brimming with talents.

A small portion of the criminals came to an agreement with the Six Nations and used themselves in exchange for better treatment. However, the majority of the criminals refused to submit and would mock all the negotiators sent by the Six Nations. They were extremely brutal and cruel with even the prison wardens being afraid of them. Many of the criminals had a complete ban to prevent people from even approaching them.

Just yesterday, the Six Nations had lost contact with the Bell of Death Island. With the entire planet being swept up by a calamity, the Six Nations were not able to protect themselves, let alone the Bell of Death Island.

The Six Nations did not know that the Bell of Death Island was also affected by the Mutation Disaster. The prison wardens had broken out in illness and thrown all of their responsibilities to the back of their heads.

There were some prison wardens who had even opened up the metal gates of the criminals, and it was as though they had just released a ferocious beast.

Puchi.

Human blood was sprayed all along the grayish metal corridor, and the large lightbulb in the middle of the room was covered with a huge blotch of blood on it, causing the entire walkway to be covered in a red eerie light.

A two-meter-tall Sharnuk threw the corpse of a warden that had been cleaved in two onto the ground.

The burly Sharnuk was half naked with his muscles bulging out, covered in scars from battle and the natural vein lines of a Sharnuk. He was a baldie. More accurately speaking, all the male prisoners had been shaved bald.

The burly man flicked away the blood on his hands, and looking back, the corpse of more than ten prison guards could be seen, including the prison warden in charge of the region. A few hundred empty golden cartridges were littered all over the ground, and there were a few rifles that had been crushed. A bloody stench had filled the entire room.

The prisoners were all locked up in individual cells, and the distance between each cell was a few hundred meters. At the end of both sides of the metal corridor was a thick metal door, and every cell was located in a sealed-up corridor.

There was not a single window in the corridor, and as the burly man tried to ram his fists into the walls, he was only able to leave a slight dent on the wall. He only had two options before him—he could either walk forward or walk back.

Ever since he was locked in this place, he had never left his cell before and naturally did not know how to find his way around the place. He could not be bothered to change into the tight clothes of the prison guards and looked at the camera in the corner of the corridor.

"Suddenly opening up my cell, and there isn't anyone stopping me even now. Hmm? There is a trace of danger in the air. Just what has happened in this place?" the burly man muttered to himself.

Being locked up in the Bell of Death Island, none of the prisoners had access to any information and naturally did not know what was going on outside.

Without any hesitation, the burly man decided to walk forward. After a few hundred meters, he was stopped by a metal door. After feeling the thickness of the door, he took a deep breath and pulled his right fist back.

With his muscles bulging out, he smashed his huge fist on the door.

Boom! Boom! Boom!

After twenty or so heavy blows, a deep circular dent was created on the metal door. As the man rammed into the door with his shoulder, this metal door was immediately shattered, and the corridor was opened for him.

Walking forward for a short distance, he finally saw the prison cell in this corridor. In front of the cell were the corpses of a few prison guards, and the prisoners had already escaped from the cell. There was pretty much no chance for anyone to get to know the other inmates, and the burly man was no exception. He did not know who his 'neighbor' was either.

He did not think any further and continued to walk forward. Very quickly, he saw another metal door, but this door already had a large hole in it. It had obviously been created by his neighbor, who had also met with some good luck.

The burly man did not stop there and continued walking past a few more cells. There were some cells without any corpses, but all of the doors to the cells were opened. They were obviously saved by his neighbor. The doors along the way had been smashed through, and he was able to pass through without any obstructions.

Very quickly, he began to pick up his pace so that he could catch up to the person in front of him.

After running for a short while and passing through a door, the never-ending walkways finally ended, and there was a large hall in front of him instead. In the middle of the hall was a grayish black metal cylindrical tube that connected the ground to the ceiling. This was an elevator well that was currently surrounded by inmates. Upon hearing the footsteps of the burly man, they all turned behind to take a look.

"Another lucky one. One who escaped on his own." A skinny, middle-aged man walked out from the crowd of prisoners and sized the burly man up before saying, "If you are not one of the prisoners that I missed along the way, you should be my neighbor on the other side. Let me introduce myself, I am called Shijake, a high-level Executive Officer of the Germinal Organization. I was caught eleven years ago."

"A member of the Germinal Organization? No wonder you were caught." The burly man nodded. "I am called Tyne, and it has been four years since I was caught. What happened in the prison? Why did they release us all? Furthermore, there isn't anyone coming forward to stop us."

"I don't know either, but since there isn't anyone to stop us, this is the best chance for us to escape." Shijake pointed at the prisoners behind him. "They all have various abilities, and there are even some who know the geography of the Bell of Death Island. They can lead us out of here."

A skinny man then walked out and pointed at his head. "I once hacked into the top-secret database of the Six Nations and saw the blueprints of the Bell of Death Island. Even though it was only a few seconds, I have memorized about sixty to seventy percent of the information and can put it to good use now. Humph, this is also the reason I was caught.

"In any case, the Bell of Death Island isn't a small island in the seas, and its name is extremely misleading. Its true location is beneath a mountain range. The Six Nations made use of a natural underground cave to build this underground prison. There is a total of thirteen levels, and every level has a circular walkway with many cells along it. The exterior of the cell is covered with a thick layer of steel and cement, and even a nuclear missile would not be able to blow it up. Neither the top layer nor the bottommost layer is the exit, and the only exit is located on one of the middle levels. Furthermore, its location is extremely concealed, and the underground walkway is extremely long."

"Since everyone wants to escape from here, why not you work together with us?" Shijake suggested.

Tyne nodded and said, "What are your plans?"

"The prison guards have not reacted to the escape of prisoners from our level, and it is extremely likely that something special is holding them back. If the other prisoners have also broken out, it is extremely likely for them to go to the top level." Shijake revealed a cruel smile. "After being shut in for so many years, it is time to regain some interest from the prison guards."

Tyne frowned but did not say a word.

All of them took the elevator up to the top floor, and the moment the lift door opened up, a dense, bloody smell assaulted them. The lift was surrounded by the corpses of the prison guards. The old prison warden of the region was lying in the corner with his abdomen cut opened and all of his intestines pulled out. His intestines had tied up his neck, and he had actually been strangled to death in an extremely cruel manner.

However, Shijake and the others remained unfazed. There was not a single friendly character among the prisoners, and none of them were fazed by the cruel sight.

Another group of prisoners covered with blood were currently waiting for the lift. It was obvious that the situation before them was their handiwork.

"There are actually others who had escaped?" The other group of prisoners were being led by a man who was disfigured by a burn mark. Licking his lips, he sneered, "Hehe, you guys have missed out on the fun. Apart from us, no one else is still alive."

Shijake's eyes narrowed. He knew the origins of this disfigured man. This disfigured man was an extremely cruel Super who had committed many crimes that made one's hair stand on edge. Even he did not dare provoke the man before him for no good reason and thus said, "How about we work together? We know how to escape."

After thinking for a while, the disfigured man reluctantly replied, "Humph, alright."

The two groups quickly came to an agreement and began to sweep the prison level by level to clean up all the remaining prison guards and save the other prisoners.

The group of prisoners grew larger and larger, and their group already had a few hundred people. With all the prisoners being released, the entire prison was very quickly soaked with blood, and all the prison guards were extremely vulnerable before them.

Originally, the Bell of Death Island had many defensive mechanisms, and they even had a self-destruct switch to prevent the prisoners from escaping. However, when the prisoners arrived at the control room, they realized that the entire control room was a complete mess. The prison guards who were supposed to be keeping watch had broken out in a fight, and the dozen prison guards were all riddled with bullets with all of them perishing together.

No wonder no one had stopped them.

"Did all of these prison guards break out in internal conflict?"

All of them had a face full of doubt and felt as though they were dreaming.

After being locked up for so long, they had regained their freedom in such an odd manner.

Why would the prison guards fight each other?

This matter was filled with oddities!

Due to the lack of information, the prisoners did not know about the Mutation Disaster. It was only because many of the prison guards had suddenly broken out in illness that they had been able to escape so successfully. Regardless of how strong a castle was, it would be easily destroyed from within.

After getting rid of all the prison guards, the few hundred prisoners rested in the large hall of the elevator well. Only then did they have the time to size each other up.

Many of them had once been infamous criminals with their notoriety spreading all across the world. Many of them had heard about each other's fame and were wary of each other.

Not a single one of them could be easily provoked.

There were also a few new criminals who had been caught recently and thus were not recognized by the rest. The majority of the prisoners had been locked up in the Bell of Death Island for many years, with a decade or two being extremely common. They had been blocked off from the world for far too long and were not up to date on the changes in the outside world.

Tyne was one of these 'newbies', and no one knew of his origins.

Because they were all wary of each other, many of the hot-tempered prisoners had reined in their tempers. In this environment where the powerful reigned supreme, even the most arrogant criminals would lower their heads. After all, while they were cruel, they were not stupid and did not have any intention of creating trouble for themselves. They only wanted to escape from prison before going their own ways and never seeing each other again.

After fumbling around for a moment, the prisoners finally found the tunnel to escape. This was a man-made tunnel that cut through the entire mountain range.

After walking for about two hours with all the prisoners growing impatient, they finally saw the light at the end of the tunnel and could smell the fresh air of the outside world.

"We're out!"

All of them were overjoyed and sped up toward the exit of the tunnel.

They were currently at the edge of the mountain range, and the exit was an extremely insignificant looking cave. The surroundings of the cave were filled with thick vegetation, and the leaves rustled in the wind.

The sky was clear, and they felt the warmth of the sun shining down on them. The feeling of freedom filled their hearts, and many of them took in greedy breaths of air. They all felt as though they were reborn at that moment.

They had finally escaped after remaining in captivity for such a long time, and their suppressed anger and ambition exploded like a volcano. While they did not understand the changes in the world, many of the criminals were eager to revert to their old ways and cause chaos in the outside world.

Right at that moment, a foreign voice was heard.

"What a coincidence, meeting all of you right after my arrival. I thought that you would have escaped by now."

Han Xiao was leaning against a tree as he looked at the prisoners.

The prisoners immediately looked over with cautiousness as they sized Han Xiao up. They all felt that Han Xiao was extremely foreign, and the majority of them did not recognize him.

"Who are you?" the disfigured man growled.

"You can call me Black Phantom. That was my past alias." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Black Phantom?" the disfigured man sneered. "Humph, which hole did you jump out from? I've never heard of a character like you."

Bang!

A thick light flashed.

The next moment, everything above the neck of the disfigured man disappeared, and the headless corpse collapsed onto the ground.

Han Xiao gestured with his finger, and the Floating Cannon Array circulated around him like an obedient pet. When facing those vicious criminals, he did not feel like talking to them slowly.

"Have you heard of me now?"

Chapter 520: Bell of Death Island (2)

"What‽"

"Impossible!"

The dull thud of the headless corpse collapsing onto the ground was like a hammer on their hearts. All the prisoners present were in a state of complete shock!

This disfigured prisoner was a ferocious individual who had killed countless individuals before. He was extremely cruel, and his powerful strength made it such that all the other prisoners dared not provoke him along the way. He was a top expert on Planet Aquamarine. However, to think that he had actually been killed in the blink of an eye without even a chance to fight back!

All of them looked at Han Xiao with shock.

How could there be such a powerful person in the world‽

Upon witnessing this scene, Han Xiao frowned and said with disappointment, "That can't be right. Do none of you baldies know my name?"

Your name... Black Phantom?

All of the prisoners stared at each other in silence. They had been locked up in prison for too long and truly had not heard of this name before. The prison guards definitely would not reveal any news about the outside to them, and only a small number of prisoners who had been locked up recently had experienced the destruction of the Germinal Organization.

Tyne came out from the crowd and said with a solemn tone, "Black Phantom, real name Han Xiao. A traitor of Germinal Organization and also the key reason behind the Germinal Organization's destruction. You are the most famous individual who incited war in the past five years and also the person who created the situation of peace in the Six Nations. Furthermore, your strength is above that of all the famed warriors, and you are at the peak of Planet Aquamarine. Your strength is above the three traditional realms, and your strength represents the fourth realm!"

He knew about Han Xiao. However, his knowledge was limited to the news before Han Xiao left the planet.

"At least there is someone with eyes..." Han Xiao then turned around, but before he could say a word, a gasp of shock sounded.

"What‽ Germinal Organization has been destroyed‽"

Shijake had a look of disbelief.

He was an Executive Officer of the Germinal Organization who had been imprisoned for eleven years and one of the leader's right-hand men. Before he was caught, Germinal Organization had still been at the peak of its strength, and he had always believed that the leader would lead Germinal Organization to completing their goal. However, he never could have imagined that after being locked up for over ten years and finally regaining his freedom, he would hear about the Germinal Organization being destroyed.

Not just him, there were a couple of other prisoners who were extremely shocked.

My goodness, just what happened while we were locked up‽

"Since someone knows me, I shall not bother wasting my breath." Han Xiao was gratified. His gaze then swept past the prisoners before him, and he found many familiar faces.

In Han Xiao's previous life, Shijake had returned to Germinal Organization after his escape, which had not been decimated by a nuclear bomb in that timeline. He had created a great deal of trouble during the Mutation Disaster, and in order to fight against Godora, which the Six Nations leaned toward, he had stood on the side of DarkStar.

With Germinal Organization being destroyed, it did not only affect the storyline of Version 1.0 but also affected Version 2.0. Originally, the players in the Germinal Organization had been granted a channel to enter the galaxy, but this path had been cut off by Han Xiao. There was no Germinal Organization camp anymore, and DarkStar had also lost the cannon fodder that they should have had.

Tyne was an important character in the Mutation Disaster of Version 2.0. He had been the first to find the Mutation Source in Han Xiao's previous life and had been possessed by the mutation source. Because he shared the intense desire that the Mutation Source had for energy, he had not been able to control himself and sucked up energy from wherever he could. This had resulted in the Mutation Source growing rapidly and speeding up the progress of the Mutation Disaster. He had been a large enemy of the players and the main antagonist.

The Mutation Source had a great desire for energy, and while it could move around on its own, its movement speed was too slow. Thus, it would possess a human body to gain a tool to harvest energy. While the Mutation Source was capable of affecting an individual's actions through hormones, it was not able to control the thoughts and actions of an infected individual. Thus, the Mutation Source was not able to make use of the infected individuals to transfer a large amount of energy over to it.

Apart from the two of them, the other prisoners had also set off storms in Planet Aquamarine and become new targets for the players exterminate.

Han Xiao had gone to Bell of Death Island early just so that he could get rid of this wildcard to ensure that his plans would not be affected. Hiring them was only something that he was doing in passing. The strength of Planet Aquamarine's Supers could no longer keep up with him, and only a couple of prisoners who had some special traits were worth anything to him. Just like Emerald Grass.

According to his understanding of the prisoners in Bell of Death Island, they were an unruly and untamable bunch, so he did not plan to subdue them with reason. After arriving, Han Xiao had used a large life force radar to scan the place and noticed a large number of living beings moving underground. As such, he had decided to wait at the entrance and catch all the prisoners in one fell swoop. The anti-surveillance device of the Six Nations was full of loopholes and like a weak sheet of paper before his equipment.

"What are your motives?"

The prisoners displayed looks of wariness.

"Don't talk so much cr*p. A calamity is sweeping over Planet Aquamarine, and every talent is extremely important. I found out the location of the prison from the Six Nations, and I am here to give all of you a chance to redeem yourselves and contribute to society."

"Impossible! The Six Nations would never reveal the location of this secret prison!" someone cried out.

Han Xiao raised his brows and added, "Oh, the Six Nations are now under my command."

Everyone was speechless.

How could the Six Nations listen to an individual's commands? This fellow was definitely trying to scare them. Even if he wanted to brag, he should be more realistic in his bragging. Did he think that they were idiots?

"Who cares about you? This daddy here isn't interested at all!"

"I am not requesting for aid." Han Xiao stretched his arms and said emotionlessly, "Taking into account all of your destructive capabilities, in order to prevent the situation from becoming worse, I will not allow those who reject me to leave alive. Thus, you either submit or die."

"Hehehe... what a braggart. What a frightening threat. However, I am not afraid of you."

At this moment, a man with a spider tattoo walked out from the crowd without a trace on fear on his face. "Kill me if you have the ability."

The eyes of the other prisoners lit up. This fellow was Black Spider, who was extremely famous for being difficult to deal with. He has a type of doppelganger Esper ability, and the moment he was killed, he would be revived in a doppelganger hidden somewhere else.

Black Spider had always felt that he had an undying body, so he was extremely arrogant and unafraid of danger.

"It's you." Han Xiao nodded. He had dealt with Black Spider before, and this fellow had been sent to Bell of Death Island because of him.

Without waiting for Black Spider to continue acting arrogantly, Han Xiao used his Hila Character Summon Card straight away and launched a mental attack without saying a word.

Black Spider's body shook, and blood oozed out from his mouth and nose. Collapsing on the ground, he raised his head with great difficulty and said with a malevolent smile, "Hehe, I am an undying being. Just you wait. I will find you again one day, and I will be your eternal nightmare!"

The next moment, he took his last breath and passed away on the spot with a malevolent smile on his face.

Black Spider was not afraid of physical death as his living state was a ball of mental energy. As such, mental attacks were his Achilles heel. In Han Xiao's previous life, he had died by Hila's hand, and today, he died due to Hila's abilities again.

Black Spider did not know that he was truly dead this time.

Even at the point of his death, he had thought that he would still wake up but did not know that his consciousness had already fallen into darkness. It was impossible for him to open his eyes again.

"This is the first time I've heard such a request. I destroyed his soul, so he won't be able to revive again." Han Xiao shrugged.

Huuu!

Before waiting for the prisoners to react, Han Xiao shot out a couple of compressed orbs, and they opened up into a large silver mechanical palm that was seven to eight meters big.

[G75-Type Claws], a blueprint of the Mechanic Class. A large mechanical arm like this was very commonly used, and it was controlled through the nerves, thus allowing the user to operate it as though it was his own limb. There were many different models, and they all had different configurations. Boosted by a Mechanic's Mechanical Force, the stats and the might of the claw were not to be underestimated. Apart from being used as a combat ability, it could also be used as a large assistant tool. If a mechanic wanted to build a spaceship, his own two hands would be far too inefficient, and the aid of such machines would be extremely important.

In the past year, Han Xiao had been left with more than enough time to forge equipment and had prepared a large stock of equipment.

The bottom of the mechanical claw suddenly spewed out flames, and it flew out more than a hundred meters before slamming down on an empty plot of land like a palm descending from the heavens.

Boom!

The earth trembled, and a thick layer of soil and dust was kicked up into the air. A crater in the shape of a palm could also be seen in the ground with cracks expanding out in all directions like a spider web.

The mechanical hand then grabbed a large handful of soil and threw it in front of the prisoners. Apart from the sound of the soil falling onto the ground, a large thud of a heavy object landing could be heard with the smell of blood assaulting their noses. While the prisoners could not see anything apart from the soil, all their faces blanched.

They knew that there was an invisible fellow in their group—the Invisible Demon!

"You can't escape from my eyes even if you are invisible." Han Xiao controlled the mechanical arm to float above his head. "Don't even think about trying your luck."

Han Xiao had already spotted the presence of the Invisible Demon, which he had not expected to find. The Invisible Demon had fought Han Xiao before and was extremely wary of Han Xiao. Thus, he had planned to make use of the opportunity when Han Xiao's attention was fixed on the prisoners to discreetly leave. However, he had ended up being crushed by a mechanical palm instead.

With Han Xiao's current strength, getting rid of the Invisible Demon was as easy as swatting a fly.

It would not be an exaggeration to say that he was able to wipe out the entire Planet Aquamarine with the strength of a single person!

Those powerful criminals in the eyes of ordinary folks were no more than third rate galactic wanderers in his eyes.

"Alright, alright. Hurry up and give me an answer. My time is very precious."

Han Xiao snapped his fingers. The Floating Cannon Array instantly surrounded the prisoners, and the fingers on the mechanical claw turned into five large barrels, accumulating energy for an attack.

The prisoners had unreconciled looks on their faces. After finally managing to escape, they had actually met someone powerful enough to send them into despair. They had just come out from the wolf's den but entered into the tiger's cave the next moment. With Black Phantom's strength, even if all of them attacked together, they would surely be wiped out.

The situation was not within their control, and the prisoners had no choice but to swallow their anger and submit. However, not a single one of them willingly submitted, and they were all planning their next move.

Pretend to submit to him and escape when we have the chance. Many prisoners had such a thought.

After doing a headcount, Han Xiao said, "The number of fatalities is fewer than I imagined. Looks like all of you know what the right decision to make is. Follow me back to the Sanctuary. Board the ship."

Board the ship? What ship? Shouldn't we be taking a plane?

The crowd was stunned.

Hum!

The sky then began contorting, and a gigantic spaceship appeared in the clear sky. Han Xiao had arrived there on a spaceship, but it had been in stealth mode. The stealth mode had just been deactivated, and thus, the prisoners were only able to see the gigantic spaceship at that moment. It was akin to a castle floating in space!

The jaws of all the prisoners dropped, and they fell into a daze.

My goodness, the ship that you were referring to is a spaceship‽

While they knew that Han Xiao was extremely powerful, because of their lack of information and preconceived notions, they had thought that Han Xiao was still a member of Planet Aquamarine and had never considered the galaxy. At that moment, the appearance of this spaceship had shattered their world view and was completely out of their expectations!

They originally did not believe that the Six Nations would submit to Han Xiao, but upon witnessing the scene before them, that belief wavered.

All the prisoners no longer had any thoughts of escaping as they boarded the spaceship with bitter expressions. In front of Han Xiao, the ferocious criminals had become docile sheep.

When the final prisoner walked up to Han Xiao's side, he suddenly stopped by the hatch of the spaceship and looked at Han Xiao with hesitation. "Do you remember me?"

Han Xiao paused for a moment and studied the prisoner before him carefully before gasping. "Hannes‽"

"That's right." Hannes laughed bitterly.

"What are you doing here? Bennett and I thought you went missing!" Han Xiao had a face full of shock. He had a hidden mission that had been issued by Hannes called [New Era—Origin], and his job was to dig out the secret behind Planet Aquamarine's history.

Before Han Xiao left Planet Aquamarine, he had reached the third phase of the mission. However, because of Hannes' sudden disappearance, there had been no subsequent clue. Since the mission had not failed, Han Xiao had a feeling that Hannes was still alive.

Hannes being locked up in the Bell of Death Island was completely out of Han Xiao's expectations.

"It's a long story." Hannes shook his head helplessly. "I found a shocking secret, and this secret brought me into grave danger. The others are dead, and I am the only one alive."

Han Xiao frowned and guessed, "Since you were locked up in the Bell of Death Island, is the culprit the Six Nations? You found a secret that they wanted to hide?"

"No." Hannes shook his head. "While the Six Nations did catch me, I was on the verge of death at that time. They saved my life instead."

"So, why are you locked up?"

Hannes laughed bitterly. "Perhaps it is because of a dead Godoran beside me."

"What‽" Han Xiao was stunned. "Why would you meet a Godoran?"

"Sigh, let's talk on the ship. You already have a spaceship now, and you are truly different from before. Perhaps only you will be able to make use of the clue that I found..."

Hannes clenched his fists with a suppressed fury in his voice.

"My guess is, there is indeed a mastermind behind the war riddled state of Planet Aquamarine, and Godora is the source of the war!"

Chapter 521: Tracing Back to Origins, One Final Link

Bell of Death Island was on another continent, and it would take about an hour to return to the Sanctuary. While a spaceship had to limit its speed within the atmosphere of a planet, it was still much faster than an airplane.

After Han Xiao settled all the little b*stards of Bell of Death Island into a guest room, he found Hannes and continued the previous conversation.

Hannes began to narrate what had happened after he went missing. After the end of the Germinal Organization battle, he had led the groups of archaeologists on a journey to seek out new secrets. Because Han Xiao had let the players complete a large number of missions, Hannes had managed to receive a fair amount of new information. He had then found a suspicious point in the large sea of record scrolls, and the evidence had actually pointed to the battle of a hundred nations on Planet Aquamarine.

In the past, Planet Aquamarine had housed over a hundred nations, and while there had been small skirmishes, they had been largely peaceful. They had all been curious about the universe, and Godora's appearance had brought about news of the universe. Knowing that the large number of nations on the planet would only slow down the development of the civilization and waste a great deal of resources, the state of the planet had begun to shift.

All the nations had taken a different stance, but none of them had been willing to give up their authority. Even if they knew that choosing to do so would result in a tragic future, before the tragedy truly arrived, they had all chosen to be short sighted. In the end, the friction between the nations had grown, and war had become the only way out.

As such, this theory had caused a world war to break out, and many nations had been eradicated in the war. Finally, only Six Nations had been left behind, and they had all begun to reorganize the resources of the entire planet. However, the negative effects of the war still had not worn off.

Hannes did not think that a single theory would result in a war between over a hundred nations. He was very certain that there must have been someone controlling the situation from behind the scenes. After much searching, he had finally made new progress in his search, but it had also resulted in a tragedy.

"The evidence led us to an underground cave in the Somar Desert. There was a large golden statue in the cave, and you will never believe what I saw. That golden statue actually began moving and launched attacks on us. Its strength was unrivaled, and our attacks weren't able to harm it in the slightest."

"And then?" Han Xiao asked.

"We fought a long battle with the statue, but it was indestructible and could even shoot lasers. My comrades all died in battle. The war didn't reap their lives, but they actually died there..."

Hannes grit his teeth and continued, "I was also severely injured and thought that my death was certain. However, the statue suddenly stopped, and the entire cave suddenly turned golden. Only then did I find out that the rocky walls of the cave were actually a disguise. On the golden wall was an oval shaped container the size of a human being. A Godoran then walked out from the container and squatting in front of me. He asked how I found the place."

"Continue, I'm listening."

"At that time, my breathing was weak, and thus, the other party was extremely close to me. I acted as though I was severely injured and tried to communicate with him. I asked him who he was and why a Godoran would be left behind on Planet Aquamarine. However, he seemed to disdain giving me an answer and wanted to stand up and leave. The statue then moved again, and it was about to raise its arms up to smash me to death.

"I didn't have a choice. I could only take a chance and attack with all of my strength. However, I never expected that the Godoran would not dodge my attack and was killed by a single fist. He was actually an ordinary person. After he died, the statue stopped moving, and I fainted from my injuries.

"After who knows how long, a special agent squad arrived at the cave and found me on the verge of death. They seemed to have found the cave by following my tracks, and everything inside the cave was seized by them. Because the matter involved Godora, I was sent to Bell of Death Island for interrogation."

"Why do you think that Godora is the one behind the scenes with just this information?"

"It isn't a wild guess, of course. Prison is the best place to think, and I have been connecting the dots in my mind. Furthermore, there must be a reason for a Godoran staying behind on Planet Aquamarine. I suspect that while Godora isn't interfering with Planet Aquamarine on the surface, they have always been monitoring us and interrupting the progress of our civilization. While I do not understand Godora, I know that only benefits are absolute, and they definitely have some reasons to do so."

"It may not be as you think. A single person cannot represent an entire civilization. Besides, Godora also have another golden skinned enemy force," Han Xiao said after pondering for a moment. "I have a pretty good relationship with Godora, and I may be able to find some people to investigate this matter. Can you give me any clues?"

"I remember the appearance of that Godoran and everything in the cave." Hannes took out a few pieces of paper and began drawing.

The appearance of the Godoran was very clear, and Han Xiao took a picture of it with his communicator. With his relationship with Godora, it was extremely simple for him to ask them to check on a portrait.

He then looked at Hannes' sketch of the statue. It was the shape of a humans but had four arms and no facial features. Instead, it had two lines of three holes where one's eyes would be, which were glowing with a golden light.

Upon seeing the drawing, Han Xiao let out a gasp.

"This is a type of Mojo Puppet, a product of Godora's mages. It is easily purchased, but the price to forge it is pretty expensive. If you aren't a mage, you can only destroy the puppet by smashing the statue. With your strength, it would be extremely difficult for you to smash a combat machine of the galactic level. This Mojo Puppet should be the Godoran's guard, and the place where the Godoran was staying should be a life sustaining chamber. It is likely that the chamber was connected to the web. If I have time, I will ask the Six Nations if I can study that item."

Hannes grabbed onto Han Xiao's hands and pleaded, "This is the only clue, and it will only be of use in your hands. I can only count on you. I no longer have anything to repay you with and can only hope that you will help me based on our old friendship. I really want to get to the bottom of this mystery and find out who is the source of the calamity!"

A notification popped up on Han Xiao's interface indicating that the third phase of [New Era—Origin] was completed. The mission gave him a few million experience points, and he successfully entered into the next phase. The interface also showed that this was the last phase of the mission, and there was only a single mission requirement, which was to find the truth. However, the only clue that they had was the Godoran's portrait.

No wonder this is a hidden Grade A mission. It's linked to two different versions, and one would have to be on friendly terms with Godora to follow up on this clue. Thus, this mission can only be continued in Version 2.0. Han Xiao's eyes glowed.

The reward was naturally plentiful, giving him a few million experience points. However, the Great Mechanic Han had the large market of the players and needed experience the least.

Apart from experience, there were a few Free Attribute Points, Potential Points, a chance for a Random Reward, and a unique Medal of Honor, which only Grade A missions had. This item was able to strengthen all of his attributes. Because he had handed this mission over to his contract workers who would work without complaints, all the mission requirements of every phase had been completed. His mission evaluation would definitely be very high, and he would definitely be able to get the Medal of Honor.

This would be his second Medal of Honor.

Han Xiao began planning his next move in his heart. If the one who started the war in Planet Aquamarine was truly Godora, information of this individual would definitely be top secret. Recklessly trying to fish for information would only alert Godora.

"I should just wait for the Godoran troops to reach Planet Aquamarine before planning my next step. The one leading the team should be Nagakin, and it will be much easier to talk to someone I know."

Han Xiao shook his head and was not too bothered by the outcome. After all, the struggles of a civilization were not right or wrong. It was only a matter of interests.

Even if Godora was truly the one behind the scenes, the current Planet Aquamarine still required Godora to save them. With so many lives at stake, being hard headed was not the solution to things, and it was best to be flexible.

Compared to harping on about the past, he was more interested in the food before him. Just like how a person ignored the source of their food when eating. Just like how growing crops required feces as fertilizer and pigs ate swill. When drinking milk, no one would bother thinking about what the person who discovered milk had been trying to do.

When marrying a wife, unless you were extremely lucky, you would have to selectively ignore the fact that your wife might have been your best friend's ex...

Thus, the way Han Xiao saw it, regardless of what the truth was, the most important thing was the value of its creation.

After returning to the Sanctuary, Han Xiao got the mercenaries to watch over the prisoners from the Bell of Death Island. While those unruly prisoners had been caught by him, they still had to be properly trained before they could be used. Han Xiao felt extremely at ease to hand them over to the mercenaries.

While those prisoners all looked extremely arrogant and haughty, compared to the galactic mercenaries who had traveled through various Star Systems and killed countless different species, they were no different from tame sheep.

In the following ten days, Han Xiao gradually set his plan into motion. The mages under him largely increased the yield of the suppressant, and the suppressant was handed out in large quantities to the refugees of the Sanctuary, thus stabilizing the situation.

At the same time, even more refugees flooded to the Sanctuary, and the entire Sanctuary was extremely crowded. As such, Bennett began to expand the Sanctuary, and with the aid of the players, the construction proceeded smoothly.

The refugees flooded over without stopping, and if things proceeded at that rate, the Sanctuary would probably have to be expanded into the size of a gigantic city.

Han Xiao did not forget about the Six Nations. Since the Six Nations had agreed to his conditions, he sent some mercenaries together with some raw materials to the capital of the Six Nations. All the citizens of the Six Nations who were not aware of the situation fell into a daze.

Some of the mercenaries stayed behind in the Six Nations to aid them in producing the suppressant, and the experienced Six Nations also advertised the news of the suppressant greatly to stabilize the hearts of their citizens.

The Six Nations naturally would not only pay lip service to Han Xiao, and Han Xiao had the authority to mobilize all of their military forces. Han Xiao only needed to say the word, and he would be able to control all these things. However, there was no need for him to do so. It would be best that he left those armies to the Six Nations so that they can help share some pressure with the Sanctuary.

The Sanctuary and the Six Nations already had some experience in fighting the Mutation Disaster, but the number of refugees that they were able to save was a small fraction of the entire planet. However, they were not able to take care of the beasts and plants in the wilderness, and the most frightening thing would be the underwater sea creatures. Their numbers were a couple of times greater than that of the land creatures, and they were also affected by the Mutation Disaster. There were even some amphibious beasts who came onto land and destroyed a few cities near the sea.

In places where they could not see, the situation of the Mutation Disaster was still extremely terrible and was getting worse by the second.

The majority of Planet Aquamarine's players were currently in the Sanctuary, and this was actually not beneficial to the big picture. However, this was extremely beneficial to Han Xiao as he was able to harvest a large amount of experience. Through the Black Star selection process, he had hired a full thirty to forty thousand players as well.

The selection trial had already become a daily activity for the players, and it was fervently discussed on the forums. The players shared their experience on the forums and came to a conclusion. A valiant warrior was no more than a shooting star quickly fading off into the night sky. Only by choosing a sneaky path would they be able to lead an eternal life.

Because it was a group-based selection trial, the players gradually began to form groups. Casual players tried their luck while professional players flaunted their skills. The core members of the large guilds would usually be protected by a thick layer of players on the outside.

All those who had not been able to pass the thirty second trials would not miss this chance again. Every time they saw Frenzied Sword, Hao Tian, and the others walking around the city with their bodies clad in high quality armor, all the other players could not help but be filled with envy. There were even a few who wanted to try their luck and see if killing them would cause the equipment to fall out of their inventories.

With the cooperation of other players, the success rate of the players increased significantly. The players still thought that it was because they had found the trick to the trials, and Han Xiao truly loved it when the players thought this way.

Han Xiao had prepared for a long time, and everything was currently going according to his plan. However, there was a scene that he had not expected.

The players had actually learned how to play Wayne Cards from Herlous, and many of them were actually addicted!

After hearing about this matter, Han Xiao almost had the urge to strangle Herlous to death! All he did was play cards every day and lead the excellent players astray!

How incorrigible!

Chapter 522: New Combat Mode (1)

After joining the mercenary group, the players took the initiative to interact with the various activities that the mercenary officers were involved in. Mercenaries were also a resource for them, and the good-looking ones such as Aroshia, Feidin, and Sylvia were swarmed by the players like bees to flowers, making them uncomfortable as they were not used to the enthusiasm of players.

However, toward their 'new companions', the mercenaries felt a little impatient.

Some of the players were attracted to the Wayne Card game that Herlous played and immediately grew addicted to it. The Wayne Card game was full of charm, with each card possessing simple enchantments on it. When played, they would display various effects, which was not only interesting but also a display of the influence of characters present in the universe. All of this made the players extremely interested in the galaxy.

To think that playing a card game could actually boost their knowledge!

With the presence of the forums, anything novel would always catch the attention of the players. There were stickied posts about the various playstyles of the Wayne Card game as well as introductions, attracting the curiosity of players from all over the world

To be able to play a mini-game within a game, this was equivalent to adding two happy matters together, double happiness!

In his past life, the Wayne Card game had also been popular among the players. Right now, having been introduced to this card game in advance, the trend of the Wayne Card game was thus brought forward.

The Shattered Star Ring deck, which Herlous proudly showed the players, was also photographed and uploaded. The cards were all famous characters of the Shattered Star Ring. While the majority still went unrecognized by the players, there were a few that they knew, such as Dragon Emperor Ames. More than a few still remembered the long, white legs that filled up their entire sight.

One player even discovered the card of Black Star and was stunned silly. He did not expect Han Xiao to be a part of the deck as well!

To be made into a card, this was naturally a symbol of status. Was this not saying that Black Star had some fame within the Shattered Star Ring?

The players could not help but feel a pleasant surprise. The stronger their faction was, the happier the incoming players would be!

However, all this caused Han Xiao to feel extremely helpless. To him, the players were capable of generating value for him every minute, and for them to spend their limited time and energy on playing cards, was this not reducing his income?

Diligence pays off, while leisure serves no purpose, men!

A great man once said that there was no problem that could not be solved through playing cards. If it existed, then just play another round!

Hearing the players' laughter and joy, Han Xiao could not restrain them. He could only silently bear with the heartache. This was because his overall goal was to attract all the players to his camp, so the strength of the players would be equivalent to the strength of his influence.

After agonizing over it for the whole day, Han Xiao thought of a new idea.

"Since the players love to play card games, I should just take the opportunity to organize a playing card competition and put up prizes and such. Such a large-scale collective leisure activity could also enhance the players sense of belonging to the camp..."

Han Xiao felt that this idea was plausible. This way, it would not cause any trouble to the players who fell in love with playing cards earlier than usual.

However, even if he wished to hold such an event, this was not the appropriate time. He had to at least wait till he led the players into the interstellar base. At that time, he could also take the chance to sell a bunch of card decks to the players.

...

Version 2.0 had already been out for more than ten days. The players were slowly adapting to it, moving back on the right track. The previous version's level limit was up to sixty, the watershed before the first Race Evolution. Now that the upper limit of the level in the game had been lifted, the players started to complete their advancement, which lead to many feeling surprised at the effects.

This topic quickly spread across the entire forums, causing the entire planet to boil.

The players started to pick apart the details behind the Race Evolution. This had been the same in his past lifetime, so Han Xiao did not bother paying any attention to it. He went to look for his officers, with the intention of learning a new Energy Training Technique.

The Energy Training Technique was nothing unique, with the majority of it being general skills without any restriction in occupation. After going around asking once, Herlous favorability toward him was high enough to simply give him a new technique without any additional conditions.

Sunil Energy Training Technique: Foundation technique in training energy for Sunils.

Overall Effect: +20 Energy

0/100 Cycles. Each cycle depends on STR, DEX, or END (Select highest attribute). Every cycle will exhaust 50,000 experience and 1,500 stamina.

Han Xiao was currently not lacking in experience, and his stamina recovery rate was also high. Within the span of two to three days, he finished learning this technique. Each cycle would add 3 Energy, for a total of 320 Energy. However, he was still a few hundred short of his target of 9,000 Energy, so he had to learn another technique.

The more of such Energy Training Techniques one learned, the more the consumption of experience would increase. However, with Han Xiao's current experience reserves, he was not worried about such an issue.

Harmon also promised to share an Energy Training Technique with him, but he had a request, which was to go all out to fight him, and he would only obtain the technique if Han Xiao defeated him. This madman was a main character build but also an addict for combat. In order to form a War League and temper himself, he would not give up on any opportunity.

Han Xiao was helpless about it. When he first recruited Harmon, they had exchanged blows. His own abilities were at the top of the list for the Grade B Supers, and he would not shirk away from a fight from anyone of the same grade as him.

The duo went to the training room within the spaceship.

They deliberately avoided the players for this battle as Han Xiao did not wish to display his abilities so early in the game. Furthermore, at their level, the arena would be too weak to withstand their blows. It would be too troublesome if they needed to repair the place after their battle.

However, Han Xiao still had certain plans. He called the mercenaries to bring all the prisoners over so as to allow them to feel the combat capability of the interstellar mercenaries.

Hannes was not included within the prisoners as Han Xiao had already given him his freedom, allowing him to stay in the Sanctuary. When Bennett saw his missing friend, he had received a good shock, and after learning about Hannes hypothesis, his mood had also grown heavy. However, Han Xiao was not bothered by it.

"Come whenever you're ready." Han Xiao nodded as he spoke toward Harmon.

Bang!

Babbling was not Harmon's style. One only saw his muscles swelling exponentially, his body shape becoming several times larger than Han Xiao. With a burst from his legs, he shot forward like a cannonball, hefting up his axe and hacking straight at Han Xiao.

Ka ka ka!

Two giant mechanical hands rapidly unfolded on top of Han Xiao's head, seizing the axe. Flames burst out to propel the hands forward as they begun a wrestling battle with Harmon, pitting strength against strength. A wave of air billowed out from their point of contact, knocking all the prisoners surrounding them away.

The group of prisoners could not even withstand the aftereffects of their collision. They crawled up, bedraggled, all of them wearing expressions of surprise on their faces.

While they had seen Han Xiao act before, their strength had been insufficient for them to comprehend the actual battle strength Han Xiao had. Standing by the side and watching the battle, they finally understood that, in front of these interstellar mercenaries, they were as good as commoners.

Han Xiao's hands shook, and another two mechanical hands unfolded beside him, striking out.

Boom! Boom!

With two heavy blows, Harmon was sent flying. His legs hit the ground with a loud thud, and the metal flooring was actually dented by him.

The four mechanical hands pursued triumphantly, continuously sending out blows. The force unleashed by the machinery was in no way light, and Harmon could not evade in time, only able to use his tomahawk to directly withstand it. The tomahawk constantly clashed against the metal hands, the resulting sound deafening.

Clank!

The metallic clashes echoed continuously in the room.

Han Xiao remained in his original spot, without even bothering to don his armor. In the past year, he had improved on his fighting style, adding a few new elite machinery systems. He no longer needed to employ third-rate tactics such as the Army Style, for he had many more means to deal with people his level.

For example, this enhanced melee tactic originated from the combination of High-End Knowledge [Huge Duplex Machinery Technology] and the Advanced Knowledge [Heavy Machine Modification]. With the giant mechanical hands as the core of this system, in addition to melee battles, they could also be equipped with other weapons, combining attack and defense.

The material used for the [G75-Type Claws] was the strongest alloy that Han Xiao could currently produce—his current material crafting was still stuck at the Advanced Knowledge [Advanced Material Synthesis], as he did not manage to learn the High-End Knowledge of material studies.

The four giant mechanical hands suddenly disintegrated, the various parts akin to butterflies weaving around flowers as they scattered. This caused Harmon to cleave down on empty space, resulting in a flaw in his defense. At that moment, the parts once again reformed, and the four palms combined together from front to back, forming a circle that trapped Harmon in the center. Only his head remained exposed.

The mechanical fingers of each hand tightened, gripping Harmon's body and restricting his movements.

Hum!

The four palms simultaneously released a sonic blast, causing even the ground to shake. One could see with their own eyes the surrounding air distort, and the shock wave radiated outward in the limited space of the training room.

While the prisoners had attempted to retreat, they were still caught up in the aftermath. The pressure of the shockwave forced all of them up against the walls, much like human paintings. The skin of everyone present undulated, like ripples on a water surface, and all their expressions looked more distorted than someone in the process of diving.

A string of damage values popped up from above Harmon's head. Because the shock wave penetrated directly into his body, Harmon's rigid muscles immediately loosened in shock, and he entered a temporary [Weakened] status

Taking advantage of this opportunity, Han Xiao jumped forward, giving a vicious kick toward Harmon's head. Numerous mechanical parts expanded in an instant around his leg, unfolding into a black mechanical foot. It viciously stomped on Harmon's face with a dull thud.

This foot landed hard, and the huge force behind the leg caused the metal flooring below Harmon's feet to distort and warp into a concave shape.

Not waiting for Harmon to be free of his negative status, the components within the mechanical leg once again let out clanking sounds as the mechanical parts came to life. The alloy casing at the bottom of the mechanical leg opened, revealing a huge cannon nozzle, completely plastered on the face of Harmon. An eye piercing glow lit up from within the cannon.

Boom!

Harmon ate a light ray cannon shot right in his face!

The duo violently ricocheted off each other, and a bulky body emitting black smoke plumes bounced heavily on the floor whilst Han Xiao landed gracefully. The mechanical hands and feet disintegrated at the same time, turning into tiny components before regathering together as a compressed orb, returning back to its original position.

This set of combo moves was a common form of combat that Han Xiao currently favored.

Xiu!

Suddenly, Harmon threw out his tomahawk while he was still tumbling. The ax spun, bringing with it a sharp whistling noise.

Han Xiao did not budge, instead the halo array deployed behind him, spraying out motes of light to form a golden light shield in front of him. The ax head violently slammed into the shield, leaving behind a large crack. Another 10 cm, and the blade would have touched Han Xiao's forehead!

After prying out the tomahawk, Han Xiao turned over to look. Harmon had just stood up, and although he had suffered from a series of blows, with black patches all around his body, he was still as ferocious as ever, bringing out a war hammer next.

"Heh, how exciting!" Harmon wiped the corners of his mouth. His tone was rough, panting, but full of fighting spirit.

"How tough can you get?" Han Xiao was helpless against him. Harmon was an organism with a single brain cell, only knowing how to solve problems using his fists. He was unlike Herlous who knew when to retreat. Instead, one had to knock him out to end the battle.

While both were proficient in close combat, Herlous could serve as a damage dealer and meat shield, while Harmon was an MT[1] through and through, extremely fleshy!

Han Xiao could see Harmon's attribute panel, which showed two overpowered specialties. There was [War God's Tenacity], whose effect was that every time Harmon's HP fell below twenty percent, there would be a chance for him to recover his HP back to fifty. The other was [Desperate Straits], where he would obtain a +2 Buff to his Strength, Dexterity, and Endurance attributes for every one percent of HP lost. In a battle, there was no cap to the limit obtained.

In theory, if Harmon was lucky, his strength could be improved infinitely—and with his Luck Glow, it was as good as him being the darling of the Fortune Goddess. These two specialties that he possessed were akin to a 'Last Stand' plus 'Bloodbath Berserk'. Thus, there was actually a high probability for the 'theory' to become reality.

This was a true genius made for battle!

As for Harmon's shortcoming, it was that all his attacks were toward a single target, without any long-range attacks. He was not a Pugilist, so he had no way to utilize the Shockwave Blast skill. He was a purebred warrior!

[1] MT is a gaming term for Main Tanks, the thicc-est guy in the team. Back

Chapter 523: New Combat Mode (2)

Initially, when Han Xiao discovered traces of Harmon, he had been overjoyed, immediately going over to recruit him without hesitation. Harmon followed the tribal traditions and was a pure warrior without any guile, strictly keeping to his promises. Or, one could say that his brain was packed only with muscles. In terms of difficulty for recruiting, he would probably be rated as one star.

Harmon had just left his mother planet and needed to form a War League of his own. Thus, the strength that Han Xiao displayed was enough to win the approval of Harmon, and they agreed to a cooperation. He would join the War League whilst Harmon would join his mercenary group. A mercenary would have sufficient opportunities to exercise his muscles, and this was also what Harmon needed.

As such, Harmon could not strictly be considered as one of Han Xiao's officers but rather an ally on level ground.

Han Xiao had researched the main character model archetype. Other than the standard luck glow, a main character would more or less have some form of commonality. For example, some characters would have the ability to prolong the plotline and events, caused by their personality and ideas. Some could do so purely out of their own strength and ability, and Harmon was precisely one of those latter characters.

The Luhan Beastmen believed in the way of the warrior. In the collapsed tribes where Harmon used to reside in, he had long been renowned as the 'Roaring Beast'. This was a form of extreme praise from the Luhan Beastmen toward Harmon. Harmon was one of the favorites competing for the seat of the Chief, a protagonist who was strong from the very beginning.

Han Xiao's relationship with him was currently neither warm nor cold. Because Harmon was someone who maintained the old tradition of a War League, he was not stingy with fighting for Han Xiao. A true warrior would never go back on his word.

Of all the officers in his mercenary group, Harmon had challenged every single one of them, and they were aware that the longer the battle dragged on, the stronger he got. It was as though he was an unkillable cockroach. None of Han Xiao's officers had managed to defeat him, save Aroshia, whom Harmon could not damage due to her pure energy body. This was also his weakness.

Han Xiao was not interested in pitting his endurance against Harmon's—he would rather end the battle as fast as possible.

"Roar!"

Harmon let out a snort, his powerful lung capacity causing the surrounding air to vibrate as he charged forward again, this time holding onto the war hammer. His every step caused the metal flooring to groan in protest as he drew close at the quickest possible speed.

Clank!

Facing his charge, Han Xiao remained unmoved. Two compressed orbs dropped from his sleeves, and the moment that they landed on the ground, a ray of light was seen as they transformed into two mechanical humanoids warriors, solemnly flanking Han Xiao on both sides.

The mechanical warriors were coated in an alloy shell that gleamed bright yellow, white, and black. Their four limbs were designed with the likeness of humans in mind, their height around two meters. The armor was not overly swollen, but it could not be considered elegant and light. The helmet had two wings on the sides of the visor as decoration, whereas their backs had two slots that looked like they could be fitted with wings. Both hands had four fingers, and from the outside, it was unknown as to what weapons they possessed.

At the same time, Harmon had already arrived before Han Xiao. With a ferocious twist of his waist, the war hammer that was as long as a door grew a fast curve as it swept across. The force behind this was much larger than before, generating a howling gale!

Hu!

Even before the hammer landed, the wind caused Han Xiao to be unable to open his eyes!

This hammer strike was obviously done with the intention to blow both Han Xiao and his robots away. If hit by this, Han Xiao estimated that it would trigger a suppressed state for him, where he would experience a short period of dizziness. After all, Strength was not his strongest stat, and even if his HP was especially large, it would not be a good feeling.

However, Han Xiao showed no sign of panic, a gleam instead shimmering within his eyes.

"Phillip, load the data."

Hum!

The two robots, which had been motionless before, suddenly jolted and began to move. Their actions flowed smooth like running water, without any stiffness expected of mechanized warriors.

The robot on the left speedily extended both its hands. The mechanical arm split open, and many components popped out. In an instant, the entire arm was remodeled into a sturdier version, and as its palm caught the hammer, the inbuilt propulsion device on its back was fully activated, erupting with a disorderly airflow.

Clank!

The war hammer was forcibly blocked and was scarily not suppressed by Harmon in the slightest!

The other robot locked its arms together as a seam appeared in the middle of its arms, with blue light flickering within. A huge amount of air was drawn in, as a sharp whistling sound was heard. The next moment, both fists punched out, and from the tips of the fists, a compressed air cannon shot was released, akin to a compressed hurricane.

Harmon took the cannon blast directly to his chest, and he appeared to be a tree that had been uprooted amid a storm. He flew back over a hundred meters, finally slamming hard against the opposite wall of the training room.

Bang!

The wall was dented, and the entire figure of Harmon was trapped inside.

"The actual battle statistics are not half bad!" Han Xiao looked at the two robots flanking him.

Other than the mechanical beasts used in his mechanic army, the Great Mechanic Han was not lacking in elites. If used for comparison, the mechanical beasts would be akin to the foot soldiers, while the elite machinery would be the mini bosses. The two mechanical warriors could be considered elites.

[Oathkeeper], the elite mechanical warrior in his mechanical army. With the autonomous control from Phillip, the huge amount of data it possessed allowed for the execution of highly complex combat patterns. Its weapons and armor were top-notch with high costs. Even with Han Xiao's current manufacturing speed, he could only construct a Protector once a day.

Their individual combat capabilities were outstanding, and even if faced with Grade B Supers, they could still hold their own. These were the hired guns that Han Xiao was using when fighting against someone of the same level.

Every Oathkeeper was an independent unit with its unique code name. The current two Oathkeepers that had been released concurrently were labelled 'Warrior' and 'Gunner'.

Harmon's muscles swelled as he forcefully pulled himself out from the hole. However, Han Xiao did not bother giving him the time to move and instead clapped his hands, deploying the Halo Array to congregate together, releasing an integrated laser cannon blast.

Boom!

The laser hit directly at Harmon once again, driving him deeper into the wall. A violent explosion occurred, with waves of heat and black smoke filling the room.

Taking this chance, the two Oathkeepers moved out, restricting Harmon as they tangled with him.

Because the Oathkeepers were not designed to be mechanical suits, there was no need to leave a space within to contain a person. Thus, they possessed many different kinds of weapons, such as compressed air cannons, gravitational and repulsion devices, laser rifles, lightsabers, photon cannons, electromagnetic shields, and more. Be it close or long range, everything possible was included.

Harmon was completely suppressed by the two Oathkeepers. He kept trying to rush toward Han Xiao, bellowing angrily, his fighting spirit growing ever stronger.

"This fellow is indeed powerful, but his single target attacks are his fatal flaw. A warrior not in possession of any spells in this version can already be considered obsolete."

With a thought from Han Xiao, another compressed orb flew out, unfolding a fan-shaped structure behind him. There was a coil of sorts on the structure, and if looking from the front, it resembled a disk. It bore a similarity to a radar disk, with the patterns on top forming concentric circles like a labyrinth.

Han Xiao put his hands behind him, and the energy from within him constantly flowed. The mechanical force travelled along the designated patterns, constantly spiraling as it let out a hum of high voltage electricity.

Ohm!

The blue glow grew more intense, and the high-speed rotation gradually blurred the coil into a single continuous piece, fuzzy and yet piercing to the eye.

This was a large-scale electromagnetic acceleration amplifier, which was specialized for a Mechanic's usage. The raw materials consisted of an electroactive polymer, which utilized the [Mechanical Force Combat Technique] to release an electromagnetic force. This electromagnetic energy would continuously increase within the amplifier, equivalent to allowing it to be primed much like a bomb. The longer the primer, the stronger the effect.

Because Han Xiao had sufficient funds in his hands, he bought the High-End Knowledge [Advanced Electromagnetic Forcefield] in the last year, using it to unlock the [Mechanical Force Combat Technique]. Even with the usage of machinery, the Mechanic could still unleash the strength of a certain weapon.

Compared to the original Trap Style, this move not only had higher crowd control but also had the advantage of being an active skill.

Buzz!

The speed of the electro-optical rotation rose non-stop, filling the entire field with a piercing white glow. Han Xiao's figure had long been covered by the light—even the free ions in the air were affected by the electrical charge. The prisoners that were huddled in a corner were all terrified as they felt their hair stand on end, and a numb feeling coursed around their skin.

On the other side, the hairy Harmon saw all his hair sticking out like a hedgehog. He felt something amiss and immediately threw out his war hammer toward the piercing white glow. However, one of the Oathkeepers' heads split open to reveal a ring-shaped purple attachment. It shot out a beam akin to gravitational pull, and the war hammer that was flying in midair suddenly halted before being brought back toward the robot.

"Have a taste of this. Yang Clan's Electrotherapy!"

Dong! Dong!

The next second, six metal pillars shot out, embedding themselves around Harmon. With a point of a finger from Han Xiao, the electromagnetic energy accumulated by the amplifier was like a flash flood as it morphed into a piercing lightning beam. It struck one of the pillars, and the next instant, electromagnetic lights swirled around the six pillars akin to a lightning tornado, forming an electric cage.

The six metallic pillars were actually release devices, and all the power was directed toward the content within them. Following the pathway of the electro-optic rotation between the columns, thousands of lightning bolts smashed within the sealed area, and Harmon resembled a lightning conductor at this point, with all the bolts aiming for him. On average, he was struck with a few hundred bolts per second.

"Ow! Ow! Ow!" Harmon was electrocuted to the point that his eyes rolled backward into his head. His whole body turned motionless, only letting out uncontrollable moans from time to time.

The electrical lights continued to flash for a good few seconds until the accumulated charges were consumed. The training hall then quieted down, with a few charged sparks lingering within the air, resounding with a buzzing sound.

Within the metal pillars, Harmon swayed and tottered before falling to the ground with a loud thud. He was completely charred and releasing black smoke, as though he was a steak that had been overcooked.

Since he had been electrocuted unconscious, his Esper ability was automatically lifted, and his inflated body slowly shrunk.

"Phew... while this guy has an insane about of HP and defense, with an additional specialization bonus, his resistance attributes fortunately aren't too perverted."

Han Xiao spat out an electric charge, recalling all his machinery. Having electrocuted Harmon till he fainted, the match was considered his victory.

"For my current combat modes, other than the Artillery Style, the Beast Style, Trap Style, and Mechanical suit, I have the foundations of the Army Style, which I've built in the past year. However, this will only show its effectiveness in a large-scale battle.

"As for the elite fighting style used for battles within the same Grade, my mechanical hands, the Floating Cannon Array, and the Oathkeepers are all representative of this elite style. Compared to when I was in Noriosse, the number of styles I have to use on my enemies has increased."

Han Xiao then moved forward to rouse Harmon. After that blockhead regained consciousness, he looked around sluggishly for a while before fulfilling his promise to teach Han Xiao the Energy Training Technique. While he had lost, Harmon was not angry at all. He would not dwell on his failures but instead take it as valuable experience to prepare for his next battle.

When the battle ended, the prisoners finally heaved a sigh of relief. Everyone was sweating profusely even though they were the spectators. They felt even more tired than having gone through a battle, their hearts palpitating in fear.

These interstellar people are truly monsters!

You have acquired [Luhan Hammer Technique]!

After obtaining the skill, Han Xiao hid his joy and nodded toward Harmon.

"Good fight."

"If there's a chance, we'll exchange blows again." Harmon snorted before walking away.

Due to the restraint brought about by specializations, Han Xiao did not feel much pressure throughout the whole thing. Instead, he took it as experience to test out his new styles. Compared to Herlous, Harmon was more like a live target.

After sorting out his equipment, he walked out of the training room to find Herlous standing outside.

"What are you doing here?"

"I caught wind of news that you and Harmon were sparring and came over to take a look. I wanted to see your bedraggled look." Herlous laughed.

"I've let you down, I guess." Han Xiao rolled his eyes. "Anything else?"

Herlous kept his smile and cleared his throat before slowly asking, "This.... I want to ask. About the thing you promised me, when can I cash that in?"

"I've promised you many things. Which one in particular?"

Lifting up his prosthetic limb, Herlous spoke with an expression of expectation. "You told me in the past that there was someone in your hometown that could allow me to regenerate my arm. While your prosthetic is really comfortable... I still miss the original goods."

"Oh, so it's this." Han Xiao came to a realization. Herlous' arm had been disintegrated by Ember, and Han Xiao had told him that Aurora's ability could actually help to treat his disability.

Rubbing his brow, Han Xiao felt a headache coming on. While Aurora had that kind of strength, this matter was a little sensitive. With Aurora being so enthusiastic in aiding others, she definitely would not reject being of assistance. The main problem was the Hila who went around with a black face as though she was angry at the world. Han Xiao did not dare guarantee that she would not be as protective of Aurora like the past.

"Let me bring you to consult them."

Chapter 524: Hila

The environment of the wilderness was harsh, with some refugees choosing to remain cowering within their own homes. They had the mentality of leaving everything to fate, choosing to bear the potential problems caused by the mutation virus rather than leave the safety of their homes. As for other refugees, they did not wish to sit and await death, choosing to brave the danger to cross the desolate wilderness filled with beasts to reach the only Sanctuary left.

With Bennett's temperament, he naturally would not be able to disregard them. Even if the Sanctuary was overcapacity, saving one more would be another gained. Thus, the current refugees accepted by the Sanctuary had already surpassed tens of thousands. The entire city was packed to the brim, with the land outside the original walls having been cleared to create a larger square to facilitate the sea of refugees.

Before they flowed endlessly in, even with the increased production of suppressants, it was still in short supply. Fortunately, there were the players present to maintain law and order. They willingly bore the burden, enjoying themselves in the process.

Due to the high number of people, Aurora was always busy as she had to play the role of a human virus detector. She constantly scanned each wave of infected, practically without any proper rest.

At a particular checkpoint of the Sanctuary, there were over a thousand dirty, unkempt refugees awaiting the virus check. Fully armed soldiers were present all around to maintain public order, and the eyes of the refugees betrayed their unease and panic. This disaster had stretched their nerves to breaking point.

"When will we be allowed to enter?"

"Do you know that in order to reach the Sanctuary, I braved countless dangers along the way! A physical search can be explained, but why are we still being kept here!"

Many of the refugees were getting emotional.

"Everyone, before being allowed into the Sanctuary, we need to run a virus check. Please cooperate," a commander shouted. While the refugees looked unsatisfied, they could only endure the anxiety.

At this point, Aurora walked in front of the crowd, closed her eyes, and felt the life signs of all the refugees present.

After a long while, she finally opened her eyes and spoke with an expression of apology, "There's an infected among you. Please follow the soldiers to the quarantine area when I indicate to you."

As the soldiers walked into the crowd to pull out the infected, their actions roused the anxiety of all the refugees present.

"What are you doing! Let go! I'm not infected!

"Let go of my kid!"

"Scram!"

The emotions of the refugees were akin to a powder keg, easily ignited by just a small spark. Even if the majority initially intended to stay obedient, with a small portion of rebels, everyone quickly turned chaotic to resist and attack the soldiers.

Shouts, pleads, grumbles, and even the sound of things being thrown on the ground could be heard. The entire place was a mess.

In such an extreme period, the methods employed by the guards were naturally as extreme. They employed kicks and punches, forcefully dragging out the infected to handcuff them and throw them into a corner. A few of the infected children were even forcefully snatched from their parents' hands, causing them to cry nonstop.

Bang!

A gunshot was heard.

The entire field fell dead silent. Everyone saw a male refugee with a face of insanity, holding onto a handgun with the barrel emitting smoke. The gun was held up toward the sky, causing the refugees around him to immediately scramble away. In an instant, the man's surroundings were devoid of human life.

The expressions of the soldiers greatly shifted, with a dozen over rifles immediately pointed at the man.

"Dammit, how did those searchers in front do their jobs‽ How did he sneak this gun into the city?"

"Put down your weapon, or else we fire!" the commander bellowed.

The man holding onto the gun was trembling in both legs, but he mustered his courage to reply, "Don't... don't be fooled by them! I heard that those who are quarantined were actually all executed. They cannot be believed!"

"You're mistaken. We actually have a way to save these infected. Don't be rash!" The commander immediately stepped out to placate the man while signaling with his eyes toward his gunmen.

The moment that the armed man's attention was shifted, they would immediately fire and put him down.

At this time, one of the infected that had been pulled out screamed in an ear-piercing voice.

"Dad!"

An eight-year-old child struggled free from the hands of the guard, stumbling as he made his way in front of the man. He hugged tightly to the trouser leg of the man, his eyes wide open in fear as he stared around him in shock, his tiny figure trembling.

The commander immediately cursed inwardly, hurriedly covering the muzzle of the soldier near him. Nobody was willing to kill the father in front of his child. If only the child was not present!

"Please consider for your child and put down your weapon. We can attest to the fact that we have the means to save the infected!"

"How... how can you save them!" the armed refugee shouted in return.

The commander kept his patience and explained, "We have produced a drug that can suppress the virus. The reason we quarantine the infected is to ensure that they are easily identified so that we can give them the drug."

"Then immediately bring the drug over for my child. I want to witness the whole process!"

"This..." The commander hesitated. "The production rate of the suppressant is extremely low. There are still several people within the quarantine zone waiting for the drug. The rough wait till your turn will be around three days. I have no authority..."

The gunman immediately grumbled, cutting into the commander's explanation, "I don't care! You had better bring the medicine over immediately, or else... or else, I'm gonna fire!"

As he spoke, the gunman pointed the muzzle at the worried Aurora, who was standing at a distance witnessing the scene. He had previously noticed that Aurora was the person responsible for identifying the virus and should be someone important. Only by threatening her could his demands be fulfilled.

Every soldier present lost color in their faces as their fingers almost depressed the triggers on their rifles.

"Don't shoot! She's the only person who can identify the virus now. The whole world needs her!"

"I don't care! I want the drug!" The man's eyes were bloodshot, his emotions highly unstable.

At that moment, a dark red energy bubble suddenly surrounded Aurora. Hila walked out from the side, her expression frosty with anger.

The armed refugee immediately fired, but the bullets were all deflected by the dark red shield. Hila waved her hand, and the energy turned into a beam, shooting directly toward the forehead of the assailant.

When Aurora worked, Hila would always make sure to accompany her as her bodyguard to prevent any misfortune from falling on her little sister. This move of hers was made to kill. She would not be lenient when removing any threats to her sister's life.

"Sister, no!"

Hila's brow wrinkled, and the energy beam that was en route to blowing the man's head off changed course, shattering the firearm in his hand instead. The guards immediately swarmed to arrest the man while prying the kid who was still hugging onto his father's leg to the side.

"You should have let me kill him," Hila said impatiently. "Kindness is the natural enemy to survival. You need to change—stop being so naive."

Aurora, however, smiled and replied, "That's not the case. I know that with my sister present, he cannot hurt me. He was just impulsive, and we should not deprive him of his life just for that. We should be working to save the refugees instead."

"Sigh, my silly little sister..." Hila narrowed her eyes, as all those bloody memories flashed through her mind. She shook her head to clear them. "Don't be reluctant in viewing people from their worst side."

In her black, skintight combat suit, Hila's long legs enabled her to quickly reach the arrested man. Looking down from where she stood, she coldly snapped, "If you do not trust us and do not wish to quarantine your son, leave this place. We lack everything except refugees. No one will stop you from leaving. Guards, release him and the child."

The guards did as instructed and let go of the man. The latter immediately scooped up his child, staring angrily at Hila. However, he instead got ferociously stared back at. From her glare that was full of killing intent, a cold feeling surfaced in the man's heart, and he could only slowly retreat in anger.

He swept the remaining people a look, hugging his child tight as he took heavy steps toward the outside. He did not wish to be separated from his son, so he was not willing to stay.

At this time, Aurora suddenly opened her mouth.

"Please don't leave."

The man paused, turning his head back to look at the petite Aurora, his face an expression of shock.

Aurora said in a sincere voice, "While we will not restrict you from leaving, I implore you to stay. The wilderness is honestly too dangerous, and only by staying in the Sanctuary can you both obtain safety. Please believe in my sincerity."

"Then immediately bring the drugs over and save my son!" Hearing her words, the man immediately interjected.

However, Aurora shook her head in response. "To resist and retaliate just to protect your kin regardless of the danger, trust me, I'm also deeply aware of such an impulse. I'm sorry, we will never give you suppressants in advance. That would be unfair to others, and making trouble will definitely not be exchanged for special treatment. But I hope that you can trust us. With patience, your child can definitely get healed."

Even if she believed in kindness, she would never let it sway her principles. After experiencing such a long period of darkness, the naivety in her had long vanished.

Her words brought upon a sense of strength and reliance, and the man seemed to hesitate. At this point, his son suddenly wiped his tears and spoke out, "Dad, I believe her. Let me go to the quarantine area. I will protect myself well."

The man gritted his teeth, finally letting go of the child. The commander came forward to hold onto the kid's hands, and while the man looked as though he wanted to intervene several times, he eventually refrained from any rash movements.

After this short episode, the emotions of the refugees also calmed down. They obediently accepted the quarantines, and order was restored.

The two sisters left the site due to the huge size of the bear tagging along behind Aurora, mild and docile.

Hila stroked Aurora's head as she frowned, saying, "Did you forget what I said? There is no meaning in helping others. To be selfless to others is to allow them to be selfish for themselves—there is no point extending your goodwill to strangers as they do not have the qualifications to obtain your help."

Aurora pulled on Hila's hand as she softly replied, "Since we have the strength to help others, if we keep it hidden and don't help them, aren't we being selfish?"

"Helping others is considered a noble affair, but helping yourself is considered a repulsive matter," Hila coldly replied. "This sort of hypocrisy makes me disgusted. The majority of morals are just scams to trick those who are stupid."

"But Uncle Black Star once saved me out of goodwill. We're people who have obtained help. Don't say that you aren't happy because of it." Aurora chuckled.

"..." Every time they touched on this topic, Hila would become speechless. "In any case, this favor of his will be repaid one day. I don't like owing others."

While she said that, Han Xiao had already entered a new state, with a huge change in status. When they first met, Han Xiao had merely been a weak, pale test subject receiving training. However, he now had this sort of achievement, making Hila wonder if all of this was actually reality. Life was truly too fickle.

Thus, Hila had always been torn over how to face the current Han Xiao. He seemed to no longer need her strength, and she did not know how exactly she could return this favor.

"Sometimes, I really have no idea how to chat with you." Aurora pretended to be an elderly, sighing. "If you could be less eccentric, the number of people giving you recognition would be a thousand times greater than the current number."

"Humph, a person that requires the approval of others is merely so-so." Hila frowned.

Aurora could only shake her head in response.

While I've always been protected by my older sister, sometimes, I feel as though she is actually the child instead!

...

Not far away, Herlous and Han Xiao had just arrived, and after listening to the talk between the two sisters, they looked at each other.

"Let's go back, I feel that there's nothing that can be done for you." Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Herlous was shocked. "D*mn your mother, you haven't even asked! Could you play a more practical role‽"

Chapter 525: Aurora

"You heard her. Even if you are my friend, they may not show you any face." Han Xiao shook his head. Aurora was a kindhearted girl and would naturally be willing to help, but the same could not be said for Hila. This lass had a cold character and did not like bothering about other people's affairs. Furthermore, she was extremely protective of her sister and would probably stop her sister from agreeing.

Even though Hila owed him a favor, with her obstinate temper, she would not let her sister pay him back.

"That can't be right. It isn't too much to just get her to use her Esper abilities." Herlous became anxious.

"There is a historical reason for this. Whenever her sister uses her Esper abilities, she has to exhaust her own life force. She once suffered from some miserable mishap before and thus is extremely sensitive to this matter."

"You promised me." Herlous refused to give up.

"Alright then, I shall ask for you."

Han Xiao shook his head helplessly and walked forward to stop the two ladies.

The nose of the gigantic bear twitched. It could smell a familiar scent, and its green bean sized eyes were fixed on Han Xiao, unsure if Han Xiao was his former owner. Only when Han Xiao waved did the bear charge out excitedly and roll around in front of Han Xiao, revealing his belly for Han Xiao to rub.

"This bear has been brought up well by you." Han Xiao stroked the bear's chin, and the bear's furry feeling was much better than Harmon's.

In this past, this bear could still be called a baby bear. Now that it was a few meters tall, Han Xiao could not call it a baby anymore.

"That's right, it grew up extremely quickly. Being by my side, my Esper abilities caused his life force to flourish." Aurora smiled.

Stroking the bear's chin, Han Xiao suddenly mused, "If that's the case, its meat quality should be great."

The bear that was rolling on the ground suddenly froze in place as its ears shot up, feeling that something was wrong.

"Why did you stop us?" Hila asked.

Han Xiao then dragged Herlous out and said, "This is Herlous, my comrade. In one of the battles, he was accidentally injured. If your eyes are sharp enough, you should be able to tell that he has a mechanical arm..."

Hila was completely speechless. "Have you been using the standard of a blind person to judge others' eyesight?"

"I promised to treat his broken limbs and wish to ask Aurora for help."

"Don't even think about it." Before Aurora could even reply, Hila rejected Han Xiao.

Han Xiao's mouth began to twitch. "You should at least pretend to consider..."

"You understand my sister; she is only able to restore the injuries of others at the expense of her own life force. In this world, I will only allow my sister to save a single person... that person is you."

Hila suddenly paused for a while before adding, "Don't think that our relationship is extremely good. It is just that we owe you a favor. Apart from you, we will not save anyone."

Aurora's [Dawn of Life] gave her an incomparably exuberant life force, and her cells were capable of producing a special life force. The life force that Aurora had was just like a bucket of water, and healing a severe injury would only require a single drop.

However, it was still her 'life force' being exhausted...

While Aurora was currently healthy, Hila would never allow her to waste her life force in such a manner.

Before Han Xiao could reply, Aurora interrupted, "Sister, this is an extremely easy task for me, and I have always been the one being helped by others. I wish to do something for Black Star as well."

"No," Hila rejected flatly.

"Sister, you can't always make my decisions for me," Aurora said helplessly.

"Why aren't you willing to listen to what I taught you? The kind will only be bullied in this world!" Hila said with exasperation. "That was the case just now, and this happened again now. When will you be able to grow up a little? As long as there is a first time, all the injured people will come and find you. Are you going to always exhaust your life force to help them‽"

Han Xiao immediately became displeased. Why did it feel like this lady was scolding him?

Han Xiao immediately got Phillip to view through the surveillance record and briefly explain to him about the previous commotion outside the Sanctuary. The daily activities of the Sanctuary were controlled by Bennett, and Han Xiao could not be bothered to interfere with such small affairs. He only wanted to know the reason behind the two sisters' conflict.

In the past, both the sisters had been living in challenging conditions and could only rely on each other. Now that they had spent a couple of years living in peace and seeing each other every day, even if they were biological siblings, their characters could not be completely compatible. Thus, conflict was inevitable.

"Sis, why are you always exaggerating matters? I will naturally reject them when I don't wish to help," Aurora said. "Besides, Uncle Black Star helped us so much, and I want to repay him..."

"No means no!" Hila then glared at Han Xiao and growled, "You are our benefactor, and we will definitely repay this favor. However, I hope that you will not think about touching my sister."

Han Xiao was speechless. These words of hers made it seem as though he had some unscrupulous motives. She was truly too overprotective.

Looking at the two quarreling sisters, Herlous looked at Han Xiao and said helplessly, "You were right. It is hopeless indeed."

"Let's go."

Just when the two of them were about to leave, Aurora suddenly raised her voice and said with a solemn tone, "Sister, you will not be able to protect me forever, and I cannot be a little child who is forever protected. I sincerely request that you do not make my decisions for me."

"No, your thinking is far too childish, and you don't know how to protect yourself at all." Hila refused to budge.

"Why do you always want to change me‽" Aurora was angered for the first time, and a golden light flashed in her eyes. "The kind of people I look down on the most are those who don't need help but mock those who are willing to help others. Only someone who went through despair will understand how much you hope for help during times of hopelessness. I know this feeling extremely well. During the nights when I needed help the most, I prayed for someone to save me time and time again, but the needle pierced into my veins over and over again without anyone ever stretching out their hands to me. Do you understand such hopelessness‽"

Hila had a face full of guilt. It was her carelessness that had resulted in Aurora being captured by the Germinal Organization and going through so much suffering. However, she had not been able to provide much aid and had only been able to save her sister because of Han Xiao's unexpected aid. Hila had always felt that she was a failure of a sister.

In the past, Aurora would never talk about the pain that she had gone through in front of her, and this was the first time that Aurora had blamed her. Hila was completely caught off guard and did not know how to respond.

"I know that you have a strong-minded personality, and to prevent you from facing pressure, I pretended to be extremely optimistic whenever I met you," Aurora said. "However, how happy do you think I could have been?

"I suffered inexplicable pain, and I know how cruel and violent humans can be. I know the despair of being in a hopeless situation without anyone to help you. The only thing I can do is fight and not submit to the darkness. I refuse to have my personality contorted by the pain and be filled with hatred. Believe me, this is far more difficult than bearing with the physical pain that I had to go through.

"Han Xiao helped me during my moments of hopelessness, and thus, I am willing to help others."

She then looked Hila in the eye and said softly, "We cannot live in the past forever, and we all have to grow. Sister, I love you, but I cannot be your toy doll. I have my own thoughts and wish to become the kind of person I want to be."

Hila opened her mouth and did not know what to say.

Han Xiao raised his brows and was a little surprised. He had not expected the two sisters to actually end up quarreling. It seemed like the two sisters had built up plenty of frustrations over the past few years when he was not around.

Even if they had gone through plenty of things together, it was impossible for them to always be so loving. When there were no enemies, they would definitely end up arguing because of their incompatible characters. This was something that Han Xiao had found from the couple living next door in his previous life.

However, having an argument might not be a bad thing. At least it would allow the two sisters to get to know each other better.

Han Xiao shook his head. Women...

Everyone fell silent, and Aurora rubbed her head embarrassedly. The atmosphere that she had taken so much effort to build instantly crumbled. She then asked carefully, "Sister, I am going to help treat him, okay?"

"You have already said so much, what else can I say? You can just take it that you don't have this older sister. Go go," Hila replied.

Aurora broke out into a smile and gave Hila a hug.

Upon seeing that, Han Xiao took the few of them to his machinery modification room. Taking off Herlous' mechanical arm, Aurora pointed her palm at Herlous' stump. A dense golden light shot out from her palms and entered Herlous' body. The broken limb then began to grow out like a sprouting plant.

In the past few years, Aurora had also begun to develop her abilities, and she no longer needed to use her blood to save others. Instead, she was able to release the life force within her body.

By the side, Han Xiao and Hila stood together and watched the scene.

Suddenly, Hila asked with a complicated tone, "Do you think that I am wrong?"

"Hmm?"

Han Xiao turned around to look at her, only to see her biting her lips with her brow furrowed. She was obviously still frustrated over what had just happened.

"There isn't a right or wrong; everyone is different. But if you want my opinion, I think that you make more sense. This world is very dangerous, and enemies are all around. The most rational thing to do is to put your own safety first."

"You would actually agree with me..." Hila had a strange look on her face. Han Xiao had returned from the galaxy when the planet was in danger. With his 'selfless' character, she had thought that Han Xiao would support Aurora.

Han Xiao then shrugged and added, "But if you really ask me to make a choice, I would be more willing to be friends with a kind person."

If not for Aurora's insistence, his request would have been rejected by Hila. To him, he liked those who were more obedient.

Both the sisters were full of potential. A Grade S Esper ability was extremely rare, and if Hila was able to grow to the heights of her previous life, she would be able to crush a dozen 'Herlous's with a single finger. Furthermore, Aurora's abilities were also extremely useful, and she was just like a walking HP potion.

As for their contrasting characters, Han Xiao did not mind it at all. As long as they were talents useful to him, all of that was no more than small details. Just like how Ames was extremely playful but there were not many who dared criticize her—strength was the most important.

...

Not too long later, Herlous' arm had regrown. Give it a few test waves, he cried out with excitement, "Haha! My arm is back!"

Aurora wiped the sweat off her face and said with glee, "I'm glad I could help you."

Rubbing Aurora's head, Han Xiao gave her a series of praise before leaving with Herlous. Herlous was extremely satisfied with his new arm and skipped away happily.

Returning to his room, Han Xiao sent Herlous away before taking out his Galactic Communicator and turning to the local channel of the Garton Star System.

The plan to hire the players was already on track, and the skills to reach the next Energy Level had also been obtained. It was now time for him to see when Godora's rescue squad would arrive.

Version 2.0 had been launched for half a month, and it was about time for Godora to arrive.

The Garton Star System was part of Godora's administrative region, and with so many planets being plagued with calamity at the same time, it was truly too much of a coincidence. Godora would naturally have their suspicions, and the first party that they would think about would be their arch nemesis, DarkStar. Because they felt that this may be a trap, Godora did not make any rash moves and investigated the situation first.

Just a few hours ago, Han Xiao's communicator had received a district message regarding this matter.

Many galactic media outlets had noticed the situation in Godora and had begun writing articles on it. As such, the calamity had attracted the attention of many, with the Godoran media being the most interested in the matter. After all, this was happening within the Godora region.

After a series of reports, more and more Godorans were informed of the calamity that their allied civilizations were facing, and they found out that their own civilization had not sent out any rescue troops. The voices of the citizens immediately sounded to push for their civilization to send aid.

After watching the local news of the Garton Star System, Han Xiao raised his brows and came to a conclusion.

"DarkStar has begun their plans..."

At this moment, Godora had not intervened in the matter, and news of the calamity would naturally be sent out by DarkStar in secret. Through some manipulation and stirring, this resulted in the entire event blowing up, causing Godora to become the center of everyone's attention.

Apart from Han Xiao, the entire Star System thought that this was a sudden, unknown calamity, but no one knew that it was actually part of DarkStar's plans.

"If my guess isn't wrong, DarkStar's forces should already be hidden on Planet Aquamarine."

Han Xiao's eyes glowed as he mused to himself.

Chapter 526: Godoran Rescue Team

Somewhere on Planet Aquamarine was a land filled with extremely high concentrations of nuclear radiation. The environment was desolate and full of decay, with thick smog and dust filling every inch of the area. The blue sky was covered by the haze, and a thick layer of white ash covered the ground. Without a single patch of green as far as the eye could see, the place seemed utterly devoid of life.

At this time, there were over a dozen narrow, shuttle-type spaceships quietly parked in the area. A group of mixed-blood Godorans were fiddling with a bunch of strange looking machinery.

This group was an ordinary vanguard force from DarkStar, with only the leader having reached Grade B. Their main objective was to infiltrate and conceal themselves, without any need to fight. Even their spaceships were kept in stealth mode, shielding themselves from all sorts of detection equipment. Han Xiao's fleet had already scanned the entire planet once, but they had ultimately been unable to discover this small force. DarkStar had invested most of their resources into various forms of stealth and anti-tracking technology, or else they would have been wiped out long ago.

DarkStar had placed an infiltration team on each of the planets that held the Mutation Source. Their mission was to monitor the disaster at a close range, using specialized machinery to observe the growth stage of the mutation source's main body in order to determine its growth. This set of machinery was a gift from the same dealer of the mutation source, truly a kindhearted interstellar arms dealer.

However, the vanguard was not aware of the location of the Mutation Source, and they did not intend to search for it. This was the command given to them by the top brass.

In fact, a month ago, this vanguard from DarkStar had successfully infiltrated Planet Aquamarine. However, they had not shown their faces, instead relying on advanced Virtual Technology to link up with the satellites of the Six Nations. Through this 'sharing of vision', they were able to observe the mutation disaster and the destruction brought about to the planet. However, they were unconcerned about such intelligence. It was only after Black Star appeared that the vanguard team started to pay attention, transmitting the news to headquarters.

The top brass stationed at the headquarters of DarkStar were extremely concerned about the development of the plan, and with Black Star causing them to lose one of their veterans the last time, they had long treated him as an enemy. This news caused them to feel some surprise, but after a round of discussion, they discovered that the reason Black Star appeared back on Planet Aquamarine was not because of them.

"I've investigated it, and Planet Aquamarine is actually Black Star's hometown. It's merely a coincidence that we chose this planet, and Planet Aquamarine should have some means to communicate with Black Star. Now that the disaster has struck, they probably requested assistance from Black Star, thus bringing about such a situation. The appearance of Black Star has nothing to do with us."

"In actual fact, this is the most plausible explanation. We've stayed in the darkness. Up till now, no one should know that this mutation disaster is our plan."

"The disaster relief squad from Godora is about to arrive on the various planets. Just one more Black Star is merely another reinforcement, and Planet Aquamarine is just one of our many planets. It will not affect our plans."

While they were hostile toward Han Xiao, their plan was more important. In order not to alert the enemy, DarkStar had rejected the idea of attacking Han Xiao. Furthermore, after investigation, they had discovered that he owned a BlackLight Stealth and could run anytime he wanted without them being able to obstruct him.

In their eyes, it was a coincidence that Han Xiao had appeared, and this would not affect the big picture. There was no need for them to be anxious and reveal themselves—the mission was still more important.

The Mutation Disaster was the core of DarkStar's plan, and the crucial part lay in their next few steps. All they needed to do was wait for the opportunity.

In the following days, the regional problems within the Garton Star System grew more intense. While the other advanced civilizations watched from the sidelines, nobody wished to help. The unlucky planets were all situated around the administrative region of Godora, so according to diplomatic regulations, the problem ought to be handled by Godora.

The other advanced civilizations did not bother to stick their hands into this affair, but nobody reproached them. However, if Godora failed to handle the planets in their administrative region, that would be a stain on their name.

Sending disaster relief was optional, of course, but it would affect the civilization's status and standing within the Shattered Star Ring. Their allies in the system would also start to re-evaluate their relationship with Godora. As a member of the Lawful Faction, they were a few rules to be observed. For Godora to reinforce its status as the dominant party in the Garton Star System, they had to quell the turmoil of public opinion. As such, they would not sit idly by and would send out disaster relief squads for humanitarian reasons.

Spaceships departed one after another from the space station in Godora, proceeding toward the different planets in each star zone. The Six Nations finally received the news that the Godoran spaceship was heading toward Planet Aquamarine.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations were so touched that they almost cried. After suffering for over a month, Godora had finally remembered that it was the parent of all these countries and was willing to pop by.

The technology of Planet Aquamarine was naturally unable to discover the source of the mutation disaster, but they believed that the Godoran technology could definitely do so. With the aid provided by Godora, the disaster would soon be solved.

Even though the Six Nations had deferred to Han Xiao to request for assistance, the long-established status of Godora to the Six Nations would not be weakened so easily. Black Star had promised them that the mutation disaster would be removed in the future, but currently, he had no way whatsoever to identify the source of the disaster. This could not solve their current urgent needs. Hence, toward the problem of the mutation disaster, the Six Nations would still put more trust in Godora than Black Star.

On the day of arrival for the Godoran spaceship, the Six Nations led a delegation of senior officials to wait at the agreed landing spot, the coordinates of which they had sent to Godora in advance.

"This is the first time that the Godoran Civilization has come on a large scale. We have to bring out the best etiquette in welcoming them."

To be able to see the Godora fleet was a huge event for the whole civilization. Even if the Six Nations were currently placed in a difficult situation, they had managed to recover some semblance of law and order. To ensure that they would graciously receive their 'savior', the Six Nations did not dare mistreat them and actually prepared a grand ceremony.

However, the Six Nations were also at a loss. This was the first time that they would meet with a galactic civilization. They were unaware of the culture of Godorans, and they did not know what the situation in the galaxy was. They were afraid of causing any misunderstandings.

On this day, the Six Nations' astrology centers kept their attention on the sky at all times. Their mission was to be the first to discover the traces of the Godoran spaceships.

In the afternoon, when the sun was at its most piercing, a fleet slowly entered the atmosphere of Planet Aquamarine. Golden spaceships emerged from the clouds, slowly flying over Planet Aquamarine. This satellite imagery was immediately passed on to the Six Nations.

The leaders perked up, preparing with anxious hearts to receive the Godorans at the landing point.

At this time, the observers suddenly sent out an urgent report. "That's not right, the Godorans have suddenly changed their course. They are no longer approaching us!"

"What‽"

The officials that were stationed at the landing site were shocked and hurriedly referred to the satellite imagines. All they saw was the Godoran fleet not approaching their predetermined location but instead heading toward the Sanctuary.

The eyes of the leaders of the Six Nations instantly bulged in disbelief.

The exchanges between civilizations should technically be handled by the Six Nations, and besides, they were the ones who had requested assistance. Why had Godora thrown them to a corner and instead run over to Black Star?

They were the true rulers of the planet!

They had initially wanted to personally come into contact with the Godorans, displaying the etiquette of Planet Aquamarine. However, the reality proved different from their imaginations. Their painstakingly prepared welcome ceremony was wasted, and the upper echelons of the Six Nations wanted to cry, but no tears could come out. They only had one thought.

To Godora, could it be that the entire civilization of Planet Aquamarine cannot compare to one Black Star‽

The leaders of the Six Nations only felt a wave of humiliation rush up to their heads as they thought about the contents of their conversation with Han Xiao—If you wish to talk on equal terms, you have to first leave the planet.

The golden spaceships hovered outside the Sanctuary, and the players ran out in droves to surround them, exclaiming.

Bennett knew of the Six Nations requesting assistance from Godora, but he did not expect the fleet to come over. He also hurriedly ran out to welcome them.

Hum!

The underside of all the spaceships opened, shooting out yellow gravitational beams. The Godorans appeared one by one, just like the ships were laying eggs.

The disaster relief squad slowly approached the ground, the head of command being Nagakin.

There was a number of new residential areas outside the Sanctuary walls to accommodate the refugees. When the soldiers and refugees saw this scene, their mouths opened wide, their faces sluggish. This was the first time that they had seen Godorans, and they were both curious and nervous, staring at the aliens without blinking.

Bennett had seen Han Xiao capture one of them in the past, so he managed to maintain a calm image as he walked up.

"Respected Godoran friends, I am Bennett, currently in charge of manning this Sanctuary. I represent Planet Aquamarine in welcoming all of you and thank you for your generosity in providing aid. Our planet is direly in need of your help."

Nagakin did not speak but instead pointed up at the spaceships hovering above the Sanctuary. Using the translator, he said in a severe tone, "What is with the spaceships above here?"

Planet Aquamarine was a simple planet, and the Godoran troops naturally felt a sense of superiority. They did not place the natives in their eyes, but to actually see a fleet of interstellar ships there, they could not help but feel curious.

The reason for the Godorans changing course to the Sanctuary was not because they knew that Han Xiao was present, but rather, they had discovered the fleet under Han Xiao's command. Thus, Nagakin had commanded the troops to change course, not landing at the agreed coordinates. This was to investigate the reason behind the fleet's appearance.

Nagakin possessed the strength of a Calamity Grade Super, and even the aura that he unconsciously displayed was enough to cause Bennett's heart to tighten. He could feel a dangerous aura from the person in front of him, causing him fright. For a moment, he forgot how to speak.

At this moment, Han Xiao appeared from the crowd and laughed. "Nagakin, we meet again."

"It's you!" Nagakin opened his eyes wide. His severe expression immediately dissipated like storm clouds after a rain, leaving an expression of joy. He boomed in laughter, taking large strides to give Han Xiao a passionate bear hug.

In the last battle when they worked side by side, Han Xiao had left Nagakin on a deep impression regarding his strength. He could not forget Han Xiao and immediately recognized him at a glance.

"Black Star‽ Hahaha, to think that you're here too!"

Compared to the disdain Nagakin that had toward the people on Planet Aquamarine, he was jovial toward Han Xiao, literally a heaven and earth difference when compared with each other.

Hearing his exclamation, the people behind Nagakin let out a hubbub of chatter.

"It's indeed Black Star!"

"The one who killed a Calamity Grade Super together with Commander Nagakin!"

The Godorans hid their arrogance, letting out expressions of surprise as they conversed.

Seeing the duo, Bennett let his surprise show, stammering in disbelief, "You... you two know each other‽"

Han Xiao let go of Nagakin, smiling, as he replied, "Didn't I tell you before? I have many friends in the interstellar region."

Bennett could only numbly nod. He did remember Han Xiao mentioning it before, but he did not know the exact circumstances. To suddenly see the Godoran commander calling Han Xiao 'brother', only then did he have a clearer picture of Han Xiao's status within the interstellar region.

"You seem to have adapted better than I imagined." Bennett sighed as he replied in a complicated tone.

In the past, Han Xiao had once invited Bennett to join him, but he had chosen to remain in Planet Aquamarine. Right now, the disparity between the two was already so far apart. He himself was almost frightened to death by the commander's aura, but the other party seemed to be really friendly toward Han Xiao.

Bennett only experienced a moment of distress and quickly recovered his original attitude, secretly happy for Han Xiao.

From afar, the players were all whispering.

"To think that the Godorans have also come to our planet."

"The commander opposite seems to be someone familiar to our head."

"I remember that in the videos of Bun-Hit-Dog, the head had a good relationship with the Godorans. These should be the reinforcements that the head himself called over to help."

"That's insane, the head really has some status."

"You really have no knowledge. Do you think the term 'Black Star Network' was coined for fun?"

Ever since Han Xiao began to recruit the players, the way that they addressed him had started to change. They no longer called him Black Star, rather changing to the term 'Head' instead. Even those players who had not joined the Mercenary Group also began to call him such, as this made the players feel closer to him. Before long, this title became popular in the forums, and it stuck as his new nickname.

Because the videos of Bun-Hit-Dog had recorded many stories of the Black Star Mercenary Group, the players were aware that Han Xiao not only had the backing of Floating Dragon but also alliances with many of the famed mercenary groups in the galaxy. In addition, they even had a good relationship with many of the lawful civilizations. Thus, someone had jokingly come up with the term Black Star Network. A lot of them felt that it really made sense. After seeing the videos, they resonated with the name, and it quickly became a trend.

The intelligence of the players was, however, limited, and they were still unaware that the Mutation Disaster was the scheme played between Godora and DarkStar, and they also were not aware that it was the Six Nations that had requested help from Godora... In short, they did not know anything, and thus, at this juncture, they still thought that the Godoran fleet had been summoned by Han Xiao.

Indeed, it is the Black Star Network!

Nagakin was jubilant for a while, but he suddenly recalled his own mission and raised a question. "That's right, why are you here?"

Han Xiao's expression did not change as he replied, "This planet is my hometown, and my objective is the same as yours. I'm here to also stop the disaster, and now is the time that I need the Godorans' help. Let's not dilly-dally. Let's just go in and talk."

Chapter 527: Tense Atmosphere

"So, it's like that..." Nagakin breathed in deeply.

Since the Godoran team had just arrived, they required intelligence. Everyone gathered within a meeting room, and in the next ten minutes, Han Xiao described the events over the past one month leading up to the mutation disaster. He also talked about the current situation of Planet Aquamarine, allowing Nagakin to better understand the situation.

"Black Star, you should have read the regional news. Not only is the disaster taking place on this planet, the War Bureau and Investigation Department have deployed many more teams as disaster relief as well. With so many planets suffering from disasters, we feel that this incident is embarrassing for us, so there's someone of my level leading the entire party," Nagakin said in a low tone. "Previously, you explained the principle behind the mutation source to me. This sort of biochemical weapon is rarely seen, and while I do not know where you got your intelligence from, I believe you have some clues about what is happening behind the scenes."

Han Xiao's eyes lit up. In his previous life, Godora did not understand the purpose of the mutation disaster, so their initial efficiency in providing disaster relief was low. This allowed the Mutation Source to grow uninhibited. Currently, his intelligence had pointed out a proper path for the Godorans to follow, which would undoubtedly increase the progress bar of the [Mutation Disaster] Mission. The overall damage for this storyline might be much less than in his previous lifetime.

However, telling them this intelligence had both pros and cons. It was not the opportune time to reveal all his cards, but Godora required some intelligence in order for them to begin their work. Thus, Nagakin connected the dots and was convinced that Han Xiao knew more about this matter.

As for the fact that the Mutation Disaster was a scheme of DarkStar, Han Xiao did not even plan to tell Godora that!

There were many reasons for this. The most crucial point behind this was that he could not obtain many benefits yet, as well as the fact that DarkStar's schemes existed through many layers. This was only the start, and based on his past life, even if he told Godora that the mutation source was placed by DarkStar, they would only realize the conspiracy the moment DarkStar launched their plans. It was as good as not telling them anything.

While Han Xiao understood the plans of DarkStar, he was clear that if he went out with everything, it would exceed the scope of what was deemed reasonable. Even a foreseer would not be able to provide such detailed intelligence. This would only make Godora suspect that he had a special channel to obtain intelligence, with the final result of attracting trouble to himself. The disadvantages outweighed the benefits; thus, Han Xiao did not plan to help Godora understand that this was a plot by DarkStar. Rather, he wanted them to fall into the trap, which would suit his own benefits.

DarkStar bought the Mutation Source as a tool to ignite a disaster, and they rode on its uniqueness that there was no quick way to resolve this. The only method would be for them to hand out the original mutation source in their hands and allow Godora to manufacture a cure.

In order to maximize his benefits, he naturally could not hand the item over when the danger had not struck. Only when Godora fell into the trap and were pressed for time could he then reveal the mutation source, allowing him to obtain the most benefits.

As for the suspicion from the other party when he handed over the mutation source, Han Xiao had long made preparations for it. During the incident of the Secret Message Bead, Han Xiao had implicated Floating Dragon in the entire affair. As for the source in his hands, it could be explained as Floating Dragon helping him to unlock the bead and keeping the thing safe. Thus, he took the benefits into his own hands while making Floating Dragon the scapegoat.

Based on the position of Ames, DarkStar would not dare go against her, and Godora could not be bothered either way. Thus, his danger level would decrease—he might even allow Floating Dragon to have higher favorability in the Godoran eyes! Han Xiao was almost touched himself by the thought he put into the plan.

The thoughts flashed by in an instant, and Han Xiao did not show any abnormalities in his facial expression. He smoothly replied to Nagakin, "You're mistaken. I once witnessed such a large-scale deployment of such biochemical weapons during one of my missions, so I went to the intelligence department to collate information. At the same time, because I'm a scholar member of the [Spacetime Research Council], I managed to obtain similar examples from within their repositories. However, I do not know the culprit behind this biochemical attack....

Pausing for a moment, Han Xiao shook his head before continuing. "But this matter is indeed fishy. If you asked me to make a guess, I would probably point this to your enemy DarkStar."

"I was thinking of the exact same thing! DarkStar has always been against us, but they suddenly started to hide and turtle up two years ago." Nagakin solemnly nodded in response. "I believe there must be a greater scheme behind this whole thing... Unfortunately, we have no evidence that they are behind this."

Han Xiao lightly laughed. "With their lousy character, I believe they are bursting from trying to hold in the fact that this is their scheme."

Hearing this, Nagakin's face showed frustration. It was true—DarkStar did not care about pleasantries at all.

"In any case, we must provide disaster relief." Han Xiao lightly skipped over the topic, leaving Nagakin to stew over if DarkStar was behind this plot; he had suggested enough. "We can cooperate. I arrived earlier than you guys by a few days. In my opinion, we can arrange our current problems into two jobs...."

Nagakin reined in his emotions, listening carefully. If the person suggesting the plan had been from the Six Nations, then he likely would not have adopted it but followed his own plans. However, Black Star was different. He had obtained the qualifications to have a dialogue of equals with him, so Nagakin was willing to listen to Han Xiao.

"The first would be to treat and save the refugees. I've already started on this, and at the moment, it seems pretty effective. However, there are more than a billion people on this planet, with hundreds of millions of people in danger. In places that our eyes don't reach, there might be thousands dying each day. If this is not contained in time, the consequences will be unimaginable."

Nagakin nodded in response. This was indeed a matter of urgency. If everyone ended up dying, who were they trying to save?

"The second matter is to discover the source of this disaster and snuff it out once and for all. This requires help from Godora, as the technology present on Planet Aquamarine is wholly inadequate to handle such a situation. If we wish to unravel this biochemical weapon, we will need to produce the corresponding antidote."

The disaster relief team would not stay on the planet indefinitely. Their main objective was to research on the source of the disaster before coming up with ideas to solve the problem.

The two suggestions were also within the plan that Nagakin had thought of, so he simply acted vigorously on the execution. After the meeting ended, he immediately brought his rescue team to begin the operation, leaving only a few researchers within the Sanctuary to experiment on the infected. This was to confirm the parameters of the virus outbreak. As for the rest, they proceeded to meet up with the Six Nations, connecting with the regime of Planet Aquamarine.

The rescue team began to operate in full capacity, at the same time cooperating with the Six Nations to ramp up the production of the suppressants. This was because of the foundation that Han Xiao had set. If he did not share the recipe of the suppressant with the Six Nations, that would have been another scene. Of course, the specific actions for rescuing the refugees would still have to be undertaken by the Six Nations themselves. The Godoran team did not have enough resources, and they would not waste so much energy on such trifling matters.

The Six Nations rode on the support given by the Godorans, restoring the morale of the citizens. This was evidently useful, as many refugees in the wilderness ran over to the Six Nations the moment that they received news of its safety, allowing them to relieve the pressure on the Sanctuary.

Across the vast land, a group of refugees with ragged clothing walked in the direction of the Six Nations.

In the early days of the Mutation Disaster, large droves of people had evacuated from the cities, as they did not dare to live in close proximity of each other. As of now, more than half of the population were refugees living in the wild. Due to the danger within the wilderness, coupled with the refugees being left to their own devices, seventy to eighty percent of the people typically died during the journey. However, because the Six Nations were busy trying to stabilize law and order, they could not spare the effort. The production of the suppressants would never be able to satisfy the number of refugees present, but it did not mean that they could ignore the refugees. They had to be searched for and welcomed back.

Thus, the players entered the sights of the refugee seekers.

Han Xiao's mercenary group consisted of the few 'Immortals', which was Frenzied Sword and company. However, to see so many of the supposed immortals there, it would be weird if Nagakin could remain unsurprised. However, this scenario had been part of Planet Aquamarine for quite a few years, so it was regarded as a unique phenomenon of Planet Aquamarine. They treated this group of people as a special species born on Planet Aquamarine.

A few years ago, an investigator from Godora had gone to Planet Aquamarine and recorded such a scenario. However, the conclusion of the investigation was vague, and thus, it did not receive much attention. At this point, Nagakin felt that the Inhumans were strange but also very willing to help out in wake of the disaster relief. Thus, he tried making contact with them.

In his past life, Nagakin's Godoran faction had attracted numerous players to join them, bringing them out to space, but now that the outstanding Han Xiao had come first, the attraction of Nagakin had its limits.

A good portion of the players were definitely interested toward the Godoran faction, but they preferred Han Xiao... No, it was not just preference. It could be called love at this level.

Of course, Nagakin did not know that Black Star was the hidden 'opponent' that he had to face and was still unaware that Han Xiao had taken away the most precious thing of his.

Even knowing that Black Star had recruited many of those Inhumans, Nagakin did not put much thought into it. Han Xiao was someone native to this planet, and the Inhumans were naturally his people. Thus, it was not surprising that they would follow Black Star. This did not obstruct Nagakin from giving out missions to the players, and even more surprisingly, the players were willing to help him in his tasks.

Just as Han Xiao predicted, the Godoran disaster relief squad brought with them a replacement of the monetary system. The original Planet Aquamarine currency was already close to collapse, and the currency of Enas used commonly in outer space was currently being made known. While the Sanctuary also had missions, compared to the rewards given by the Godorans, there was no comparison at all between the two.

The players were all clear that Enas was the true currency that could be used in the future, so the side to support in doing their missions was clear. The missions issued by the Godoran team also had a limit, so they were always treated like hot cakes among the players. Furthermore, with the faction store of Han Xiao whetting their appetite, it made the players hate the fact that they could not earn enough money to upgrade their equipment.

Han Xiao would definitely not give out missions that rewarded Enas—it was impossible to make him do something like that. However, he used his relation with Nagakin and issued a few missions where the reward could be claimed from Nagakin, allowing those players of his faction to accept those missions. The meaning was clear—if they joined the Black Star Mercenary Group, they would get better missions from the Godorans! This reflected Han Xiao's position on profiting through the Mercenary Group.

We're not the producers of the missions; we're merely the middlemen!

Using the Mercenary Group's network and word of mouth to obtain employment tasks, like borrowing flowers to offer to Buddha, to hand them out to the players would create endless resources for them, which the players would then spend on them. This was equivalent to taking the money of NPCs and giving it to himself. The players in this case were like the hardworking little honeybees, and this setup resembled a full-fledged production system where Han Xiao did not need to pay attention to in order to reap the benefits.

The current players would witness the benefits of being in the mercenary group, and those that had yet to join would be even more pressured! On the forums, everyone discussed the pros and cons of joining either the Godoran faction or the Black Star Mercenary Group, and the final conclusion was that the Black Star Mercenary Group far outshone Godora!

Joining the Godoran faction would only allow them to accept missions, but joining Black Star would allow them, based on footage of Bun-Hit-Dog, a large variety of endless tasks!

While the players have not truly felt the meaning behind this, the moment they entered outer space, which was a foregone conclusion, things would be different. Just the speculations on the forums caused the players realize just how impressive the Black Star faction was—Black Star Network was not just for show!

The foundations that Han Xiao had laid down during Version 1.0 were slowly beginning to unfold.

...

The Garton Star System was still reporting news of the disaster, and polls showed that nearly all of the Godorans were supportive of the sending of disaster relief squads. The citizens also performed all kinds of blessings, sympathetic toward the experience of their allies.

The intervention of the rescue team had greatly improved the situation of Planet Aquamarine. After several days, the treated refugees reached a new high. It was a pity that the researchers never had any breakthroughs in this period.

Because they could only come into contact with the virus through the infected, it was difficult to achieve any effects in the short run.

Han Xiao was sure that there were people from DarkStar observing the situation of the disaster relief. However, it seemed as though they had not made any moves the past few days. Nagakin and the others were still in the dark, but Han Xiao had the feeling that a tense atmosphere was brewing.

Now that Planet Aquamarine looked as though the situation was turning for the better, it seemed as though the situation could be stabilized. However, Han Xiao knew that the mutation disaster would not be as simple as that.

The moment the Mutation Source advanced to the next level, the effect would increase further, and even those who had been injected with the suppressants before would be affected once more. The dosage would have to be increased in order for them to be immunized. Currently, yield was the biggest limitation, and the more people that were saved now might have to be abandoned later. The problems regarding this would be tricky to think about.

Moreover, the higher the growth stage of the mutation virus, the more its intelligence would grow. At that time, the condition of the disease happening would no longer be as uncontrolled as it currently was, and there would be motives behind its actions. During which, not only would the ordinary citizens be affected, even the weaker Supers would fall under its control. Following the growth of strength of the virus, it would slowly infect even stronger people.

The scariest thing about the virus was that, upon reaching a certain stage, the virus would cause irreparable damage to the brain with every attack. After a long period of time, their ability to think will slowly degenerate, and those with the virus would experience an unprecedented stimulation. The pleasure they felt would be many times that of mating and addictive. It would reach a point where they would subconsciously refuse suppressants, actively seeking the disease and allowing it to destroy the last vestiges of its sanity. That was the worst case scenario.

Since Han Xiao was aware of such a matter, it meant that in his previous life, the virus had reached such a level.

If this Mutation Disaster could not be solved, then the final solution would be to abandon the planet and take all the survivors with them.

This was the worst end, and Planet Sunil was a good example of it. The treatment of refugees on the Mutation Disaster planets would not necessarily be better than that of the Sunil people. In the end, there was a high chance of the demise of their 'civilization'.

The situation had not yet devolved to such a stage, but Han Xiao was not as optimistic as the rest. While DarkStar had suffered a few losses to him, the other party was still a vicious dog.

Other than the disaster relief, Han Xiao was also following up on Hannes request, asking the Godorans to probe for leads. The other party agreed to it.

The most surprising thing was that Nagakin came to a conclusion extremely quickly, locking onto the identity of the Godoran that Hannes had met.

And the truth of it greatly exceeded their expectations.

Chapter 528: New Clue

"Angora, a pureblood Godoran citizen. Once lived on the mother planet before shifting to Colony Planet Gautin. Single parent family with poor living conditions. Family members passed away. No spouse or relatives. Graduated from a public school. Did not have any full-time jobs, and we only have records of a few part-time jobs. Total working time is less than seven months. Locked up for a few days because of fighting, and the last record of his activity is more than ten years ago..."

In the room, Hannes and Bennett were seated on the opposite as Han Xiao read this document out before passing it over for the two to read. This piece of information had been given to him by Nagakin. By performing a match with the portrait, Godora's AI was able to easily lock onto the target in the database.

In a galactic civilization, details of all the citizens were recorded, and they needed to use their individual ID for all daily activities. All of their activities would also then be fed back into the main database. The storage center of a high-grade civilization would not only be a single database. The database would only be the largest backup, and apart from that, when data was being transmitted to the main database, it would pass by a few relay nodes, and a backup would be made in those nodes. Thus, even if the main database went down, all of the information would not be lost and could easily be retrieved from the relay nodes.

Personal details of the citizens would naturally be confidential information, but with Nagakin's status, it was an extremely easy matter to gain access to the database. According to the law, the personal information of citizens was not allowed to be shown to outsiders. However, rules were dead, whereas people were alive. Nagakin had always wanted to build a good relationship with Black Star, and if Black Star only wanted such a simple piece of information, the upper echelons would also turn a blind eye to the matter. After all, strength gave an individual special privileges.

Of course, Nagakin would also ask why Han Xiao was investigating this person, and Han Xiao did not hide anything from him. He said that a friend had met a foreign Godoran on Planet Aquamarine. As for Hannes' guesses, which did not have any evidence to back it up, there naturally was no need to reveal it.

"It's him alright." After taking a close look at the portrait on the file, Hannes confirmed that this was the mysterious Godoran whom he had met on Planet Aquamarine. Noticing that the picture on the file looked much younger, Hannes could not help but ask, "How old is he?"

"According to his birth date, Angora is already more than ninety years old. The lifespan of a Godoran is roughly 1.5 times yours, but the universe would rarely calculate it as such. With a Life Sustaining Hibernation Chamber, it is possible to greatly slow down one's aging. On the file, it has been a few decades since the last recorded activity, which means that Angora did not use his own ID during this period of time. He was inside a Life Sustaining Hibernation Chamber when you met him, and he may have stayed in Planet Aquamarine for a very long time already," Han Xiao mused as he looked at the file in deep thought.

This file was pretty detailed, and it had records of all of Angora's activities from birth until he went missing. The most unexpected thing was the fact that this file was far too ordinary. Angora seemed like an ordinary galactic resident, and with Godora's productive capacity, the majority of its citizens did not need to work anymore. This was also the problem with the majority of the high-grade civilizations.

They would not starve to death if they did not work, but their lives would not be too good. It was probably because of this that Angora had left the mother planet. While the civilization was able to provide for the unemployed, the unemployed would only have their most basic level of needs fulfilled. If they wanted anything better, they would naturally have to go out and work for it. However, the prices and societal climates of the various planets would very naturally end up eliminating those who did not work.

Colony Planet Gautin was located at the periphery of Godora's territory and was a backward planet. If Godora separated its colonies into ranks, Gautin would definitely be at the lowest rank. It was pretty much the slums of the galaxy.

Bennett frowned and said, "Could the mess on Planet Aquamarine be related to him?"

While Bennett was not familiar with the matters of the galaxy, he still had a basic level of judgement. Not just Han Xiao, even he felt that this was the file of an ordinary individual without anything special.

"It's difficult to say. We can't tell which organization he belongs to." Han Xiao shook his head. "However, we have a new clue now. We can choose to either make a trip to Gautin or get the Six Nations to hand over the hibernation chamber that they obtained. As long as I can check the serial number of the chamber, I will be able to find the seller and continue the investigation."

"Alright, we shall be relying on you then." Hannes nodded.

"I shall go and talk to the Six Nations," Bennett said. With him conveying Han Xiao's intentions, the Six Nations definitely would not reject him. Bennett felt that this was all he could do.

Bennett was also a legendary character who had survived the era of the hundred nations and was extremely curious toward the reason for the situation on Planet Aquamarine developing to such a state.

Han Xiao nodded and took out his communicator. After searching through his contacts, he chose a mercenary who was part of the Sky Ring Army. This mercenary had once been a comrade in arms for one of his missions. Han Xiao requested the other party to help him and sent Angora's details over. The other party immediately agreed to help investigate the matter.

Because Gautin was pretty far away and Han Xiao had things to do on Planet Aquamarine, he did not intend to send out the mercenaries under his charge. Thus, he made use of the network that he had built up to hire another mercenary to investigate the matter on his behalf. Sky Ring had many different businesses, and their efficiency would be much higher.

Two days later, the Six Nations sent the hibernation chamber over. Han Xiao hacked into the system and easily obtained the serial number of the chamber. Not only that, he even found out that the hibernation chamber could access the net. With his current skills, Han Xiao was easily able to hack into the account that was logged into the chamber. However, there were only entertainment programs recorded in the account without anything valuable. Still, Han Xiao sent it over to Sky Ring as a new clue.

Following which, Han Xiao threw that matter to the back of his mind.

He had done what he needed to, and he just did not have many clues. He could only wait for Sky Ring to make some progress.

The situation on Planet Aquamarine was slowly stabilizing. Because Godora knew about the effect of the Mutation Source, they did not take too many detours like in Han Xiao's previous life. More and more refugees were saved, and the size of the Sanctuary expanded rapidly. The construction zone continuously expanded, and despite the new buildings being extremely simple looking, the Sanctuary gradually looked more and more like a city.

With his name being hung up on the Sanctuary, all the refugees who entered the Sanctuary would remember his name. While the mutation virus would act up again in the next phase, gathering all the refugees together would make it much easier for them to suppress the chaos. Even if they did not have sufficient suppressants, they could subdue the refugees with force. At the very least, the number of casualties and fatalities would be far less than in Han Xiao's previous life. It was just that there would be a much higher demand on manpower. Even though Bennett was aware of what might happen in the future, he was still insistent on saving people.

Nagakin's rescue squad, the players, the Sanctuary, and the Six Nations. Everyone was extremely busy during this period, and there were even a few beast attacks.

Han Xiao continued to hire players, and some of the players who had earned Enas began purchasing items from the faction store. However, because the reward from the Godora missions were little, the players had only spent less than 10,000 Enas in his store, and it was far from being enough for him to pay off his debts.

However, Han Xiao was not the slightest bit anxious as this was only the beginning.

Han Xiao had always believed in collective wealth. Only when the players' wallets were full would the buying power of the market increase. As for making the players wealthy, this was something that Han Xiao would not even think of any time soon. After all, it was not easy for the players to earn some money.

Planet Aquamarine was temporarily fine. Before DarkStar took action, Planet Aquamarine would not have any storms. Han Xiao was more concerned about the situation on the other calamity planets. The situation of the calamity was being reported all over the news channels of the Garton Star System, and the citizens of Godora were praying for the rescue squads.

However, a few different voices could also be heard.

"With so many planets falling into calamity at the same time and the symptoms of their illness being similar, this is too much of a coincidence. This matter definitely isn't so simple."

"I heard some rumors that Godora had weapon research facilities on these planets. Their experiments went wrong, which resulted in the weapons being spread out, thus causing the calamity."

"If they wanted to conduct experiments, why didn't they find a planet without any inhabitants? Why would they take the risk and test their weapons on the civilizations of their allies?"

"Indeed, this rumor is too stupid, and it definitely false."

"Not necessarily. If it is a biological weapon, then living beings are needed to conduct an experiment."

"You're thinking too much. It is probably DarkStar behind this matter. They have the technology and enjoy attacking low-grade civilizations in the Garton Star System to create trouble for Godora."

"What if Godora is intentionally pushing this matter onto DarkStar. Such an enemy is a natural target board."

"Ah, how is that possible? You are just spouting nonsense. You will have to take responsibility for your words in the future."

On Godora's web, some of the citizens began guessing wildly. Compared to thinking about proper rescue missions, many of them preferred to come up with ridiculous conspiracy theories. They preferred the excitement brought about by these rumors. However, not too many people would believe such rumors.

At the same time, there were new rumors about the disaster relief operations.

"I have a friend who is part of the disaster relief squad..."

"The 'I have a friend' series has appeared."

"He said that the calamity is too strange, and the upper echelons are completely helpless toward it. They don't know how to solve the problem at its roots and may resort to shifting the entire civilization and receiving the refugees."

"Ah? That can't be right."

"With so many planets, there will be far too many refugees. Shifting so many people will be a huge project, and the upper echelons will probably let those refugees temporarily stay on our colony planets."

"How can that be? I don't want to live together with those backward individuals."

"That's right—they can go to other uninhabited planets. Why do they have to come to our territory and snatch our resources?"

"I can still accept the matter if they are only staying temporarily. I am only afraid that they won't be willing to move away."

"Just throw those refugees onto an uninhabited planet and let them die on their own. Just don't come to Godora."

"That's right. It's enough for us to send out a disaster relief squad. We do not have to take responsibility for them at the end."

All of those opinions had only come out from their imaginations without any concrete evidence. However, it immediately drowned out all the well wishes and prayers for the calamity planets.

Through a small survey conducted, the support that the citizens had toward the disaster relief efforts had also dropped slightly.

All of those rumors appeared very naturally without any signs as though there was something brewing in the darkness.

In the Garton Star System was Colony Planet Gautin, a grayish planet that looked extremely colorless, floating in the darkness of space.

Looking down from outside the atmosphere, the city looked extremely orderly. While it was a lousier Colony Planet, the city would not be dirty or messy. It just was not as prosperous and flashy as the other Colony Planets. Gautin seemed to be dull and grayish without that many golden buildings; Godorans loved the color gold the most.

This situation was because Gautin had outsourced a portion of the city's design to a galactic construction company. As such, the place did not really have the special traits of a Godoran planet. The Godoran citizens who stayed there were naturally those who did not wish to work either.

The planet did not have much wind, and the clouds seemed to be frozen in midair. The moonlight of the artificial moon was not gentle, and the towering buildings were all coated with a layer of light silver paint. All the residential buildings were more than a hundred meters tall, and the windows were all lit up. There seemed to be the warmness of a thousand households being lit up, but those who understood the reason would know that it was because the Godorans who were not willing to work generally enjoyed being holed up at home.

As such, there were not many vehicles on the streets and almost no pedestrians making use of the public flying runes. Only the cleaning robots moved down the streets slowly. While the streets were clean, it was cold and silent.

In a small apartment near the periphery of the city, three Godorans were playing cards and chatting away. They were all pretty old with wrinkles all over their faces. Their figures were plump, and despite the fat on their bodies, it was obvious that they had been pretty fit when they were young.

Chapter 529: Ridiculous Truth (1)

"Have you heard about the news in the Garton Star System?" one of the fat Godorans said with a chuckle. He, Kedan, had an amiable look on his face. He had once been part of Godora's Investigation Department but had been fired because of negligence. He had even stayed in jail for a good few years because of that. After leaving prison, he had migrated to Colony Planet Gautin and had stayed there ever since. The two others beside him were his friends.

"Of course, I've heard the news." Another person shook his head. "The television is reporting how many low-grade civilizations in the Star System are suffering from a calamity."

"It's none of our business at all. Why are you mentioning this? Could it be that you are trying to steal a card while we are distracted?"

"Scram," Kedan said with exasperation before whispering, "Do you still remember what I told you guys about?"

"Which matter?"

"The matter when I was still in the Investigation Department."

"Che, you've bragged about that matter a few hundred times, and we are tired of hearing it."

"Do you know, that planet is currently on the list of calamity planets?" Kedan chuckled. "I wonder how it has developed over the years. I want to go back and take a look. Do you guys want to come with me?"

"Are you sure? That planet isn't safe now."

"The older one becomes, the more one wants to look back at one's past achievements." Kedan chuckled. "Furthermore, I have a friend who stayed behind in that place, so he can receive us and be our guide. Besides, the rescue squad is there, and we can either pretend to be spectators or help with the disaster relief."

As the two of them heard that, their tones became strange.

"That can't be right? He's still on that backward planet? Won't he be bored to death?"

"Are you a fool? His hibernation chamber can be connected to the net, and I have always been in touch with him. He..."

Kedan rubbed his palms with excitement, but just when he was about to continue, the doorbell rang. The sudden ringing of the doorbell caused the three of them to jump up from their seats.

"Who would come at such a time?"

Kedan had a doubtful look on his face as he walked to the door and peered into the peephole. He did not know the few standing outside the door. They were all dressed in combat attire with a ring-shaped emblem on the center of their chest. Kedan felt as though he had definitely seen that emblem before somewhere.

Opening the small window at the top of the door, Kedan showed his face and asked warily, "Who are you guys looking for?"

The other party sized up him up before asking, "Are you Golden Mitland?"

Strange, why would these people know the IGN of my web account? Kedan immediately felt that something was wrong. After denying that he was Golden Mitland, he immediately tried to shut the window. At that moment, the person outside the door raised a laser rifle and pointed it right at Kedan's head.

Kedan's body froze in place, and he did not dare move the slightest bit. His legs began to tremble, and he thought that the other party wanted to rob him. Before he could even plead for mercy, he heard the next question from the other party, which sent shivers down his spine.

"Do you remember Angora?"

"I... I don't know him...." Kedan's eyes widened and his lips trembled. At that moment, the anxiousness that he felt was on a whole different level. It was as though this name had a frightening magic.

The person outside the door shook his head and said, "It's okay even if you don't know him. Follow me if you don't want to suffer."

"To... to where?"

"Black Star wants to see you."

A couple of days later, the Sky Ring spaceship silently waited outside the atmosphere of Planet Aquamarine. Han Xiao piloted the BlackLight Stealth and went up to receive them.

There were only two other people in the control room, Hannes and Bennett, and this was their first time entering the universe in a spaceship. They watched the scenery on the outside in a daze as they enjoyed this novel experience. However, it was a mere few seconds from the surface to outside the atmosphere, and they reached the universe before they could even react.

Han Xiao had left the others waiting on the surface. He was only receiving the members of Sky Ring, so there was no need to make a big fuss out of it. Sky Ring had sent him some good news—they had managed to find Angora's friend through the information that he had provided. This friend seemed to be called Kedan, and he appeared to know about Angora.

The two spaceships were aligned, and the hatch opened up. At that moment, the face of this Godoran was dripping with anxiety, and his eyes were filled with fear.

"Don't be afraid, I only want you to give me some intelligence." Han Xiao took out Angora's portrait and asked, "You know him, right?"

Kedan felt waves in his heart and shook his head vigorously.

"I put him through a lie detector; he is lying," the Sky Ring mercenaries interjected.

"Since you are so afraid, you are probably aware of what went on behind the scenes. Let me ask you directly. Are you related to the war on Planet Aquamarine?" Han Xiao raised his brows and knew that he might have caught the mastermind.

"No! I have never heard of Planet Aquamarine before! You guys caught the wrong person!" Kedan's lips were sealed. However, none of them believed him.

Han Xiao took out a small metal plate that was about the size of a nail and stuck it onto Kedan's neck. He then used his Mechanical Force to activate the metal plate, and Kedan's body began to tremble violently. His eyes turned white, and his entire body shook. With his body contorting on the ground, he lost control of his bowels.

"Let me introduce this item to you." Han Xiao pointed at the metal plate. "When this little cutie is activated, it unleashes a powerful voltage with a good kick. If you like this feeling, you should keep your mouth shut and slowly enjoy it."

An electrical treatment was akin to torture, and the interface showed that Kedan was only an ordinary person, not a Super.

Kedan was like a fish out of water, with his body squirming around. A few minutes later, he finally broke down in tears and promised to share everything that he knew.

Everyone then helped Kedan up and placed him on a chair for him to calm down. At the same time, they put the lie detector apparatus on him. Kedan was still trembling, and he looked at Han Xiao with a guilty expression before narrating what he knew.

"I used to be a low ranked member of the Godora Investigation Department, and that was a few decades ago. At that time, Godora had just found Planet Aquamarine, and the usual practice for a low-grade civilization was to observe their progress. My job was to monitor the progress of this new civilization, give them an evaluation, and submit a report to the Foreign Affairs Department or War Bureau. This job was extremely easy but also very boring..."

"Get to the main point. What has the war in Planet Aquamarine got to do with you?" Hannes pressed.

Kedan began trembling as he said, "That... that was my doing. I made use of my job to send someone to Planet Aquamarine and got him to incite a war in secret..."

"It is indeed related to Godora!" Hannes flew into a rage, and Bennett jumped to his feet.

"Just what exactly did you do?" Han Xiao said with an odd tone.

Kedan then began narrating the process. In summary, he had pretended to be a guest from a high-grade civilization and contacted some nations privately. He had then made a few empty promises to them or emphasized on some theories. In any case, it had been extremely easy to get those backward aboriginals to listen to the words of an alien from a high-grade civilization. He had then fanned the flames in the background.

At that time, Planet Aquamarine had just found out about the presence of a high-grade civilization in the galaxy, and the state of the entire world had fallen into chaos. If nature had been allowed to take its course, there was a chance that the situation would have stabilized on its own, and the nations would have worked together to welcome a new era of peace. This was the most logical thing to do.

But at the critical moment, aliens had fanned the flames from behind the scenes to create conflict between the various nations and light up the flames of war. Even the nations that did not wish to go to war had also been dragged into the storm and could not remain neutral.

In the end, a world war had broken out on Planet Aquamarine, and only the Six Nations had been left behind. While the source of the war had been an exhaustion of resources, the critical factor had been the 'emissary of a high-grade civilization' leading the nations into war.

Before this, Hannes had already made such a guess, and he felt as though his guess had just been verified. Both Bennett and Hannes were extremely furious. They had both been through the world war and could feel their bones turning cold.

The civilization that was currently helping Planet Aquamarine had been the mastermind that schemed against them previously. Why would a galactic civilization want to do such a thing? Did they want to swallow Planet Aquamarine, or did they wish to eliminate all enemies with potential‽

"What about Angora?" Han Xiao asked with a frown.

"He is a childhood friend of mine, and we studied in the same public school. It is just that my results were better, and I managed to get into a school of the Investigation Department. He left the mother planet, and I didn't see him for a long period of time. However, our relationship was still extremely good, and I reached out to him to work together with me. I got him to pretend to be an emissary while I shielded him from my post."

Just when Han Xiao wanted to nod his head, he realized that something was wrong. A cold glare flashed past his eyes and he said, "Why was Angora the one pretending to be an emissary? He's only an ordinary citizen."

He found a dubious point. If Godora was behind this matter, they would definitely have sent a professional. Why would they choose someone like Angora? Could it be that Angora had another identity?

Chapter 530: Ridiculous Truth (2)

Kedan squirmed around uncomfortably before saying, "I mentioned this matter to him, and he found it very interesting. Thus, I brought him along with me..."

Han Xiao felt that the matter becoming more dubious by the second. "What do you mean? Didn't Godora instruct you to do so?"

Kedan paused for a moment and realized that they had misunderstood something. After hesitating for a moment, he thought about the other party's terrifying devices and softly said, "No, this has nothing to do with Godora—it was my personal plan."

Both Hannes and Bennett were completely stunned.

"With such authority in my hands, my day to day life was far too boring. As I was observing the situation of Planet Aquamarine, a flash of inspiration suddenly struck me, and I wanted to treat Planet Aquamarine like a sandbox for me to play around with. After all, it was extremely easy for me to play around with a backward civilization, and there weren't any risks involved. Because the upper echelons weren't bothered by the civil war of a low-grade civilization, I wanted to create a war and see all of you fight because of me. I felt that it was extremely interesting. After thinking about it, I immediately carried out my plan.

"Angora worked together with me for this, and he chose to stay on Planet Aquamarine in the end. He felt that there wasn't any meaning to return to Godora and chose to stay on the backward planet to personally witness the outcome of his actions. He felt that this was an extremely interesting matter as well."

After Kedan finished his words, the entire place fell silent. The lie detector machine did not give out an alarm, which meant that everything Kedan said was true.

Hannes and Bennett were thoroughly dumbfounded.

Wasn't this a plan of the Godoran Civilization?

Was it really only because someone felt bored?

"Impossible!" Hannes lost control. "You are only an ordinary individual. If Godora wasn't involved, how could two ordinary individuals accomplish such a matter‽"

Kedan shrunk back and said meekly, "It is extremely simple actually. No one suspected that the emissary was a fake because we are truly Godorans."

Hannes was completely stunned. He had thought that it was impossible for two ordinary individuals to cause the entire planet to devolve into war, but he was speechless at this moment.

That's right, they are Godorans.

That is enough...

Because Godora was a high-grade civilization, Godoran's were also 'high grade'. Who would suspect them?

Bennett's face turned cold, and he grabbed Kedan's collar. Countless families had been ruined in the war, and it was all because two people had found it amusing. Looking at Kedan's eyes, which were filled with anxiety and fear but not a single trace of guilt, the words that were about to come out from Bennett's mouth were swallowed back.

At that time, Planet Aquamarine was probably like an ants' nest in the eyes of the Godorans. How was playing around with ants a crime?

Han Xiao had a strange look on his face, and he found the truth to be extremely ridiculous.

He had thought that there was a mysterious organization stirring up chaos from the dark, but the truth was completely out of his expectations. There was not a single organization that would even think of scheming against a weak civilization like Planet Aquamarine. The only reason was because an audacious fool had sadistic tendencies. There was no scheming or conspiracies. It was just that simple a reason.

A small figure in Godora had felt bored and incited a war for his own amusement. After the show ended, he had acted as though nothing had happened. In the end, because of the authority that he had in his job and Godora's indifference toward Planet Aquamarine, he had managed to hide this matter for a few decades.

Someone like Angora who was a failure in his own society had chosen to bully the weak and display his superiority in a backward planet as enjoyment.

The only thing that those two individuals had relied on was their gold-colored skin.

The truth was so simple and ridiculous and yet so desolate.

Because they were weak, they were reduced to playthings.

This made Han Xiao feel as though Planet Aquamarine was like a virtuous young lady being raped by a little brat of a wealthy family, unable to even have the thought of resisting.

To Planet Aquamarine, this was a calamity that they did not deserve.

While Han Xiao did not have any attachment to Planet Aquamarine and was not someone who would be affected emotionally, he was truly a little frustrated. However, his frustration was directed toward Godora. After all, the crime of the Godoran civilization in this matter was probably that they were too powerful. Perhaps it was their strength that gave them a sense of superiority.

"How... ridiculous." Han Xiao let out a long breath filled with complicated emotions.

Despite a notification popping up on his interface that he had completed the hidden ranked A mission, he didn't have the mood to check it immediately.

The mercenaries from Sky Ring left without Kedan. He was knocked unconscious and locked up in a cage. Han Xiao then allowed Bennett to deal with Kedan as he wished.

Both Bennett and Hannes felt that it was extremely difficult for them to accept this truth. The decades of change on Planet Aquamarine had all been because of this ridiculous reason. All of the suffering that they had gone through suddenly seemed so meaningless. An entire civilization had been toyed with by two aliens.

Their planet could have been much better.

"Don't think too much. If this is the truth, we have no choice but to accept it." Han Xiao shook his head.

Bennett lowered his head and did not know what to say. He then stood up abruptly and looked at Han Xiao with seriousness.

"While I didn't interrupt you when you were negotiating with the Six Nations, I felt uncomfortable in my heart. However, I was wrong." Bennett clenched his fists tightly. "I finally understand your efforts. It is a crime to be weak! You didn't go into the universe just for the solution to the calamity. You also went into the universe for the future of Planet Aquamarine! You are far nobler than me!"

Han Xiao's mouth began to cramp up. Since when did he have such thoughts?

Could it be that the higher the Favorability, the more vivid one's imagination would be‽

"If not for you, this planet would still be in the dark. I thank you on behalf of Planet Aquamarine." Bennett gave a bow. As Hannes heard those words, he also stood up and bowed toward Han Xiao.

"Don't be like this... You guys are making me feel as though I am good guy," Han Xiao said with a helpless tone. His actions were out of his own interests but had an unexpectedly good outcome.

He had never felt that he was a good person. Just like now, he was already thinking of how to make full use of Kedan.

At the same time in Black Phantom Sanctuary, the players were excitedly carrying out the disaster relief missions, and a new round of the Black Star Mercenary Group selection was underway. The sound of fighting and cheering could be heard from afar. Many of the refugees who had been injected with the suppressant finally had hope toward life again, and despite the planet being overwhelmed with calamity, the entire Sanctuary was filled with energy.

In the sky, a couple of Godora spaceships were hovering, and Nagakin looked down at the plaza in deep thought.

His assistant by the side asked, "Your Excellency Nagakin, what do you think of these Inhumans?"

"Full of potential." Nagakin nodded. After a few days of observation, he had already noticed the players' potential. From the slight importance that he had attached to them at the beginning, he paid close attention to them now.

With the unexpected surprise of the Inhumans, Nagakin felt that the objective of his mission should not be disaster relief.

While Godora had sent troops over to aid Planet Aquamarine, this did not mean that they would be overly invested in a low-grade civilization like Planet Aquamarine. The way Nagakin saw it, those Inhumans would be able to bring him much greater benefits.

"There are plenty of Inhumans, and there are more than a million on the entire planet. There are so many Super, and all of them have the potential to grow. This is a force that shouldn't be underestimated," the assistant said.

"That's right. We should begin engaging the Inhumans... There is value in roping them in."

"What do you want to do?"

"Issue a recruitment notice, just like Black Star. Godora should be far more attractive than a single Mercenary Group."

Nagakin made his decision. While he respected Black Star's strength, with such a large group of Supers before his eyes, he could not ignore their presence and wanted a slice of the cake.

Even if the Inhumans were from Black Star's hometown, Nagakin would not allow Black Star to swallow the entire cake alone.

Chapter 531: Advancement, Virtual Mechanic!

As for how they should deal with Kedan, both Bennett and Hannes still had no idea. Naturally, Han Xiao recognized that Kedan had value and felt that he should be exploited.

Kedan was a Godoran citizen, and the act of kidnapping him had some risks. Thankfully, Kedan was only a member of Colony Planet Gautin, which was in the periphery of society. Sky Ring had taken some effort to bring him over, but according to them, there had been two others present. Since the mission had not been carried out by Han Xiao personally, there would definitely be many loopholes.

There would be some risks in keeping Kedan. Even if he was a sloth who did not work, Godora would still protect their citizens. However, Han Xiao definitely would not let him go so easily. While Kedan's actions had violated the Godoran law and he would be sentenced when he returned, Godora definitely would not compensate Planet Aquamarine.

However, in a galactic generation, the movement of people from planet to planet was far too rapid. Furthermore, many citizens would not stay in the colonies but take a spaceship to the other Star Systems. The gigantic and complicated distribution of the Godoran population meant that the Public Security Office was laxer in managing them. A member living in one of the periphery colonies being kidnapped was only a small matter, and the local Public Security Office would not have the manpower to give chase into the universe. They would definitely send the matter to their higher ups with the case being handled in an extremely inefficient manner.

As long as Godora could not find the person, this kidnapping incident would be over. After all, it was only an ordinary citizen going missing. It was impossible for Godora to invest a large amount of resources to search for him in the universe. If they were unable to find him after some time, the case would just be closed as an unresolved case. The Sky Ring mercenaries had turned on their anti-tracking devices after boarding the spaceship, and it would be difficult to track them after entering hyperdrive. Thankfully, they were not complete pig like teammates, so Han Xiao was extremely grateful.

"You made me think about my hometown." Risda voice suddenly sounded in the control room.

"Both filled with desolation, right?" Han Xiao shook his head.

"At least there is still hope." After saying that, Risda fell silent. He had always been in the BlackLight Stealth and controlling the spaceship but did not like to show himself.

Risda allowed Han Xiao to use his body as Han Xiao pleased and had always been very cooperative. Han Xiao did not let Phillip control the spaceship either. When comparing the ability of the two, Risda was naturally far superior to Phillip as he was an AI lifeform.

The BlackLight Stealth landed in the Sanctuary, and Han Xiao instructed Bennett not to kill Kedan temporarily.

Han Xiao first checked on the progress of the recruitment before checking on Sylvia's homework. He then returned to his own living quarters to check the mission reward, which he received. He had received more than 8,000,000 experience points, a chance to draw a Random Reward that he did not plan on using yet, two Free Attribute Points, and one Potential Point. A high ranked mission would tend to reward him with attribute points.

The best reward was naturally the Medal of Honor, which provided him with a three percent increase to all attributes.

_____________________

You have received [Medal of Honor – Seeker of History (A)].

_____________________

This item was like a Character Summon Card and would immediately take effect on the interface. He still had the Medal of Honor from the Germinal Organization and Sanctuary's mission. All three medals had the same effects, but the effects could not be stacked. Only when he gathered three Medal of Honors would he be able to exchange them for a special medal that could increase all his attributes by twelve percent. Since he had obtained the third Medal of Honor, Han Xiao immediately changed the medals into the special medal. This was akin to having a permanent buff.

After checking his reward, Han Xiao opened up his attribute interface. It was a good day, and he had finally completed the Energy Training Technique that Harmon had given to him. His Energy Level had broken the 9,000 points barrier, and he had finally entered the next level.

_____________________

Energy Attribute: [Magnetic] - Increases Machinery Affinity.

Energy [Lv10]: +18 STR, +25 DEX, +28 END, +32 INT, +22 MYS, +3400 Stamina Limit, +25% Machinery Affinity

_____________________

Just this level of attributes was enough to increase his total Energy Level by a third. The higher his Energy Level, the more significant the bonus.

The Promotion Mission [Energy Secret] had been completed, and the Class Advancement requirement was for him to choose a specialty between large sized machineries, nanotechnologies, or virtual technology. The method of doing so would be to raise the relevant High-End Knowledge to the maximum level.

Between the Armed, Energy, and Control Branch, Han Xiao had not bought [Super Nanometer Force]. However, Han Xiao was planning to choose the Virtual Technology branch, so that did not affect him.

The Virtual Technology branch focused on infiltration and defense. It was extremely powerful in a battle between Mechanics. Basically, it followed the philosophy of 'what is yours is mine, and what is mine is still mine'. Even if he was not able to infiltrate the other party's machines, he would be able to stop the other party from infiltrating his own machine.

Furthermore, Virtual Technology also supported the Army Style. The more powerful one's abilities, the larger the army he could control. He was not the only person in the galaxy who would construct a Mechanic Army, and those who specialized in Virtual Technology would be able to restrict the Army Style to a certain extent.

Of course, Virtual Technology also had its own weaknesses. When facing those not of the Mechanic class, they did not have the strength of those who walked down the path of nanotechnology or large sized machinery. After all, the strengths of the two other paths was extremely obvious. Their combat strength was the priority, and their focus would be to increase the strength of their machines.

In his previous life, Han Xiao had also played the two different paths before. By creating more powerful machines, he only needed to send his machine out, sit back, and relax.

Of course, this was an exaggeration. The Mechanics from these two paths would still have to control the battle; ignoring the battle completely would be the action of a lazy player.

In his previous life, most of the players had chosen these two paths because the path of Virtual Technology was far too difficult to take.

Most importantly, even if the players did not choose the Army Style, those from the large sized machinery and nanotechnology route would have other powerful means. However, the most suitable strategy for those on the Virtual Technology would be the Army Style.

Most players enjoyed the most cost-efficient method of battle. After all, it was not easy for them to earn money, and the Army Style was not something that a poor peasant could play!

Through Han Xiao's personal experience, the Virtual Technology path was the most useful one. While the strength of the Virtual Technology path was not that obvious, the Virtual Technology path was the most stable in actual battle. There was an advantage when fighting other Mechanics, and it was not too weak when dealing with opponents of other classes. After all, it was still of the Mechanic Class and had its foundations.

Han Xiao did not chase after the highest attribute a single machine could have. What he did not have in quality could be made up for in quantity. With the large market of the players, he was not afraid of the matter of costs. Compared to improving his strengths, Han Xiao preferred to make up for his weaknesses.

As long as he had sufficient experience, he could raise the levels of his blueprints and skills up to an extremely high level. As such, the quality of his machines would not lose out to those from the other two paths.

Besides, there was also a personal reason for him choosing the Virtual Technology path.

After determining his path, Han Xiao threw his Potential Points into the relevant Knowledge, and notifications began popping up on his interface.

_____________________

You have completed LV 120 Promotion.

END Attribute Boost enhanced. 1 END = 65 Max Health = 75 Stamina

_____________________

The advancement this time gave me a larger attribute boost to my health. At the very start, the increase was only 5 points. During my first Race Evolution, the increase was 10 points. Now, the increase is actually 15 points. The previous ratio of 1:50 had been increased to 1:65 now.

Han Xiao clenched his fists and took a deep breath. The familiar sense of pain appeared again, but compared to the pain that he had felt when he became a Void Prowler, this pain could only make him frown slightly.

_____________________

[Advanced Artificial Intelligence Technology] reached Lv.5 (max), Class Advancement Succeed!

You have received a new class [Virtual Mechanic Lv.1]. +150 Energy, +3 DEX, +3 END, +6 INT. You have received 6 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

You have learned [Professional Machinery Affinity]!

You have learned [Strengthened Smart Defense]!

You have learned [Strengthened Smart Control]!

You have learned [Strengthened Hacking]!

You have learned [Optimized Resource Allocation]!

You have learned [Optimized Mass Production Configuration]!

You have learned [Virtual Technology Essence]!

_____________________

All his new skills had basically strengthened the skills relating to Virtual Technology. Hacking and virtual defense were the core of this path.

[Strengthened Smart Control] was capable of increasing the attributes of an independent machine, and the skill introduction was: 'An excellent smart system which increases the efficiency of a machine.'

Both [Optimized Resource Allocation] and [Optimized Mass Production Configuration] were able to increase the efficiency of his assembly line. The former would lower his costs, and the latter would increase his manufacturing speed. The Virtual Technology path would provide a large increase toward the overall productive capacity of an assembly line and was extremely suitable for the Army Style.

[Professional Machinery Affinity] was the core skill of a Mechanic, and it would provide an additional sixty percent Machinery Affinity when raised to the maximum level. [Virtual Technology Essence] gave an additional bonus to all Virtual Technology related skills based on one's Intelligence and was similar to [Machinery Analytical Comprehension].

Because this was a Class Advancement that determined his class route, he had learned more skills than before. In fact, these skills were even more important than the increase in level. Without any hesitation, Han Xiao immediately raised all the skills up to their maximum levels and obtained the best result.

He had obtained more than 3,000,000,000 experience points from the players, and just raising those skills to their maximum level burnt away more than 1,000,000,000 experience points.

The investment was definitely worth it, and the result was obvious. His combat power had risen by a full 800 Ona, and the boost in combat power that leveling the skills gave him was more than the effect of leveling up.

He still had 2,200,000,000 experience points. At his current level, raising the level of his main class also required a large amount of experience. But similarly, the amount of experience that the players could gain from missions had also increased.

Only Han Xiao would be able to gather such a large amount of experience in such a short period of time.

All of his experience was placed into leveling up, and his main class leveled up four times. While his remaining experience was enough for him to level up once more, Han Xiao did not continue leveling his main class. Instead, he spent his experience points on his [Scholar] subclass, raising it from Lv.5 to its max level, Lv.10. After that, he was left with less than 100,000,000 experience points, which was not enough for him to level up again.

While the experience required to level up a subclass would increase with each level, the amount of experience required would still be less than leveling a main class. The attributes of the [Scholar] subclass were still pretty useful, and Han Xiao gained 50 more Intelligence and 5 more potential points.

His [Virtual Mechanic] class was increased to Lv.5 and gave him an additional 15 Dexterity, 15 Endurance, 30 Intelligence, 30 Free Attribute Points, and 5 Potential Points.

He threw all of his Free Attribute Points into Intelligence as usual.

His energy surged within him, and bearing with the discomfort, Han Xiao checked the change in his attributes.

_____________________

Level: 130

Main Class: Mechanic

Race: Void Prowler (Human Form)

Attributes: 181 STR, 401 DEX, 361 END, 1110 INT, 124 MYS, 41 CHA, 1 LUK

Free Attribute Points: 0

Potential Points: 49

Health: 37,824

Stamina: 37,995

Energy: 9,770 [Lv.10]

[Lv.10 Energy bonus stats: +71 STR, +97 DEX, +108 END, +122 INT, +77 MYS, +10,920 Stamina Limit, +85% Machinery Affinity]

Power Level: 8,945 Ona

Grade: B+

Remark: You are a powerful galactic Mechanic and an elite among elites. The biggest difference between you and other Grade B Supers is that additional '+'.

_____________________

Heh, this note is truly cheeky.

Level 130, and my power level is close to 9,000 Ona. This means that if I get to level 140 and complete my Promotion, I should be able to enter into the ranks of a Grade A Super and gain the destructive force of a calamity.

Han Xiao ran calculations on his stats in his heart. While his level increased quickly, he did not forget about leveling his skills. Furthermore, the skills that he had leveled up were mostly the skills of his main class. Thus, his advancement rate was about twenty to thirty levels ahead of the players, and his actual combat capability was above the average of his level. In fact, he would be able to sweep aside the majority of the Grade B Supers.

If he faced Ember right now, even if he did not make any preparations beforehand, he would be able to last in a battle against Ember.

Even if he could not win, he would be able to disgust the other party to death.

Especially the amount of Health that he had. Every time he saw this figure, Han Xiao could feel his forehead turn numb. When he was at this level in his previous life, the Health of a Mechanic had been less than 20,000 points. Even the main tanks of the same level would not have as much Health as him!

His [Intermediate Strengthened Life] Molding Talent was truly too ferocious. If he could raise the level of this Molding Talent again, everyone would probably puke blood from just seeing his Health.

Going up from level 130 to level 140 would require a few billion experience points, but the experience that he had harvested from the players was almost all spent. He would still be able to earn around one billion experience points from the players by selling his skills, and he would have to find a new way to harvest the players after that.

With the new version having been out for so many days, the experience points of the players had basically been spent. Han Xiao would have to wait for them to accumulate a new batch of experience points.

It seems like I will still need some time. Han Xiao was already extremely satisfied. At his level, he could not possibly hope to increase twenty levels in one go.

The discomfort that he felt had lasted for more than an hour before finally subsiding. Han Xiao let out a long breath as he felt the sensation of being filled with strength. He was feeling extremely hungry, and only after eating a few dozen energy bars was his hunger slightly sated.

He took off his sweat-drenched shirt and looked down at his well-toned muscles. Following which, he changed into a set of clean clothes before putting on all the compressed orbs again.

Beep beep!

At that moment, his communicator suddenly rang; Herlous was calling.

"If you are calling to show off your new arm, we can end the call here." Han Xiao raised his brows.

"Nope, it's something serious this time." Herlous frowned. "Nagakin had issued a recruitment notice toward the Inhumans, and many Inhumans are crowding over to take a look..."

The way Herlous saw it, the players were all good helpers who could aid Sunil in their catastrophe. However, Godora had actually tried to take a slice of the cake, and Herlous was immediately incensed.

"Oh?" Han Xiao revealed an 'I knew it' smile and chuckled. "Hehe, since you are heartless, don't blame me for being unscrupulous. I shall go and take a look."

Chapter 532: Openly Poaching

At that moment, the Six Nations received a request from Bennett to open a video conference again. With the special status of the Sanctuary, the leaders of the Six Nations placed huge importance on the Sanctuary and took time out of their busy schedules to hold the meeting.

Once all the leaders had come online, they saw a silent, solemn Bennett, and the entire atmosphere immediately became serious. The leaders of the Six Nations were extremely curious about what Bennett wanted to talk to them about.

Not too long later, someone asked, "Bennett, what's the matter?"

"Everyone, I am going to tell all of you about a lie that we have been living in for the past few decades," Bennett said slowly, and all the leaders were puzzled. However, as Bennett began to narrate what he had just learned, the faces of all the leaders changed.

In order to verify what he had just said, Hannes brought Kedan over and interrogated him in front of the Six Nations' leaders. Kedan naturally spilled out everything that he knew without missing a single detail. The leaders listened carefully, and all of their faces turned ashen. The poker faces that they had trained over the past few years were also shattered, and traces of rage could be seen on all of their faces.

"This is the truth of the matter, and the entire planet has been played like a fool. If not for Han Xiao, we would have been kept in the dark forever..." Bennett clenched his fists and gritted his teeth.

Han Xiao did not know what was going on in the secret conference room, and Bennett was contacting the Six Nations behind his back. However, apart from keeping Kedan alive, Han Xiao did not have any other requests, so it could be said that he had approved tacitly.

"All of these years, we..." a hoarse voice murmured.

The gazes of the Six Nations were complicated. While this was the truth, they were the final victors of the warring era and did not regret anything that they had done. However, when they thought back to the miserable scene of corpses littering the earth accompanied by the sound of explosions, their hearts were filled with sorrow.

The victors are kings, and losers vilified. There was no point talking about winning or losing, but to think that there was such despicable scum at work behind the scenes. They could not help but feel a sense of desolation that ran deep within their bones. So what if they were the leaders of Planet Aquamarine? To the high-grade civilizations, they were no more than ants fighting each other. Regardless of how heroic they were on the battlefield and whether or not they were the victors, they were still ants.

Despite knowing the truth, they had no way to seek justice.

All of their feelings toward Godora completely changed at that moment. Their rationality was not affected, and they understood that Godora was still a civilization that they had to look up to and rely on to tide through the calamity. However, the thoughts in the depths of their hearts had been changed forever.

Bennett took in a deep breath and solemnly said, "When Black Star was negotiating with all of you the last time, I was standing behind him. In truth, I didn't agree with his thoughts at that time. However, I finally understand his thoughts now. He has long understood the fact that we will only be toyed with by others if we remain weak. I do not know how sincere all of you were when submitting to him back then, but I feel that all of you should understand our reality right now..."

All the leaders fell silent, and they were suddenly reminded of a scene from not too long ago. After putting in a great deal of effort to put up a grand welcoming ceremony and confirming the landing coordinates with the Godoran disaster relief squad much earlier on, the other party had changed their landing coordinates at the very last moment and thrown them aside for Black Star.

In truth, this was only a small matter, and while the leaders of the Six Nations had been dissatisfied, it was only dissatisfaction. However, together with the truth that Bennett had told them, this 'small matter' had a completely different feeling.

We aren't sufficiently respected after all.

"I will stand beside him forever," Bennett said with a resolute tone. "If he is disappointed in all of you one day, I will take over your positions as the ruler of the planet. All of you are extremely clear that this has nothing to do with ambition."

"We understand!"

The leaders of the Six Nations nodded slowly and were extremely clear on the weight of those words. Bennett was not chasing after his ambition but the hope of their civilization.

"Just as Black Star said, he is our only choice. He is the only one who can bring us the future."

"Don't worry, we know what to do."

The leaders of the Six Nations all spoke with sincerity. This time, they truly did not have any other thoughts. With the future of their civilization at stake, they were willing to completely submit to Han Xiao.

It was not the slightest bit forced, and there were no feelings of discomfort in their hearts. The leaders of the Six Nations only felt thankful.

They were thankful that a legendary character like Black Star could appear on Planet Aquamarine, rewriting the history of an entire civilization with the strength of a single person.

The sun was blazing, and the Sanctuary was filled with commotion.

Han Xiao slowly walked toward Nagakin and did not know that Bennett had secretly provided him huge support without him knowing. Not too long ago, Herlous had given him a call and said that Godora was trying to snatch a slice of his cake. He was currently going to see how Nagakin intended to recruit the players.

They do not understand the nature of the players. To them, the players are only special aboriginals. If they use ordinary methods, the players probably won't respond to them at all... Han Xiao shook his head and snickered. Godora did not understand the habits and thoughts of the players as well as he did.

The Sanctuary had demarcated a region for Godora's disaster relief squad, and this region was now completely surrounded by the players. The recruitment notice that Godora had issued had attracted a large number of curious players.

"Planet Aquamarine, which all of you are on, belongs to Star Zone 9 of the Garton Star System. The Godoran Civilization is the ruler of the Garton Star System with experts as many as the clouds. We have superior magical technology in our grasp and can come and go in the universe freely..."

Some Godorans were currently explaining the situation of their civilization, aided by various different films. This was Nagakin's plan. He decided to first let those aboriginals understand the situation of the galaxy and let the other party understand how powerful their Godoran Civilization was. Through displaying their strength, they would be able to paint those Planet Aquamarine Inhumans a clear picture of the galaxy so that they could attract them.

Nagakin observed the recruitment from the side. While his idea was good, and there was nothing wrong with it, the actual situation was completely out of his expectations.

The Inhumans were not the slightest bit curious about the situation of the galaxy and did not have any yearning toward Godora. Instead, they looked slightly bored.

"That's not right. Why aren't they interested?" Nagakin was slightly depressed.

The players watching by the side were completely unmoved. While Nagakin's plan would have been extremely effective against ordinary aboriginals, it was completely useless toward the players.

At least eighty to ninety percent of those present had watched Bun-Hit-Dog's footage before. Not to mention Godora, they probably understood the majority of the Shattered Star Ring. The information that the Godorans were sharing was no longer anything new to them.

Nagakin was completely puzzled and naturally did not know where the problem lay. After the Godoran spokesperson finished his introduction of their Godoran Civilization, he began describing the strength of their technology and various different magical and technological products. It was obviously with the intention of showing off their strength.

After the players watched for a while, they shook their heads, and the crowd began to disperse.

"So boring, let's go."

"What's so special about all these things. Do you think that we are some country villagers?"

"Cheh. They truly haven't seen the vastness of the world."

Seeing this scene, Nagakin and the Godoran spokesperson were dumbfounded. They thought that the Inhumans were aboriginals from a backward planet who had not seen the world, but in the eyes of the players, it was instead these Godorans who had not seen the world.

Trying to fool us with these items. Do you really think we have never seen magic or technology‽

We have seen a floating continent in the universe, and Godora actually showed this to us‽

What a joke!

If Han Xiao was here, he would definitely have burst into laughter.

What's the use of all these things? You might as well issue them a mission instead. If you don't take out some benefits, why would the players bother with you?

However, that was only the thought of the majority, and there were still some players who were curious and thought of joining the Godora Faction. It was not because they were attracted by Godora but because they wanted to try and see if they could join two factions.

Nagakin's recruitment process was different from that of the Black Star Mercenary Group. After all, Godora had their own procedures, and the recruitment process was more complicated.

There were already some players who had begun asking how they could join, but right at that moment, a loud commotion broke out not too far away, and the gazes of the players were immediately drawn to the commotion.

Upon seeing Han Xiao being surrounded by players, all of those players threw Godora aside and rushed over to Han Xiao.

In the eyes of the players, Han Xiao's appearance was basically tied to the appearance of benefits. Every time he appeared, he would definitely create a commotion, and he had left a deep impression on the players. His popularity was also something that Godora would not be able to compare to.

The Godoran camp had already been quieting down, but it was now completely deserted. The faces of the Godorans all turned dark. Since when had they been treated in such a manner before? They had actually been ignored by a bunch of aboriginals, and many of them were fuming.

Nagakin's face contorted slightly, and a depressed look could be seen on his face. The scene before him was completely different from what he had expected, and he truly felt the difference in popularity.

"That's right. Black Star is from this planet, so he should be more popular."

Nagakin would not give up like that. While the start had been exceptionally poor, he believed that there would be many who were willing to join Godora's side. After all, Godora was a high-grade civilization, which was not something that an ordinary mercenary group could compare to.

He believed that as long as he continued to explain Godora's situation to the Inhumans, many of them would make the right choice.

While he was trying to poach players from Black Star, Nagakin did not think that anything was wrong with his actions. After all, the Inhumans were all free to choose. Both of them had the right to recruit the Inhumans, and they were competing on equal grounds. He would not be dissatisfied with Black Star because of this and thus felt that Black Star would not be angry over the matter either.

Seeing Han Xiao appear, Nagakin walked forward with a smile.

Chapter 533: Not Angry, Not Angry At All

After a short, casual conversation, Han Xiao followed Nagakin into the Godoran camp and shook off the crowd of players. He did not wish for the players to hear his conversation with Nagakin.

While the players could move about in the Godoran camp, the core region of the camp was not open to them, so the Godoran troops stopped the players outside.

Walking into the room, both of them sat down.

"How is the disaster relief going?" Han Xiao asked with a smile.

"The situation is improving, and order is gradually being restored. Your information was a huge help. Not just on Planet Aquamarine, the disaster relief squads on the other calamity planets have acted according to your information, and the situation is stabilizing. As long as they can control the effect of the calamity, we only need to wait for the research department to develop an antidote."

Upon talking about serious matters, Nagakin's face became stern.

Following which, both of them discussed the disaster relief operation on Planet Aquamarine. They discussed the problems that Nagakin was currently facing, their management problems, and so on. After a long conversation, Han Xiao suddenly said, "Right, I saw you recruiting people on my way over."

"Haha, that's right," Nagakin said in a straightforward manner and did not attempt to hide anything. "I never expected such a strange phenomenon to occur on Planet Aquamarine. After a period of observation, I noticed that they are all full of potential. No wonder you wanted to recruit them. I am also prepared to recruit some Inhumans."

Han Xiao stroked his chin and did not show any emotion. "Hmm, I have long known about the Inhumans. Your Observer didn't understand their situation, and upon seeing that they behaved like ordinary humans, he decided to ignore them entirely. Indeed, they are full of potential, and their numbers are not to be underestimated."

"That's right, your prestige is extremely high among the Inhumans. Can you help me?" Nagakin's eyes lit up, and he felt that he could seek Black Star for help.

He had seen that the Black Star Mercenary Group did not accept everyone who applied and was holding a selection instead. Thus, he thought that Black Star did not intend to dominate the entire market of Inhumans. As such, he felt that Black Star would not be angry, and upon seeing Han Xiao's calm reaction, Nagakin felt that his thoughts were confirmed. As such, he had approached Han Xiao for help.

Han Xiao immediately had a strange look on his face. Don't go too far, alright? Not only are you trying to poach the players, you still want me to teach you how to poach them well!

Han Xiao then nodded and said, "I can give you some advice, but I can't guarantee the effects of my advice. After all, the Inhumans aren't my subordinates."

Nagakin thought for a moment before saying, "What method did you use to get so many Inhumans to be interested in your mercenary group?"

"Nothing much actually. I pretty much did the same thing as you. I introduced the background of my mercenary group, the situation of the galaxy, and some of the benefits they can get. The rest was up to the choice of the Inhumans. As long as you explain Godora's background, I believe that you will be able to attract some of them."

"I think so, too." Nagakin nodded. His method was not wrong. It was just that Black Star had the initiative.

Since he was going in the right direction, Nagakin did not intend to change his plan. Compared to joining a mercenary group, joining Godora should be a much better choice. It seemed like he only needed to give the Inhumans some time to understand Godora better.

After another few sentences, Han Xiao bade farewell and walked out of the Godoran camp with a chuckle.

Nagakin's guess was right; he was not angry at all. He had known all along that Godora would be his competitor, and Nagakin's actions were within his expectations. Originally, DarkStar would also have been another competitor, but because of the Germinal Organization's destruction, DarkStar would not appear for the time being. With him being tied onto the same boat as Godora, it was almost akin to DarkStar being eliminated from the picture, so he had one less competitor.

Han Xiao was extremely clear that there was nothing special about Nagakin's recruitment process. It was just like what he was doing, introducing his own background to the players. It was just that, in his previous life, the players could only choose between righteous and evil. However, in this life, the players had a new camp to choose from, and thus, Godora was not able to monopolize the market.

After he built up a strong rapport with the players over time, it was a dream for Nagakin to shake his position in the players' hearts so easily.

Even if Godora was able to give the players benefits, they still would not be able to compete with him. The many videos that Bun-Hit-Dog had posted had a huge effect on the players. The videos allowed the players to fully understand the Black Star Mercenary Group and also look forward to joining the mercenary group. The effect of the video series that Bun-Hit-Dog had produced allowed the players to form a sense of belonging to the mercenary group.

In terms of benefits, he had the advantage. In terms of feelings, he had the advantage. In terms of interest, he still had the advantage. He had the advantages in every area, and Nagakin still did not know why he had lost.

Because of sufficient preparations, Han Xiao did not even need to take action personally, and Godora would not be able to shake his position in the players' hearts.

Furthermore, the players could indeed join two different factions. The way Han Xiao saw it, their true choice would be made when it was time to leave the planet. At that time, the players would have to choose who they wanted to follow. Thus, Han Xiao was not anxious yet.

When the players had to make a choice between the two, he would definitely have the advantage. Together with the effect of the crowd, more players would select him for sure, which was as good as moving the Players' Main City!

At that time, the Godoran camp would definitely be cold and desolate.

However, Han Xiao would never fuss over having too many schemes. Even if his advantage was obvious, he would not ignore the situation and started to think about a plan to deal with Godora.

I am still in an alliance with Godora, so I cannot drop all pretenses. That would be far too irrational. While Godora's competitiveness still cannot be compared to mine, of the many different types of players, some will choose them for sure. However, this isn't too big a concern. It is enough for my recruitment to achieve the intended effect. Hmm, after this is over, I can set up a branch on Planet Aquamarine, and I will have a never ending supply of new blood in the future.

Han Xiao stroked his chin and thought of two different methods to deal with the situation.

First, I should increase my attractiveness to the players. The players already more or less understand the benefits that I can bring to them, but there is still room for improvement. If I want to get the players to follow the mercenary group into the galaxy, I must first make them reluctant to part with me. Heh, there is actually a very simple way.

Letting out a light chuckle, Han Xiao immediately formed a plan. Just like how the Sky Ring Army had different ranks, he could also create a ranking system in the Black Star Mercenary Group.

When the player's contribution points reach a certain level, including the contribution points that they spent in the faction shop, they could reach a new rank. He would give those different ranks a different glorious title and record them in the player's mercenary file.

Apart from giving the players a sense of achievement, there would be practical benefits that came along with the ranks. For example, they would be able to get different discount levels in the faction store at different ranks. As such, the players would not be willing to give up their previous accumulations, with the main reason being that they could not part with the money that they had spent earlier. This way, their sense of belonging to the faction would also be increased.

An achievement ranking is an important key to the success of a faction. It's akin to the ranking structure within the organization. I should get it settled soon so that it will be easy to manage the faction in the future. I still have to think of a cool name for the ranks.

Han Xiao clicked his tongue in a good mood. As for coming up with names, it was something that he was the best at.

Apart from increasing his own attractiveness, the other plan would naturally be to deal a blow to the opponent.

Since he could not drop all pretenses with Godora, he could only choose to stab them in the back. His choice of weapon? Public opinion.

Han Xiao immediately picked his target.

The player forum was the best platform to deal a blow to Godora's image. The forum was something that only the players could see, and even if he stabbed Godora in the back, they would not know what was going on.

Han Xiao then let out a cunning smile. It seems like I have to make use of Bun-Hit-Dog.

That night, at the core region of the Sanctuary, a group of players were currently rushing over to Han Xiao's living quarters. The ones who had received the notification were Frenzied Sword, Bun-Hit-Dog, Hao Tian, and Maple Moon. They were the four who had met Han Xiao the earliest.

"I wonder why Black Star has summoned us so suddenly."

Not too long ago, they had received a faction mission on their interface, instructing them to immediately meet Han Xiao. Since the reward of the mission was plentiful, the few of them had not delayed in the slightest and gone to find Han Xiao immediately.

When they reached the appointed location, a black dressed Han Xiao appeared in front of them and nodded emotionlessly. After greeting them, he took the four of them through a series of winding corridors, and they reached a secret interrogation room. At the same time, they were shocked to realize that Bennett was also present.

This main character figure was one that everyone on Planet Aquamarine recognized. For two important figures to appear at the same time, Frenzied Sword and the others immediately knew that this matter was not so simple.

"What do we need to do?" Maple Moon asked.

Han Xiao turned around and slowly said, "A few days ago, we caught someone, and the results of the interrogation were harrowing. Thus, we changed many different interrogators to confirm the intelligence. All of you are partners whom I trust, and I need all of you to help me interrogate him again."

As he said that, he issued a new mission called [Interrogation] to the four of them and set the reward as the daily limit that he could give out.

Upon hearing that, the four of them turned around to take a look at the one-way mirror and saw the target who they were supposed to interrogate.

He was a frantic looking Godoran who was looking around in fear.

Chapter 534: Operation Begins

In a flash, ten days passed, and it had already been a month since Version 2.0 was released.

The overall situation was relatively good, with the number of sheltered refugees rising day after day. The beast hordes that had wreaked havoc were also eliminated one after another. The players had completely assimilated into the new version and were scrambling around, adding to the overall progress of the main task. In addition to providing disaster relief, there was also a competition happening in secret.

All in all, Nagakin's policy had been pretty effective. As the saying went, even the fiercest lady would be afraid of a stalker. Under the constant propaganda from the Godoran spokesperson, the players attempted to join the Godora faction with the mentality of trying. Han Xiao was not surprised, as trying various different possibilities was the God-given nature of a player, not to mention that the two factions were not in conflict against each other.

The image of Godora within the minds of the players was very weak. After all, it was the first time that they had come into contact with the various factions. They were unlike Han Xiao, who could be considered long-time buddies with them. However, while Godora could not compare to the Black Star Mercenary Group, the benefits given were pretty good, and the magical technology that they employed was attractive.

Nagakin was satisfied with the current recruitment process, and Black Star did not seem to have any intention of interfering.

However, just when he was about to celebrate, a video appeared on the player forums, causing a huge uproar.

Every ten days, Bun-Hit-Dog would release a new recorded video. With his current fan base on Planet Aquamarine, each release of his videos would attract a large number of players to view. However, the most recently recorded video was not a continuation of the Black Star Series. Rather, it was a new series, labelled 'Planet Aquamarine: The Old Era'.

"It's not the Black Star Series, eh, disappointed."

"A new series? Sounds interesting, not sure what the content is about."

"It's an international series. Let's see what it's all about."

After the customary roasting session, the players opened the video to have a look with high expectations. While the majority of viewers would beat Bun-Hit-Dog to death if given the chance, they had to admit that the quality of his video channel was consistently good, with humor as the main focus. This allowed everyone who watched it have a good time.

The video began, but there was no opening comment from Bun-Hit-Dog. Instead, it jumped straight into the content, literally starting with a boom. The opening scene showed nuclear bombs raining down from the sky, exploding into mushroom shaped clouds when they landed on the ground. However, the whole process was devoid of sound. Only after the shelling ended did the background music slowly start to play, as though trying to pull the audience into the picture.

This section was familiar to most of the viewers. After all, it was the recording of the Six Nations bombing the Germinal Organization headquarters. However, the video then shifted to a series of tragic war pictures. Some of the topics of the images were vague and unclear, causing the audience to comment in confusion.

"What's the video this week about? I can't tell at all."

"It's quite the messy start."

Just as the audience began to get suspicious, a narrative suddenly sounded amid the war scenes. It was Kedan's voice, and his tone was weak and trembling as he slowly explained their crimes. This confession was made through Bun-Hit-Dog recording and editing the interrogation of Kedan. He had broken down the testimony of Kedan and added imagery, allowing the audience to better understand the meaning behind his words. Such cutscene editing greatly enhanced the visual and audio contrast, giving the audience a sense as though they were recalling the past.

Following Kedan's words, the atmosphere of the channel became filled with distress and grief.

Toward the end, the images of the war were integrated with the interrogation proceedings, brought out to great effect. This allowed the audience to understand the theme of the video. This was the truth about the Old Era of Planet Aquamarine, and the images in concert with the audio painted a detailed picture of this theme, fully bringing out the grief and sadness. Only toward the end of the video did Black Star appear, and Bun-Hit-Dog utilized Black Star as the core to wrap up his entire video. For this video, Bun-Hit-Dog did not utilize his famed humorous antics but made the video with a heavy and emotional atmosphere. Compared to his past videos, the contrast was excellent, and the impact was great.

Ten days ago, Han Xiao had pulled some strings, allowing Bun-Hit-Dog to interrogate Kedan to learn about the truth of the Old Era. He had been eighty percent certain that Bun-Hit-Dog would take the secret and make it into a video to be shared with the players. Being a video producer, he would definitely use this unknown part of Planet Aquamarine as material to grab people's attention.

Indeed, it was as expected. Bun-Hit-Dog had a sharp nose toward the smell of news material and found an intrinsic value within the recording. He thus made a video out of it, thinking that it was his good luck to have stumbled upon such a secret. He did not know that this was all part of Han Xiao's plan. After a long period of interaction, Han Xiao was clear on how to utilize Bun-Hit-Dog as a weapon to sway public opinion. He only needed to hand out a few fragments of information, and he did not need to worry that Bun-Hit-Dog would not be able to come out with a satisfactory video. After all, the guy was a professional!

The response to the video was fierce, and all the viewers were stunned. No one knew that this new series actually held such a shocking secret. In an instant, Planet Aquamarine became a recipient of sympathy.

As for Godora, there was not much of an impression that they left on the players. After being 'polluted' by the video channel, they stamped the Godorans with the title of 'high and mighty' and 'arrogant'. The favorability that the players had toward them sharply decreased.

A great portion of the players were actually pragmatic, valuing their own interests and rewards above all else. However, this was not their only motivation. The players also had their own preferences, and their likes and dislikes sometimes outweighed their benefits! Few people would like to interact with those who thought themselves high and mighty.

Furthermore, after Version 1.0, the majority of players had developed some sentimental feelings toward Planet Aquamarine. Thus, they naturally stood on the side of Planet Aquamarine, feeling some anger toward Godora.

In resistance to 'authority', this was a favorite activity of many of the players!

The impact of the video was slowly taking effect, riling the emotions of the players. The forum posts for Planet Aquamarine shot up at a staggering rate, and their collective emotions worked to turn Godora into a megavillian overnight.

Even more players began to chant the slogan "Tonight, we bleed blue!", the blue being a reference to Planet Aquamarine.

Han Xiao had followed the response on the forums. At this point, his objective had basically been achieved. The public opinion target was not to raise himself on a pedestal nor to denounce the enemy, and he did not distort any facts. He merely exposed the 'secret', allowing people to see that it was a citizen of Godora that had done such a thing. Regardless of whether they had been instructed to do so or not, Godora had to bear this black mark.

I guess, it could be considered some form of overdue compensation for Planet Aquamarine.

Originally, the welfare of the mercenary group for Godora could not have been compared to that of Black Star, and now that their moral identities had taken a hit, their ability to attract mercenaries to join reached a new low. If their attraction could be likened to stock prices, it would show a continuous decrease.

Under this chain reaction, Nagakin's recruitment took a sharp downturn. Players who were originally willing to explore the Godoran camp quickly dispelled such thoughts. After all, there were already a few guinea pigs in front of them, and since there was no particular benefits given by the Godoran camp, there was no need for them to be pioneers.

Thus, the numbers in the Godoran camp plummeted, with even players that had previously joined the Godoran camp jumping ship back into the embrace of Black Star.

Confusion naturally clouded Nagakin's mind. He did not understand; everything had been perfectly fine a few days ago, so how come suddenly the Inhumans had stopped going over to him? What was the problem?

He could not understand, but little did he know that there was a negative public opinion circulating, in an area that he could not see, none of which was positive toward Godora.

In the room, Han Xiao was still browsing the forums. He let out a deep breath. So long as I interfere, Godora is destined not to be able to recruit anyone.

Even though he and Nagakin had fought side by side, it was Han Xiao who had essentially saved Nagakin. If it was not for him being involved in Nagakin's mission, then the latter would have ended up crippled.

For Nagakin not to give a fart and run over to pick up the fruits of his victory, and furthermore think that he, Han Xiao, would not be angry over it, did that not mean he himself was too magnanimous a person? Since the other party did not want to talk logically, then Han Xiao could only resort to physical means, blackening Godora's name. This left him in a sunny mood.

After throwing the problem of settling Godora to Bun-Hit-Dog ten days ago, however, Han Xiao had stopped caring about it. Rather, he had focused his attention on the organization structuring of the Black Star Mercenary Group. Following the increased recruitment of players, he put this matter on his agenda not only for the convenience of management but also to allow the players to have a material goal that they could work toward, as a ladder that they could climb up.

The latter matter was more important since it affected the fighting spirit of the players, which was equivalent to giving them a goal in their lives.

Han Xiao had formally introduced the different level systems for the Mercenary Group the previous day. The different levels in the mercenary group system would be linked to the amount of privileges such as discounts or items available within the Faction store. There was a total of six levels being divided, with the first to the fifth levels simply going from '1-Star' to '5-Star'. It was an intuitive system.

Truthfully, he had wanted to think of cooler titles, but he had finally chosen an easy to understand route. Just like the Sky Ring Army, the simpler it was, the easier it was to tell apart the differences.

As for the sixth level, also the highest level, it was named 'Black Star Eighteen Knights'. This level was not fixed but rather set at the top of the leaderboards. For those who had reached the rank of '5-Star', the top eighteen players on the leaderboards would achieve this title, and the corresponding benefits would naturally be a lot higher.

Since the positions of the Black Star Eighteen Knights were determined through the rankings, this would make them extremely competitive. This was the money burning machine that Han Xiao had specifically prepared for those of the guilds and the moneybags.

Players could view their positions in the Black Star Mercenary Group as well as their rankings through their personal mercenary file, but because the majority of the players still did not own an interstellar communicator, they could only request to view their files through Phillip.

There were three factors involved in the criteria for the mercenary level. The first was the Credibility Point of their personal mercenary file, the second was the Faction relationship level, and the last was their total contribution to the Black Star Mercenary Group.

Credibility Point needed to be accumulated through the successful completion of hired tasks. The players would have to continuously complete missions before they could increase their credibility points.

As for the Faction relationship, that was also easy to understand. For example, players who had just joined the Black Star Mercenary Group would all be at the 1-Star level. In order to be promoted to a 2-Star Mercenary, one of the prerequisites was to have the Faction relationship reach the level of [Friendly]. This meant that their contribution point had to be at 1,000 or more. After promoting, however, there was no need to maintain the current contribution points. Even if the points were spent, the level would not be reduced.

As for the last factor, the total contribution amount was the highlight. For example, if someone had 3,000 contribution points and spent 1,000, their total contribution amount would still hold at 3,000. It somewhat resembled a player's total contribution history in the Black Star Faction. For promotion from 1-Star to 2-Star, a total of 20,000 points was needed.

Once the hierarchy was placed online, the players would immediately start to dissect and study it. They would quickly find out that the loophole that they could exploit would be the total contribution point factor!

Because, for those players whose relationship was below the [Friendly] level of 1,000 points, 50 Enas could be exchanged for 100 Contribution Points. However, when the current contribution level hit between 1,000 to 3,000 points, then the same 100 Contribution Points could only be purchased with 500 Enas instead. Thus, so long as their current Contribution was capped at below 1,000 points, then the total Contribution Point factor could be improved at the lowest cost!

With this discovery, the players would definitely be overjoyed, feeling as though they had found a loophole.

Han Xiao had long predicted this, and he loved to make players feel as though they had taken advantage of the system.

The reasoning was simple. The players had to maintain their current contribution below 1,000 points. Thus, if they wished to save money, they would have to spend all their contribution points. The only outlet would be the faction store, and in order to do so, they also had to spend a corresponding amount of Enas. This formed a completely cycle where he would ensure the players consumed his goods, and at the same time, it allowed the players to think that they were saving on Enas for Contribution Points.

In addition, the other two factors affecting the promotion of the mercenary level were hard requirements with no loopholes present. As such, the players could not abuse the total contribution point method to quickly increase their mercenary levels.

The 'shortcut' to raising one's total contribution points was actually a scheme from the Great Mechanic Han. By taking advantage of the psychology of the players, he purposely left a 'loophole', allowing the players to discover it.

Even with the large influx of newcomers in the Mercenary Group, only the dozens of players that had followed him from the start were close to the standard of 2-Star. The requirements to promote were strictly set this time. Judging by the current progress of the players, Han Xiao estimated that most players would be at the level of 1-Star to 2-Star in this version. No player would be able to reach the highest level during this version. After all, this was a long-term plan.

Inside the room, Han Xiao leaned against the back of his chair, propping up his feet as he muttered to himself, "The formal planning for the Mercenary Group is just getting started. Let's take it slow."

As long as he gathered enough players, the capability of the players would be equivalent to his own influence. He had enough patience to wait for the players to slowly mature.

Beep beep!

At this time, his communicator let out an emergency notification.

Opening the virtual screen, Han Xiao gave it a quick glance. It was an urgent news alert stating that the DarkStar fleet had opened attacks on several other planets with the Mutation Disaster!

Han Xiao immediately narrowed his eyes, his expression turning grave as he sat up straight.

"It has finally begun..."

Chapter 535: Impending Crisis

It had been two months since the outbreak of the Mutation Disaster, but DarkStar had not made a move. Thus, many people had felt as though something was amiss. After staying silent for so long, DarkStar had finally taken action and set out their fleets to attack three different calamity planets.

This news immediately created a huge reaction, and many of the galactic residents knew that the show was starting. As the archenemy of Godora, it was obvious that DarkStar would not let go of such a good opportunity, and the final piece of the puzzle had finally appeared.

Currently, there was no evidence to show that the Mutation Disaster was a conspiracy initiated by DarkStar, but this was no longer important. As long as DarkStar interfered in this matter, Godora's largest opponent would definitely be DarkStar.

DarkStar attacked three calamity planets in one go, and the local Godoran disaster relief squads fought an intense battle. However, because they were caught off guard and the size of their fleets were small, the three Godora disaster relief squads suffered huge losses.

Logically speaking, the civilizations of those three calamity planets should have been completely vulnerable before DarkStar. However, DarkStar did not destroy those three planets but seemed to have their sights set on the disaster relief squads. After causing some destruction, the DarkStar forces retreated before the Godoran reinforcements could arrive.

The outcome of the ambush was that almost seventy to eighty percent of the disaster relief squads was destroyed, and the situation that had stabilized was thrown back into chaos.

Because of this, Godora raised their defenses and sent out their regular army to the different calamity planets to stop DarkStar's ambush. But even so, they were not able to stop DarkStar in their tracks.

The second wave of ambushes took place soon after, and another few calamity planets were the targets.

The same scenario unfolded again. Despite Godora raising their defenses, DarkStar had also strengthened their attacks, and a galactic battle broke out between the two parties.

The spaceships crashed into each other with their protective shields flickering. The explosions of the spaceship's cannons flickered in the dark space like new stars being formed. The bright ray from the laser cannons was like a rainbow bridge in the pitch-black space.

After a huge battle, DarkStar retreated in time again, and the battle did not develop into an all-out war. Godora's fleet suffered a loss again, and all the disaster relief efforts went to complete waste.

Most of the time, DarkStar only hid in the dark to scheme against Godora; it had been a long time since their last head on battle. With DarkStar coming out from their nest again, it was no longer a small skirmish, and Godora immediately felt the pressure.

While Godora did have the advantage in terms of strength, Godora's territory was large, and their fleet was stationed around the different bases of the Garton Star System. The spare forces that they could mobilize were not sufficient to suppress DarkStar, and Godora was not clear about the size of DarkStar's forces either.

The most frightening part about DarkStar was the fact that they were hidden in the dark. It was impossible to predict their actions beforehand, and Godora had a huge headache because of this. If they did not know what DarkStar's next target was, they would not be able to make any targeted arrangements and could only defend passively.

In the past two ambushes, DarkStar seemed to have targeted the disaster relief squads, but Godora would not pull back their disaster relief squads just because of that. If they did, it would seem as though they are afraid of DarkStar, and Godora would never show such an attitude to their enemy. Furthermore, since they had already begun their disaster relief efforts, if they gave up halfway, it would be a huge hit to their reputation. Besides, the situation had not yet reached such a stage.

After so many years, both parties were finally in confrontation again. The entire Garton Star System was shaken, and this became the most watched affair in the Garton Star System.

...

"DarkStar will not stop like that and will continue launching their attacks. We will definitely meet them sooner or later."

In a conference room of the Sanctuary, Nagakin narrated the situation with a solemn expression. In the entire conference room, only Han Xiao was familiar with the situation. Both Bennett and the leaders of the Six Nations listed to Nagakin by the side.

The moment DarkStar launched their first ambush, this matter became serious. A few days ago, a Godoran fleet had suddenly descended to guard Planet Aquamarine. There were currently 120 Godora battleships waiting outside the atmosphere of Planet Aquamarine, waiting to defend against DarkStar's ambush.

Nagakin could no longer be bothered about disaster relief or recruitment. Defending against DarkStar was his priority. He had approached Han Xiao to discuss the matter many times over the past few days, and they were currently holding a meeting to inform both the Sanctuary and Six Nations to be on high alert. Of course, the Planet Aquamarine civilization would not be able to put up a fight in a galactic battle, but Nagakin wanted them to be mentally prepared for the possibility of being ambushed at any time.

"Because of our disaster relief efforts, we can only defend passively, and the situation is not to our advantage. DarkStar's motive is very likely to make use of our thin defense line to attack our weak points and slowly chip away at our forces. We can't know what DarkStar's next target will be," Nagakin said with a deep voice.

Han Xiao nodded. This was indeed DarkStar's motive, but it was only a small part of their plan. DarkStar's Mutation Disaster plan was targeted at weakening Godora's strength. Not just their military strength but also to shake the stability of their rule. They would only ambush the calamity planets but will not destroy the low-grade civilizations. If they destroyed the civilizations, Godora would not need to carry out any more disaster relief operations. DarkStar's motive was to hold Godora back.

The faces of Bennett and the others were solemn. It was impossible for them to be anxious as there was no use for them to be anxious.

"How are you planning to deal with the situation?" Bennett asked.

"The War Bureau has redeployed troops from the other Star Zones, and the second and third wave of reinforcements are on their way. The heads want us to continue our disaster relief effort while keeping our guard up..."

Nagakin frowned slightly. In truth, the upper echelons had thought of migrating all the refugees on the calamity planets. However, there was a huge hidden danger in doing so. They would not be able to detect if the Mutation Source entered the spaceship together with the refugees. As such, this plan was temporarily shelved, and the War Bureau decided to fight DarkStar head on.

Some of the more aggressive generals even felt that this was a chance. DarkStar was always in hiding, and it was extremely rare for DarkStar to make an appearance. Thus, they felt that they needed to make use of this opportunity to bait the DarkStar fleet and strike them with a heavy blow. Thus, the War Bureau decided to deploy further reinforcements.

"In the end, we can only choose to wait," Nagakin said solemnly.

In truth, he had hidden another order from the upper echelons. If their forces were not a match for DarkStar's fleet, the upper echelons requested them to make a strategic retreat and preserve their strength. If the calamity planet was destroyed because of this, Godora could only express their regret.

Han Xiao shook his head. DarkStar's ambush was completely random, and even he was not able to predict when it would come. Even if he knew DarkStar's plans, he did not have the strength to block them.

If DarkStar's fleet come, I will have to join in the battle as well. This time, it wouldn't be a battle on land but a galactic battle... Han Xiao mused to himself. The danger of a galactic battle was far greater than a battle on land. It was no longer a battle between Supers but a battle between fleets. He would also have to face great pressure.

After the meeting was over, Han Xiao gathered all of his officers and requested for them to be on high alert. On top of that, he also got them to unload the materials in the spaceship's storeroom into a secret underground base in the Sanctuary.

The spaceship that he had rented was a model that was built for cruising, and its combat capability was not great. He was not prepared to send those rented spaceships into battle. Not to mention the fact that they would not be of much use, he will suffer a huge loss if the spaceships ended up being destroyed. However, he had other plans for the spaceships.

As such, the BlackLight Stealth was the only spaceship that his mercenary group could send out. While it was little, thankfully, its quality was high.

The members of the Sanctuary also got into action. They scattered the refugees and decreased the population density of the Sanctuary. On top of that, they constructed a few basic defensive measures. However, with their lack of technological skills, they could only leave everything up to luck. While the refugees did not know what was going on, they all listened to orders obediently. The atmosphere of the entire Sanctuary became extremely tense.

The players did not know what they were about to face next. Han Xiao still remembered that, in his previous life, whenever they suffered from an ambush, the mission progress of the Main Storyline Mission [Mutation Disaster] would fall greatly. With the players' current strength, it was difficult for them to contribute much in a galactic battle.

If DarkStar doesn't come, that would be for the best. Han Xiao let out a sigh.

...

A concealed DarkStar squad was moving slowly in the galaxy. This was a high mobility armed squad, and their flagship was not a DarkStar mothership but a command ship called 'Blood Gal'. There were more than two hundred battleships surrounding the flagship, and the majority of the battleships were assault ships with immense firepower.

In the busy command center of the battleship, the fleet commander Nakapu had his arms behind his back as he looked at the projected star map. This gaze was emotionless, and he was cold to the point that he did not seem to have any emotions.

Not too long ago, he had led his fleet to launch two different ambushes and destroyed more than a hundred Godoran battleships. In those ambushes, his loss was less than half that figure.

Nakapu's fleet was made up of the elites of DarkStar, and their strength was not to be underestimated. He was following his orders and on his way to the next ambush target.

"How many more days until the destination?" Nakapu asked calmly.

"17 hours and 26 minutes," the navigator replied.

In the holographic projection, the star map of Star Zone 9 could be seen. The target planet was currently flashing in red.

Planet Aquamarine!

Chapter 536: Raid (1)

The Andrea Continent, once the territory of the Germinal Organization, had borne the majority of aftermath of the war of the old era. The expedition of the Six Nations to this land had caused the surroundings to deteriorate further, with the radiation level shooting past the warning line. The lands were blackened, the surroundings were desolate, and all the wanderers that had previously been living in this area were shifted to the other three continents. Andrea had become largely uninhabited, with only a few mutant beasts still surviving within.

The ruins of the Germinal Organization lay on that continent, the once magnificent base having turned into a black pile of scorched earth. The central base had also vanished, leaving only a black hole, and the underground base had been completely obliterated. By the side of the circle was a black line radiating outward, extending over hundreds of miles.

Due to the excessive concentration of nuclear radiation, the Six Nations had only sent some drones to explore the ruins after the explosions. Nothing valuable was left, and there were no signs of life. Everyone had died under the frenzied series of nuclear strikes.

As such, the Six Nations did not bother wasting their resources to clean up the mess. Over the past couple of years, the original base of the Germinal Organization had become filled with thick ash and dust, and the little shrapnel that had been shot out during the explosion bore signs of erosion. Death and defeat hung heavily in the atmosphere.

Yet, in that area where even mutant beasts could not survive, a silhouette stood in the very center of the Germinal Organization ruins. While it could be described as a 'silhouette', it was actually merely a blackened skeleton. It was as though the steel-like flesh and blood of the person had been incinerated in the explosion a few years ago, but the charred skeleton remained somehow, not turning into powder. Even after such a long time, it did not decompose into ash. Only the body of a Super had this sort of toughness, far beyond that of ordinary humans.

It was obvious that the signs of life in this corpse had long since disappeared, and the gray dust floating in the air drifted in and out of its hollow eye sockets.

It was such a corpse that was slowly coming back to life. It gradually took one step after another, limping with a lump of black gelatinous substance attached at the cervical vertebrae. It extended out threads akin to roots, entwining the limbs along the bones as if it was a puppeteer, using the corpse to practice like a marionette.

This black gelatinous substance was the mutation source. It had already passed through its 'infant stage' of only being able to passively extract energy. It could now actively pursue energy, as well as constantly swap its hosts, as it crossed mountains and waded through the oceans to finally reach the Andrea continent, benefitting from the senses of the countless lives it occupied. The energy present there was not only huge, it also contained the highest amount of radiation energy present that could be easily absorbed by it.

The Germinal Organization's ruins were a death zone, with all the previous hosts of the Mutation Source dying within. It had no other alternative except to continuously drag its current body over to the ruins. The skeleton that it was controlling had been the only corpse left in the Germinal Organization ruins, that of the Germinal Organization's Leader. During the explosion, because the Leader had been situated in the underground base, the various layers had shielded him from most of the impact. In addition to the strength of his body, his bones had been preserved, while the rest had long turned to dust.

At a molecular level, the nuclear radiation in the Germinal Organization ruins was continuously being absorbed by the Mutation Source. On the microscopic level, one could see that the speed of cell division had increased by over a hundred times, and the proliferating cells were constantly being integrated into its body, improving its control. Energy was constantly being transformed and synthesized.

In the past plot, Tyne had become the original carrier of the Mutation Source when he first escaped from prison. However, because he had been captured by Han Xiao to be reformed, without this powerful 'tool', the Mutation Source had wasted a lot of time on the road.

However, in the past plot, it had also not possessed as wonderful a 'nurturing cradle' as the ruins of the Germinal Organization.

The skeleton slowly staggered as the Mutation Source absorbed as much energy as it could like a man dying of hunger and thirst. The radiation levels, thus, slowly decreased at a level unseen to the naked eye.

Nakapu's fleet was suspended at the rear of a barren planet. The distance from there to Planet Aquamarine was extremely short, with only one short-range jump needed. This was the closest sector one could go in stealth mode. Any nearer, and the stealth system would no longer be able to hide from the military radar of Godora. The fleet would also expose its location.

This area was similar to being in the deep sea. With one's field of vision comprising only of darkness, only the flow of water could be used to determine if enemies were approaching. The closer the distance, the more obvious the disturbance in water would be. Gravity was not unlike the flow of water; get too close, and stealth would lose its effectiveness. This was dependent on the reconnaissance capabilities of the spaceship's equipped radar.

As longtime enemies, DarkStar was clear of the capabilities of Godora's military equipment while constantly raising the bar for their own stealth cloaking abilities.

The interior of the command ship was bustling, as everyone scurried to perform final preparations for the attack. Nakapu was confirming various intel from the scouts sent out.

"What is the number of defense forces that Planet Aquamarine currently possesses?"

"There are a hundred and twenty regular Godora frigates in outer space. This is a medium-sized fleet. It should be a force sent from the Nadban military base."

"Any intel from the ambush troops?"

"Yes, they said that in addition to the escort fleet, there are more than a dozen space shuttles of the Godora disaster relief team. The leading team is a senior officer of the war bureau, Nagakin, a pugilist at the Calamity Grade."

Nakapu remained expressionless. "A Calamity Grade Super, this is slightly troublesome. We don't have any high levelled combatants here, so we can immediately rule out the option of fighting through our warships. Luckily, it's just a pugilist. Any other news?"

"Other than the Godorans, there's another force that is on Planet Aquamarine, the Floating Dragon Field Team's Black Star Mercenary Group. They too own over ten spaceships."

"Black Star..." Nakapu remained unmoved. "They're the mercenaries who ambushed us on Noriosse, right? They're also a bunch of annoying fellows. Seems like Planet Aquamarine is slightly more special, with a defense far above that of the previous two planets. This will be a little thorny. Let's go with Plan 4."

Even after hearing that Black Star was on Planet Aquamarine, Nakapu was not surprised. To him, it was merely another enemy that they needed to deal with. There was no need to kick up a big fuss.

It was not that Nakapu was looking down on them. After calculating the contrast of combat power between both parties, he had decided to carry on with the execution of the attack.

In other words, the addition of a Black Star Mercenary Corps just made him feel slightly more troubled, and that was it.

"DarkStar may appear at any time. I need all of you to react at the first sign, so all of you had better keep your eyes wide open for me and raise your spirits!"

In Planet Aquamarine's orbit, the warship squadron commander of the Godoran troops, Barette, was shouting loudly through the comms channel. He was a short Godoran with an explosive temper. His voice boomed like thunder, echoing through the receivers.

"Commander Barette, the radar has discovered our objective. A fleet is approaching us at a fast speed... They've stopped! The coordinates are C-02-07!"

Barette immediately gazed at the radar screen, seeing more than a hundred blips being displayed on it. This was the DarkStar fleet. He then looked out of the porthole, but there was no sign of the DarkStar troops approaching. The distance between the two was closing fast, reaching the extreme limits of both parties' cannon range.

Ohm!

At this time, the alarm in the command room suddenly blared, flashing with a red light.

"Warning! Detected a high index energy response rapidly approaching! Impending collision!"

Outside the porthole, the inky darkness of the universe was suddenly lit up with thousands of green light rays as the densely clustered ion guns shot from afar.

Nakapu's fleet was employing over-the-horizon strikes!

Chapter 537: Raid (2)

The attacks arrived abruptly!

The plasma shells of the ion guns mostly impacted on the golden shield of the Godoran frigate; however, a few of them slipped through the seams between each Godoran shield, falling toward Planet Aquamarine.

The beams got smaller in one's field of view, some falling into the sea, causing small waves to rise up. Some landed on the ground, blasting out mini mushroom clouds. At least when in outer space, the view was considered small.

"Open the Weiss magic protection shield!" Barette screamed.

The Godoran frigate changed their formation, gathering in the direction of the attack. They shot out golden rays of light, which formed ten gold semi-circular shields in front of the frigate. The shields tightly sealed off any attacks from that direction into Planet Aquamarine.

The next round of ion rays from Nakapu's fleet quickly arrived, slamming into the protective shields. The ion cannons fired constantly, and the rays appeared like a shower of light, causing the shields to continuously ripple.

"Increase the power output!" Barette's huge hands were sending out command signals nonstop. "Don't just be sitting ducks, retaliate! Retaliate! Retaliate!"

The Godoran fleet locked on to their target through their radars and began to launch their own over-the-horizon attacks. They launched beam after beam of golden lasers into the empty space of the universe.

While both sides were unable to see each other, the exchange of green and golden lasers never stopped, intensely firing. If not for the fact that they were warring in a vacuum, the people on Planet Aquamarine would have heard the sounds of battle, akin to the continuous rumble of thunder.

Barette quickly notified his superior and sent the intelligence to Nagakin.

...

On Planet Aquamarine, the Six Nations had already discovered the confrontation between the two parties through the Natural Satellite and were thoroughly panicking.

While they did not have a clear idea of what DarkStar was, they had learned from Nagakin that they were a strong enemy, even on an interstellar level, that could easily crush them. The Six Nations did not dare dally, immediately beginning the evacuation. The refugees all entered the underground bomb shelters.

In the first wave of attacks, a dozen ion bombs fell on the surface. Most of them landed in the wilderness, with the one landing in a suburb near the Six Nations' territory. It resembled a bolt of green thunder falling from the sky.

Boom!

A miniature mushroom shaped cloud shot toward the sky, as a huge crater appeared on the ground. The subsequent shockwave levelled an entire street, leaving only ruins in its wake as dust filled the air.

The evacuation also started to be rushed as the tense atmosphere gave way to panic. While the refugees were still unaware of what was happening, it did not stop them from thinking. With the tightly packed crowd, stampedes broke out. Due to the large number of people present, many of them had also not received the suppressant, and this resulted in the mutation virus triggering, spreading, and causing havoc.

The guards rushed in, but small-scale chaos was everywhere, and it was difficult to manage them at the same time. Bennett had a grave expression as he continuously issued commands, barely stabilizing the situation.

At this point, the players triggered an emergency mission. The mission introduction read, "Planet Aquamarine has encountered an attack from a fleet from outer space! Help is needed to ensure safe evacuation of the refugees!"

Almost every player looked up at that moment, and it was faintly clear that there were rays flashing about in the sky above them.

"Are there battleships outside of Planet Aquamarine attacking us?"

"A pity we can't even see it properly, d*mn!"

Curiosity was akin to a feather tickling the hearts of all the players present, causing them to feel an itch in their chests. They clearly knew that there was a Super level battle happening in outer space, but the inability to participate or see it in person was just too torturous!

The suppression of the rioting refugees would be left to someone else; it was not within Han Xiao's consideration. While he had also triggered the same emergency mission as the rest of the players, the experience reward was too small in his opinion. He had no interest in the task and instead opened his communicator, contacting Nagakin.

"How's the situation?"

"The fleet is currently engaged with DarkStar, but we do not know when the reinforcements will come. I need to return to help them." In the scene, Nagakin was boarding a spaceship hurriedly, his tone urgent.

"Then I'll first restrain my troops and wait. Don't switch off your communicator. We'll keep in touch." Han Xiao nodded. With Nagakin and the Godoran fleets in the battle, there was no need for him to join.

He was not surprised that DarkStar had suddenly launched a raid. In fact, he sighed in relief, with the emotion of someone who had been waiting for far too long. Looking at the soldiers beside him, he was not worried at all.

DarkStar would not destroy this planet—this was the crucial intel that Han Xiao had received. Based on the intel, the probability of the enemy landing was not high. Instead, they would choose to attack from space to reduce their losses.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had calculated that there should be a team of DarkStar agents lying in wait on Planet Aquamarine. The other party would definitely be aware of Nagakin's and his presence. After all, DarkStar was well aware of the importance of information. They would definitely calculate every variable before deciding on the method of attack.

In his previous life, Han Xiao had also experienced such a matter. He was deeply aware that this was the key point and immediately ordered the mercenaries to board the spaceships and travel to the territory of the Six Nations. While the rented spaceships had basic capabilities, they had a shield that they could deploy to resist the falling cannon shells from the sky. The power of the battleship's ion cannons was no joke. One shot on a human would cause around 2,000 damage even after factoring the damage reduction!

To the current players, a cannon shot would be able to destroy an entire team! Naturally, Han Xiao would not be such a fool to take the blow head on. In this sort of battle, only the pugilist class would dare to streak around unprotected, thanks to their thick skins.

As a result, this would not cause the [Mutation Disaster] mission to drop too much in the overall progress. However, to the players, each visit that the DarkStar made would be a cheat whereby large chunks of their progress bars would disappear for their mission.

DarkStar naturally would not just attack Planet Aquamarine. The rest of the calamity planets were attacked at the same time. While Han Xiao did not have the capacity to aid the other calamity planets, he could at least reduce the losses on Planet Aquamarine, putting a halt to DarkStar's plan to destroy the disaster relief results. Otherwise, all their previous work would be wasted.

"The Godoran fleet is now resisting the enemies, and Nagakin has also gone up. There's no one for me to ask about the situation." Han Xiao rubbed his hands as he stared at the real time image of Nagakin that was being transmitted.

He hoped that Godora would be able to force DarkStar to retreat without him making a move. DarkStar was unaware of his current power, and the longer he hid this trump card of his, the better.

...

As Nagakin left the atmosphere, he immediately caught sight of the ten golden shields. The Godoran and DarkStar fleets were still exchanging shots over the horizon, and with his experience, he immediately saw that while this method looked intense, it could not restrict both parties.

The ion cannon shots were being forcibly blocked by the shields. Even if one shield was broken, due to the distance, the troops were able to quickly react and send another spaceship to swap and replace the shield. As such, the formation continued to hold steady.

Other than the conventional ship-borne ion guns, most of the other weapons did not have the range, and nuclear energy guided missiles would be blasted apart midway by the ion guns. The technology levels of the Godoran and DarkStar fleets were similar. Without any overwhelmingly powerful weapon, if both sides wanted to cause irreparable damage to the enemy, they had to draw closer.

Beep beep!

Barette linked to Nagakin's comms channel.

"The shields can't be maintained forever, and we cannot stay on the receiving side. If this goes on, there will not be any injuries on DarkStar's side. I'll draw closer, Nagakin; you will lead the assault and crush them!"

"Don't take the risk!" Nagakin yelled. "Right now, the situation is to our benefit. As long as we continue this stalemate, DarkStar will eventually retreat."

"Nonsense! DarkStar's technological level is about the same as ours, but we have you, and your capabilities are enough to completely topple the enemy. This is the best chance to defeat DarkStar!" Barette shouted into the channel. He was considered a more radical officer, believing that rather than protecting the calamity planets, it would be better if he took the opportunity to attack the armed forces of DarkStar.

Just as Nagakin was about to reply, Barette screamed into the mic.

"Wait a minute... the radar indicates that the enemies are moving backward. DarkStar is retreating‽"

...

Nakapu's eyes were narrowed into slits as he stared at the radar screen, his hands folded behind him. His fingers subconsciously rubbed the hem of his clothes as he shook his head. Finally, he opened his mouth to give the command. His tone remained passive throughout, without the slightest emotion.

"Attention, prepare for the transition."

Chapter 538: Choosing to Pursuit

On the radar screen of the Godora fleet, the hundred odd light blips representing the DarkStar fleet had started to pull away, and the ion cannons' shots had also become sparse. All this signified that the enemy was retreating.

Barette's expression changed as he hypothesized, "DarkStar is unable to break our defense, so they're going to retreat before our reinforcements come. They're giving up on the attack this time!"

Observing the battle, Nagakin furrowed his brows. "Looks to be the case..."

"The distance between us and them is getting further. I'm going to pursue them; we can't let them go so easily!" Barette bellowed.

"Don't be careless. This could be the enemy's ploy to lure us out. We're better off maintaining our current position."

Barette's face was unpleasant as he growled, "DarkStar rarely appear. I'm not going to let the opportunity slip away! We were passively slammed a volley of shells previously, and now we're going to just watch as the enemy saunter away? This is not my style!"

The DarkStar fleet was retreating without pause. Once they passed a certain distance, the radar would no longer be able to see through the stealth mode of the other party, and DarkStar would once again enter stealth mode and become an invisible fleet.

As he gazed at the blips moving further away, Barette was sluggish, wishing to move.

Nagakin also hesitated a little. The safest tactic was naturally to stand by their current position; however, opportunity was always fleeting. Besides, he himself was not sure if the enemy was really retreating.

If they pursued and engaged DarkStar, with their strength, they could probably destroy a few DarkStar assault ships. In addition, if they could delay the retreat of the enemy until their reinforcements came, it would allow them to hit DarkStar hard!

The first two attacks had caused a lot of losses for Godora. The entire War Bureau was holding in their anger; even Nagakin wished to obtain some accomplishments in the war.

Furthermore, Barette was currently the commander of the frigate. While Nagakin's rank was higher, he could not directly overrule Barette's orders.

"Nagakin, stop hesitating!" Barette said in a low voice. "Whether you come or not, I am going to make a move."

Nagakin's eyes sharpened as he made a decision. "Transfer a portion of them to remain on sentry."

He no longer tried to persuade Barette, instead preparing to pursue the enemy.

"I don't need you to remind me!" Barette's eyes lit up, and he immediately sent down the new orders.

The next moment, the Godora frigate was divided into two teams, where eighty of them chased in pursuit of DarkStar and the remaining forty stayed in Planet Aquamarine's orbit, awaiting further orders.

Barette had decided to pursue the enemy, but he did not put all his eggs in one basket. The enemy's fleet numbered about one hundred and ten. Since he was the pursuer, it was sufficient for him to utilize eighty spaceships. On one hand, he could pose a threat, and on the other, he need not be afraid of retaliation from the enemy, able to hold their own on the battlefield. Furthermore, they had the Calamity Grade Super Nagakin, who could put up a fight even if the enemy had one as well.

The pursuing troops quickly caught up, and the ion guns erupted in succession. Golden lights flashed as they carried out an attack over the horizon while releasing interference rays to prevent the enemy from escaping.

Since DarkStar was retreating, Barette adjusted his strategy to maintain sufficient distance to compensate for reaction time. His objective was to harass and delay them, but at the same time, he took precautions for if the enemy were to suddenly turn back or possibly launch an ambush.

Both fleets moved in the universe, gradually distancing themselves from Planet Aquamarine.

At this moment, in the opposite direction of Barette's departure, dozens of transition jumps appeared, stopping in outer space near Planet Aquamarine. When they revealed themselves, it was a new fleet of DarkStar spaceships, with the few dozen all being assault ships.

Nakapu's fleet actually consisted of over two hundred battleships in total, but Godora only had one hundred and twenty battleships at hand, almost half of DarkStar's numbers. As such, Nakapu had chosen to split his fleet into two formations, commanding the main fleet to tangle and sap away the strength of the Godoran fleet, luring the tiger away from the cave.

As for the other strike force, they would then take the opportunity to attack, piercing through the blockade created by the Godoran fleet, and complete their objective of wrecking Planet Aquamarine.

If the Godoran fleet did not separate, this strike force would still appear and launch a pincer strike.

In the command ship far away, Nakapu, who was being chased by Barette, sent out the order to the strike force.

"Attack!"

The forty battleships that were still patrolling around Planet Aquamarine immediately reacted, rushing to set up a resistance. This time, the strike force did not engage in an attack from over the horizon but instead went for a close-range shootout. Various explosions could be seen on the shields of both sides as they fought intensely.

The size of this strike force was twice the size of the remaining Godoran fleet. The troops fought a bitter battle and immediately informed Barette of the situation.

After receiving the news, Barette's eyes flashed. "So, it turned out to be this tactic. Humph! The enemy actually had twice our number. That's why they could carry out such a plan... All units, listen up, pick up the speed and pursue. Don't let the enemy escape our field of vision! Tell the defending troops to give up on Planet Aquamarine and immediately rendezvous with us!"

Nagakin jumped in shock. "You're not going to reinforce them‽"

"There's no need, and time doesn't allow us to do so. To turn back and reinforce now would be an act of futility. We would even allow the DarkStar command ship that we are pursuing to escape. The gains do not justify the losses. The division of the enemy is a good thing, as we can gather all our troops and completely destroy the DarkStar command ship! If we give them enough pressure, then the strike force will also have no choice but to forsake the mission and reinforce the command ship!"

Barette coldly snorted. If the target planet had been an important asset to Godora, he definitely would have abandoned it, choosing security over destroying them. However, this calamity planet, Planet Aquamarine, was insignificant to him and could be forsaken at any point.

Between protecting Planet Aquamarine or destroying the DarkStar fleet, he would unhesitatingly choose the latter!

During the first two attacks, the situation had also given Barette some suspicions. As such, he had decided to simply leave Planet Aquamarine unprotected under the salvo of gunfire from the strike team to see if DarkStar would really destroy the calamity planet. If they still did not wreck the planet in such circumstances, then at least it would reveal the intentions of the enemy.

Even if he guessed incorrectly, there would not be any problems. Losing one planet meant less pressure for the War Bureau.

Nagakin's brows furrowed tightly. With matters as such, he had no control over Barette's decision. He replied, "I'll have to first inform Black Star."

"No need, I heard it all." From the communicator came Han Xiao's voice. He did not say much, only calmly replying. "Leave the strike team to me."

"You have to resist them." Nagakin cupped his fists before turning off the communicator. Sighing loudly, he quickly went to the doorway.

At this time, the spaceship that he was in accelerated to catch up with the DarkStar command ship where Nakapu was located. Both spaceships collided into each other's formations, and artillery fire blasted indiscriminately. Because the spaceship that he was in was the closest to the DarkStar fleet, his battle was the first to begin, leaving him no time to be concerned of the situation on Han Xiao's side.

Chapter 539: Virtual Intrusion (1)

Boom!

Nagakin's spaceship collided with a hundred-meter-long DarkStar spaceship. Violent vibrations shook both ships, and the door in front of Nagakin was slammed open, exposing his entire person into the cosmic environment. The Godoran combat uniform immediately reacted, providing a suitable environment for survival.

Shortly after, a raging golden flame ignited around Nagakin's body and blasted off behind him, acting as a propeller. Nagakin resembled a golden meteor as he viciously slammed into the outer shell of the DarkStar battleship.

When comparing the size of a hundred-meter-long battleship to a human, it looked like an ant going against an elephant.

However, the strength revealed by this one fist actually left a deep depression right in the tough outer armor of the DarkStar battleship!

A continuous barrage of punches rained down, the shadows of the punches blurring into one. The next second, Nagakin had forcibly created an opening in the DarkStar battleship. A large number of metal fragments burst out, and Nagakin strode into the ship, clad in a golden flame.

Boom!

The DarkStar ship began to continuously tremor as Nagakin ran rampant within, destroying the DarkStar battleship from the inside. None of the DarkStar warriors present were able to obstruct him, as though he was in an unmanned environment. All the equipment and devices were smashed into smithereens, and in a chain reaction, more and more parts were paralyzed.

Very quickly, Nagakin rushed out again, jumping into his spaceship to leave this battleship, seeking his next target.

Behind him, the battleship that was riddled with holes suddenly exploded, becoming a series of fireworks in the universe!

In such space warfare, the strongest Supers usually acted as the vanguard of their troops, initiating the battle through destroying the insides of the enemy's battleships. Rarely did both sides collide head on with each other. After all, the danger of attempting to destroy each other's battleships was too great, and the efficiency could not match that of destroying the battleships internally... Of course, the standard did not include those Beyond Grade A Supers.

The remaining Godoran troops responded to Barette's commands to retreat and prepared to rejoin the main force. Nakapu was able to quickly perceive the general idea of Barette's strategy and responded. He split up the strike force once again, with a large portion in pursuit of Barette's retreating troops to prevent the incident of being pincered by the enemy.

Thus, there were only thirty assault ships left to attack Planet Aquamarine. While Black Star never made a move in the end, Nakapu still calculated his strength into the equation, leaving sufficient troops according to his judgement.

Without the protection of the Godoran fleet, Planet Aquamarine resembled a delicate and frail lady. The thirty DarkStar assault ships entered the atmosphere, spraying cannon fire toward the surface of the planet.

Boom!

Cluster after cluster of green colored ion cannon rays fell like lightning, constantly bombarding the surface.

Those assault ships did not just fire randomly but rather aimed in the direction of the Six Nations and the Sanctuaries. Their objective was to destroy these sites, spoiling the disaster relief efforts.

Han Xiao had earlier allowed dozens of mercenaries to utilize their spaceships to protect those places. At this time, they opened up their shields, blocking the descending ion cannon rays.

Boom!

Sounds of explosion rang among the clouds, with the shields of the spaceships being besieged to the point where they could not differentiate night from day. The shields continuously grew weaker.

Many of the refugee players were unable to see the spaceships that were situated at a high altitude, but they were able to see the green ion cannon rays flying over their sanctuaries. The rays streamed down continuously, akin to a deluge of lightning, and the roar from the cannons painted a sign as though an apocalypse was imminent.

This scene gave many players a huge surprise, causing them to burst out in discussion.

"Is this a fleet that's attacking us‽"

"F*ck, the progress bar of our mission is decreasing. Is it because we're being attacked!"

"If not for all these spaceships shielding us, I think we would all be blasted to death!"

As for the actual refugees in the Six Nations and the Sanctuaries, they did not possess the natural assurance of safety like the players. Every explosion caused by the ion cannon rays seemed to strike straight into their hearts, scaring them witless. Their faces were white as paper, and they only thought of rushing to escape. The scene was a complete mess.

Han Xiao had already entered his BlackLight Stealth, and the Mercenary Group had also gathered on the battleship. Everyone wore a solemn expression. Now that the Godoran troops had gone in pursuit of the enemy, the remaining enemy battleships had to be dealt with by them.

Having long known that the Godorans were not reliable, Han Xiao had not held many expectations toward them. As such, he did not feel disappointed and only shook his head in response.

"It's hard to rely on anyone in this day and age. You can only rely on your two hands!" Sylvia observed, speaking hurriedly. "There are thirty small DarkStar assault ships attacking. Based on the current firepower, our shields can still hold for a few minutes. We have to get rid of the enemies in this time, or else the Sanctuaries will suffer huge damage."

Han Xiao nodded in response. Only his BlackLight Stealth could allow him to go against the enemies, so if he wished to end the battle quickly, he would need to enter their battleships, wreaking havoc from within. However, the firepower of the assault ships was fierce, and to get close, even with his BlackLight Stealth, there was still a certain amount of danger.

Thankfully, I did the Class Advancement for the Virtual Technology route. If the hardware is insufficient, then I shall make it up through the software!

"Ginette, take control of the spaceship. Sylvia, assist as the deputy."

In order to maintain the combat capability of the mercenaries, Han Xiao decided to let others control the spaceship.

Han Xiao turned and opened an operation panel next to him. A 3D virtual model was generated in front of his eyes, and his fingers danced as he quickly inputted a flood of data. The data flowed like a waterfall, invading the intelligence network of the enemy's spacecraft through their virtual network. Because of his class [Virtual Mechanic], he was proficient in this aspect of technology since it gave him high skill bonuses.

All Virtual Mechanics possessed a data transmitter that did not require any hardware connections to be able to connect to the intelligence of a spaceship. They could be directly connected to any target system as long as they were within range of the transmitter.

As Han Xiao manipulated the data, he commanded, "Risda, help me crack the firewall!"

Although this should be Phillip's task, Risda's processing efficiency was higher than Phillip's, and the help that he could offer would be greater.

As Han Xiao proceeded with the data invasion, the BlackLight Stealth launched. Due to its powerful engine, the spaceship quickly reached the sky, circling around the thirty DarkStar assault ships as it rained down gunfire.

Boom boom boom!

Numerous lasers hit the shields of the enemy ships but were unable to pierce through.

The assault ships also fired a few potshots in the direction of the BlackLight Stealth, but they were helpless against the high specs of the BlackLight Stealth. The commander saw that there was only one spaceship, and since it could not break through their shields, they allowed it to remain like a fly buzzing around their heads as they concentrated their fire on the ground below.

Through the satellites, the top brass of the Six Nations watched the battle unfold in the sky with bated breath.

Because Godora was not reliable, the last line of defense on Planet Aquamarine was Black Star. However, it looked like he was unable to stop the advance of the enemy. In the underground fortress where the top brass of the Six Nations hid, a sense of despair slowly suffused.

At this point, a shield on one of the assault ships suddenly flickered and vanished. The next moment, the laser of the BlackLight Stealth accurately hit the hull of the ship, piercing through the armor and causing it to explode.

Bang!

Flames roared toward the sky, and black smoke billowed as the assault ship suddenly lost control. Its tail swayed, ramming into its companion. The DarkStar members in both ships tumbled till they could not differentiate the ground from the sky.

"It hit!"

The top brass of the Six Nations suddenly felt their spirits being renewed!

On the BlackLight Stealth, the virtual interface in front of Han Xiao had changed to a projection of the DarkStar assault ship. This was the one that they had succeeded in destroying.

Han Xiao was controlling the projection, which would feed the response directly back to the assault ship's main body. He was the one who had turned off the shield generator of the assault ship.

"Done!"

The corners of Han Xiao's mouth curved up, and he took a look at the interface as messages flowed out repeatedly.

You have used [Virtual Intrusion] on number D065 of the DarkStar assault ship...

Beginning to crack the firewall (Level 3)...

Undergoing first level of authentication...

Authentication passed!

Undergoing second level of authentication....

Authentication passed!

Undergoing third level of authentication....

Authentication passed!

Intrusion successful! You have succeeded in gaining control of the D065 DarkStar assault ship!

Privilege Level: Medium

Data has been sampled!

Backup generation complete!

The next time an intrusion is done to a similar smart machine: +10% Success Rate, +25% Speed.

Your authority has been blocked by the other party's Virtual Intelligence. Undergoing authentication... Authentication successful!

You have successfully retained your privileges!

Time until next authentication: 16 seconds

Chapter 540: Virtual Intrusion (2)

So long as the machine could be remotely controlled, the virtual intrusion skill could tamper with the data to gain operational authority, snatching command of the machinery. Spaceships were naturally included within the scope.

The difficulty of the intrusion would depend on the intelligence level of the target machinery. Furthermore, even if the invasion was successful, they would be constantly harassed by the opposing party's artificial intelligence. One had to successfully break past the artificial intelligence before they could retain the command authority.

As for the operational authority, it could be understood as how many commands that would be unlocked by the user.

Once the first intrusion was successful and intelligence data from the target had been recorded, the subsequent intrusions would decrease in difficulty. As such, in galactic wars, Virtual Mechanics were to most hated class of all. Every mechanic that got attacked by such methods would feel as though their wives had been taken advantage of by another man, giving them the feel of a cuckold.

This ability of the Virtual Mechanic was very suitable for space warfare. In fact, among the five Superhuman classes, the Virtual Mechanic was the class with the highest efficiency.

The defense of the spaceship's firewall was very strong. According to Han Xiao's standard, his success rate was not high, but having an auxiliary intelligence on his side improved the success rate as well as intrusion speed. Risda was an AI lifeform, with a startling operation speed that could increase the chances of success by thirty to forty percent.

On the battlefield, Han Xiao took over an assault ship, first opening fire at it and crippling its systems, before manipulating it to crash toward its companions surrounding it and disrupting their formation.

The DarkStar strike force jumped in shock at the unexpected turn of events. They had originally thought that the BlackLight Stealth would be unable to break through their defenses, so they had paid them no attention. To think that they actually managed to crack their firewall and invade their assault ships! They could no longer ignore that potential deadly threat.

The strike force assigned ten spaceships to entangle with the BlackLight Stealth, and the remainder continued firing on the surface whilst stretching their formation.

The reaction of the enemy was within Han Xiao's expectations. As long as he managed to divert some firepower away from the surface, more time could be won for them. The BlackLight Stealth possessed high capabilities, with speed as its biggest advantage. Ginette's maneuvering skills were also excellent, allowing them to constantly avoid the crisscrossing green lights.

Boom!

In the sky, a sleek, black spaceship was weaving left and right amid the ten assault ships.

"The fastest way to get rid of these enemies is through boarding them! Other than those operating the ship, everyone is to occupy a hatch, ready to occupy the enemy's ships!" Han Xiao commanded loudly as he activated his Void Dragon Mechanical Suit. He connected his mechanical suit to the BlackLight Stealth, and with a flash on his arm, a virtual intrusion interface appeared in the form of a projection above his arm. In this way, he eliminated the need to stay in the spaceship to operate the virtual intrusion, allowing him to move to the hatch like everyone else.

Since he was an essential part of their combat force, Han Xiao had to utilize himself in the battle.

"The enemy has thirty assault ships, and we cannot make it in time if we intrude them one by one. Thus, we can only use more destructive means." A glint flashed through Han Xiao's eyes, and the data inputted by him also changed.

There existed many forms of virtual technology intrusion. One was to forcefully rob control from the original owner, which was the most time consuming. Other than that, one could also use different means to tamper with the enemy's data in order to conceal or confuse. This was usually used for single infiltrations. As for the most destructive form, it would be utilizing a virus or flooding the system with large amounts of redundant data to destroy the intelligence of the target AI, crippling most of its functions for a short amount of time. This method was the fastest, equivalent to sending a direct punch to the person.

However, the most direct method would be to simply allow one's side to fight against the enemy's AI. For someone at the level of Risda, the DarkStar assault ships were not even at the level of little toddlers when facing him. When facing such tool-type AIs that had not developed independent thought, he could just destroy them with a wave of his hand.

If one likened robbing control of an AI to stealing one's wife, then destroying the intelligence was akin to breaking the other party's wife!

On the data stream level, Risda resembled a Fixed Star, emitting countless heat and light rays. As for the firewall on the assault ships, they were akin to shields on the data stream level, constantly forming large holes due to being pierced and the intelligent structure inside being shot and riddled with holes.

The results of the battle in the data world were immediately reflected into the material world.

Ohm!

With a chain of loud noises as the only indication, the engines of four of the assault ships suddenly stalled. They quickly tumbled down, their shields flickering before vanishing completely.

The AIs of the affected ships had fallen into a slump, unable to continue operating the ships for a short period of time. The pilots scrambled for the controls, attempting to switch over to manual mode during free fall. There was indeed plenty of time to switch to manual mode before the spaceship crashed.

However, the BlackLight Stealth suddenly dived, and their laser cannons locked onto the four assault ships, firing continuously.

Peng peng peng!

The outer armor of the four assault ships was blown open.

At the same time, taking advantage of its speed, the BlackLight Stealth swept past the four assault ships that were free falling, and the hatch opened to release the mercenaries. The grapples on their arms shot out and latched onto the armor of the assault ships before contracting and allowing the mercenaries to invade the enemy.

While the DarkStar ships might have lost their shields, the armor plating on the ships still boasted a certain amount of defense. A beam from the laser cannon would not be able to blow the ship up so easily. Thus, the fastest way to eliminate them was to destroy the ship from the inside!

In addition, as long as they boarded the enemy ship, not only would they be able to blow the enemy out, they would also be able to use force to seize control of the spaceship!

Boom!

The invading mercenaries wantonly destroyed the insides of the spaceship. Flickers of lights constantly appeared within each assault ship, and the guards inside each DarkStar ship were completely unable to stop them. The command centers of each ship were wiped out.

The mercenaries quickly took over each spaceship. Because the AIs of the assault ships had already been turned into idiots by Risda, it was impossible for them to verify the pilot's authority. The mercenaries quickly switched to manual mode, obtaining control rights over the spaceship.

In an instant, Han Xiao's side gained four more battleships. The team immediately became stronger, as the four assault ships aimed at the other DarkStar ships and opened fire.

During this time, another six sieging assault ships had their AIs crippled, and the mercenaries rushed in to begin a grand killing.

Pa!

Flying through the gap in armor that was surrounded by flames, Han Xiao landed on the cabin aisle. The mechanical wings behind him automatically folded as his wrists threw out a large number of compressed orbs. As they landed, they transformed into dozens of leopard-type mechanical beasts as well as two Protectors. They opened fire in all directions.

Bang bang bang!

Lasers flew everywhere, blowing up various parts of the spaceship. The insides of the spaceship turned into a charred, smoky mess as the bulkheads were torn apart. Following these gaps, the machines marched toward other areas of the spaceship, cleaning up the DarkStar guards.

Han Xiao bumped his fists together, and two giant fists expanded, wrapping themselves around his arms. He did not need to follow the aisles, instead simply bashing through everything as he proceeded in a straight path. He left behind a wreckage of twisted metal.

He made a beeline directly toward the control room of the spaceship.

Dozens of DarkStar guards rushed to the scene, obstructing Han Xiao's path. One of the team leaders shouted, "Quickly, block him. Don't..."

Before he could even finish, Han Xiao waved his hand, his mechanical arm sending a huge slap over. Merely the wind pressure produced by the hand extinguished all the flames around him. Before the team leader could finish his words, his vision was fully occupied by Han Xiao's giant metal palm.

Bang!

A huge sound was heard as the giant mechanical palm slapped the team leader against the wall of the spaceship. A huge imprint was even left there!

When the palm was removed, only some residual flesh could be seen in the indent created. Blood was splattered all over the contact point. This Grade C DarkStar warrior had been killed in a second, even simpler than swatting a fly.

In such assault ships, the strongest would probably be a Grade C guard. The elites of Grade B and above would not appear in such a place.

The rest of the guards paled, but before they could even make a move, Han Xiao brought his palms in front. The fingers of the two giant hands closed together as the five fingers transformed into a drill, and it spun at high speed toward them.

Whir!

The drill bit created a howling gale as it spun!

The next moment, the two mechanical drills swept past with no one able to stop them. The screams of misery were deafening, but in less than three seconds, the guards that had been blocking his path were all shattered. This was the literal sense of offering one's life in sacrifice.

Blood drenched the surroundings, turning the place into something akin to a slaughterhouse. However, Han Xiao had long become familiar with such a picture, and his face remained impassive as he strode forward. He would not go easy, and those who blocked him would immediately be killed.

There was nobody that was his match on the ship. Amid the explosions and screams of misery, Han Xiao began a matchless killing spree as he rushed to the control center. Behind him was a series of warped metal holes that created.

The whole journey took less than a minute, as though he had entered an empty ship!

In no time, Han Xiao destroyed anything that could breathe in the control room and came in front of the operations panel, directly taking over the assault ship. Immediately, he pulled the ship to accelerate up like a madman, even as he split his attention in that dizzy scenario to continue his virtual intrusion.

In order to save time, he was prepared not to return to the BlackLight Stealth, instead driving the hacked assault ship to ram the enemy.

The machinery that was clearing the rest of the ship of living beings quickly came to the control panel. They transformed back to compressed orbs, automatically moving to Han Xiao's hands.

Taking this short respite, Han Xiao eyeballed the mission interface.

The [Godora's Ally] was a Main Storyline mission, with the objective being to fight against DarkStar. There were several sub-missions, including a requirement of having to destroy the DarkStar spaceships. This included [Fleet Killer] and [Frontal Battle], which were high reward tasks. The easiest among them would be the [Assault Ship Destroyer], which required one to destroy five DarkStar assault ships to complete. The reward was 6,300,000 experience and 300 Godora Favorability.

An idea suddenly surfaced in his mind.

"That's right. This mission should originally have been the main storyline of the players, but since they did not join the Godoran faction, I guess they cannot trigger this..."

The corners of Han Xiao's mouth tugged up, but he quickly refocused his attention. Goodness, since he was fighting, he just needed to concentrate on fighting! He should not think about such trivial matters like the players being obstructed. It had almost made him feel guilt!

He increased the engine thrust, rushing toward another ship. As the distance shortened, the other party's hull constantly enlarged in his own field of vision, allowing him to clearly see the outer armor of the enemy ship.

Boom!

The two assault ships collided into each other, and the bow of the ship pierced into the abdomen of the other assault ship. Shrapnel flew all over the place!

Han Xiao drove the spaceship at close range as he opened fire, blasting several holes in the armor. He then smashed apart the walls of his current ride to fly outside, entering the other enemy ship to once again begin another round of slaughter.

The DarkStar assault ships begin to plummet one by one. Some fell down to the ground, whereas some were taken over by the mercenaries and used against their enemies. There were even some that exploded in midair. The Black Star Mercenary Group quickly gained control of the situation, surrounding the remaining DarkStar ships.

At the same time, the Six Nations and Sanctuaries were observing through Natural Satellite imagery. Upon seeing Black Star show his power, all of them could not help but let out jubilant looks on their faces, a wave of joy coursing through their hearts.

This sort of reliable feeling... was akin to Black Star being the guardian of the entire planet!

Chapter 541: Escaping After Provoking Me? Not Going to Happen!

Far away in the intense battlefield between the Godoran and DarkStar fleet, Nakapu received news that Black Star had managed to block the sudden ambush and was even trying to wipe them out. A strange look could be seen on his face before his brows began to furrow.

"Black Star actually has such strength? This isn't compatible with the intelligence!"

They had formulated their battle plan based on the intel that they had, and the error of the intel had resulted in them underestimating the strength of their enemies. As such, a huge error had been made in the development of their battle plan, and the state of the battle was not in their favor. Nakapu's expression was no longer calm, and a grave look could be seen on his face.

"Black Star managed to protect Planet Aquamarine, and the small fleet won't be of much use. With the strength that he has shown, even if the assault force were to retreat, they would definitely suffer a huge loss. The fleet under my command is tangled together with Godora, and if this situation drags on, it is very likely that Godora will send reinforcements..."

After pondering for a few seconds, Nakapu came to a conclusion. The ambush mission had failed!

"All forces take note. Cease battle and retreat immediately!"

Knowing that he had already failed, Nakapu was not willing to continue the battle and decisively ordered a retreat.

The DarkStar fleet broke away from battle and began their retreat. Because the Godoran fleet used space jamming equipment, the DarkStar fleet was not able to speed up and jump into dark space. Thus, DarkStar was trying to break away from the Godoran fleet and counter the effects of the space jamming equipment with their own equipment. The further the distance between them and the Godoran fleet, the easier it would be for them to get rid of the interference.

This meant that the DarkStar fleet would be able to escape the moment they pulled away a certain distance.

Nakapu's face was expressionless as he stared at the porthole with the colorful explosions from the battlefield being reflected on his face.

This was the first time that DarkStar had suffered a loss in an ambush mission. Thinking about it, Nakapu's gaze turned cold.

If he had known of Black Star's strength, he would not have tried to minimize the loss of his forces and would have sent his entire fleet into a head on battle with Godora's defense line. However, there was no 'if' in this world. Since the outcome was already determined, there was no time for him to regret. He could only accept his defeat. Nakapu let out a sigh and calmed himself down.

He would never allow this to happen again.

Above Planet Aquamarine, the battle was in its most intense state. The spaceships that were under the control of the Black Star Mercenary Group had achieved a balance with the enemy's spaceships with their firepower being equal.

Boom!

An enemy ship had its protective shield destroyed under concentrated fire, and half of the ship was quickly smashed into bits. It then dove down toward the ground like a meteor, disappearing from the eyes of those present.

There were less than ten remaining DarkStar spaceships that received the retreat order from Nakapu and heaved sighs of relief as they hurriedly escaped from the battlefield. As they escaped, the mercenaries chased them while firing rapidly.

The mission for this assault force should have been extremely simple. They only needed to hover in space and continuously fire their cannons. However, they had never expected to receive retaliation from the Black Star Mercenary Group, and they actually were not a match for the other party! While they were superior in terms of numbers, their enemy's spaceship was too high ranked and could dodge the majority of their attacks. Furthermore, even if their attacks landed on the enemy's ship, their attacks were not even able to break the protective shield. On top of that, they were on the losing end when it came to the strength of their Supers. As long as the enemy boarded their ships, they were finished.

With their assault force suffering heavy losses, they did not want to stay there any longer but had no choice due to the orders from their higher ups. It could be said that the retreat order had come in an extremely timely manner.

"We finally chased the enemy away!"

Seeing the satellite image, the leaders of the Six Nations were overjoyed. The enemies had come ferociously, and the golden skinned freaks of Godora had abandoned them. Just when they thought that they were finished, Black Star had stood up and defended the planet from the incoming enemies. The various territories had only suffered minimal damage and were still in good condition.

This outcome was much better than what they had expected.

At this moment, Han Xiao returned to the BlackLight Stealth. Ginette turned around, and before she had the chance to be smug, she was grabbed by the shoulders and thrown from the pilot's seat into Sylvia.

"Aiyoh!" Ginette and Sylvia were both sent rolling on the ground.

"Ow ow ow..." Sylvia rubbed her head and took a deep breath. Her head had been smashed by Ginette's Battle Suit.

Ginette rubbed her ass, and a trace of anger could be seen on her face. "Oi, why are you throwing me around? I am a girl! Can't you be gentler!"

Han Xiao could not be bothered to deal with her and took his mechanical suit off before sitting in the pilot's seat. Rubbing his wrists, he said in a low voice, "The battle isn't over yet, and the enemy's flagship is still in battle with Godora's fleet. We will be able to reach the battlefield quickly with BlackLight Stealth's speed, and this is the best chance to deal the enemy a heavy blow. Tell the others to remain on Planet Aquamarine. I will be back quickly."

At this moment, Herlous had just returned to the BlackLight Stealth. After hearing those words when he entered the door, he turned around and jumped out without hesitation!

What a joke! He obviously was not willing to ride a spaceship piloted by Black Star!

"You want to interfere in that battle‽" Ginette was startled. "We've already blocked the enemy, so there isn't a need for us to participate in a head on battle."

Han Xiao shook his head. "We have only defeated a couple of spaceships attempting to ambush us. This isn't a big loss to DarkStar. The commander of the enemy forces is the key. Since he dared ambush us, we must give him a good fight!"

His target was the enemy's flagship, not the escaping spaceships. As the old saying went—Don't chase a poor thief. It meant that he should not chase an enemy without money! At least this was how the Great Mechanic Han understood it.

Thus, he would go after the leader!

After exposing his strength, DarkStar would definitely refresh their intel on him, and the enemy would definitely come up with measures to deal with him in the future. Unless he could secretly scam another wave of players, it would not be possible for DarkStar to receive another error in their intelligence. Thus, it would be best for him to make use of this opportunity to increase his battle merits. Defeating a DarkStar flagship was also a mission requirement in the mission [Godora's Ally].

Han Xiao piloted the BlackLight Stealth out of the atmosphere and locked onto the coordinates of the battlefield. It was still a distance away from him.

According to the information from Godora, it seems like the enemy was currently retreating. With the speed and stealth abilities of BlackLight Stealth, he was definitely capable of arriving at the battlefield in time.

The next moment, BlackLight Stealth transformed into a ray of light and disappeared from sight.

The ray of light stopped a short distance away from the battlefield. If they went any further, they would be in the region of the space jamming region. The chaotic battlefield was right before their eyes with bright colorful balls of exploding cannons all over the place. The powerful homing missiles exploded into a huge ball of flames, and the plasma cannons melted the protective shields of the spaceships.

"What an intense battle..." Han Xiao's gaze swept past the radar. "DarkStar is indeed retreating. The largest spaceship in the middle should be the flagship."

Locking onto his target, Han Xiao estimated the distance. He needed to enter the battlefield for the enemy's flagship to be within the range of his Data Transmitter. Furthermore, the AI of the enemy's flagship would definitely have a stronger defense.

"Nagakin, I am settled on my side. What about you?"

With the transmission being connected, Nagakin's appearance could be seen. His spaceship was currently the target of the enemy's fire and was facing an endless wave of attacks. The spaceship was currently trying its best to avoid all the incoming attacks and could not approach the enemy's spaceship.

"Black Star? You are on the battlefield‽"

Han Xiao nodded. "Long story short, I can infiltrate the AI of the enemy, so I am preparing to attack the enemy's flagship. If you can approach the enemy, I will be able to disable the nearest few frigates and create an opportunity for you to charge the enemy ship."

Hearing that, Nagakin's eyes lit up. "Alright! Let's do that!"

At the same time, Barette's voice sounded in the communicator. "We can try that. My fleet will try to restrain the enemy's fire and allow Officer Nagakin's ship to approach the enemy's flagship."

Based on his judgement, Barette knew that it would be impossible to sink DarkStar's fleet. He had just received news of the battle at Planet Aquamarine, so he had confidence in Han Xiao's strength.

While he was not concerned about Planet Aquamarine, Barette did not dare underestimate and doubt Han Xiao's strength.

To create a mercenary group with some fame in the Shattered Star Ring in a few years, he naturally was not someone to be underestimated. He definitely had the strength to back up his fame.

Ginette's face changed color upon hearing that. "We are charging into the battlefield‽ It is far too risky! Cannon fire is flying in all directions, and even I'm not confident in avoiding all those attacks. This is only a small spaceship, and a single mistake will put us in grave danger!"

"Humph, my piloting skills have been tested through time. I wouldn't make a mistake." Han Xiao shook his wrists and sped up while shouting, "Sit tight!"

The BlackLight Stealth sped up rapidly and sliced straight into the battlefield. It swerved past the chaotic attacks and weaved through the battlefield through rolling, abruptly stopping, diving, cycling around, and many more other piloting techniques. It was like an agile black bird freely roaming the chaotic battlefield, easily passing through the gaps in the endless lights of battle.

The view outside the ship was spinning, and Ginette hurriedly tied herself to her seat. At the beginning, she was afraid that Han Xiao would make a mistake. After focusing her attention on the outside for a short while, her entire brain seemed to be spinning, and her face became completely pale with the urge to vomit at any moment.

"Slow... slow down. I can't see clearly!" Ginette could not help but yell out. She had never imagined that Han Xiao's piloting skills were superior to even hers. This skill of his was sufficient to be the ace pilot of any organization!

"Heh, since you are not piloting the ship, why do you need to see clearly?" Han Xiao clicked his tongue.

Ginette turned around, and her eyes widened in shock. She saw Han Xiao using a few mechanical arms controlled by his nerves to control the spaceship while he attempted to infiltrate the AI of the enemy's ship. He was actually doing two things at once.

Sylvia was frightened to the point her face turned pale. "Te... Teacher, please don't be a reckless pilot!"

"Don't make noise. I am busy. Don't distract me."

The moment the BlackLight Stealth entered the battlefield, the DarkStar fleet noticed their entrance. With a single look, Nakapu's expression changed.

"This is Black Star's spaceship! Why is he here?"

All of a sudden, Nakapu thought about the battle report from the assault force and roared, "Not good! He is here for revenge. Everyone, listen up. Don't let that black spaceship come near us!"

Nakapu could not help but be wary of Black Star's hacking abilities. If he got close to their ship, their flagship will probably be infiltrated, and they would be in danger.

DarkStar's fleet immediately changed targets, and the BlackLight Stealth immediately faced a greater amount of pressure. They also changed their formation, and the blood colored flagship no longer stayed in the middle of the formation but flew toward the front in an attempt to distance themselves from Han Xiao.

"It seems like they have noticed me," Han Xiao said with a frown. "Don't want me to get close?"

Right at that moment, Barette's fleet began their retaliation and suppressed DarkStar's fleet. At the same time, they began tearing apart the rearguard of DarkStar to create a gap for BlackLight Stealth to enter.

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled, and he immediately piloted his ship into the gap. With his piloting skills, even with the focused fire from the enemy, he was like a fish in water.

The BlackLight Stealth was a stealth spaceship created with the technology of the Federation of Light, and its speed was far superior to the technology of Godora and DarkStar. It was a pity that BlackLight Stealth did not have the weapons of the Federation of Light. If he had a Particle Cannon equipped, he would have been able to shoot through the defenses of a few dozen spaceships, and there would have been no need to go through this hassle.

There were differences in the strength of particle cannons, and it was dependent on the technique of the user and caliber of the energy source. The particle cannons used by Godora and DarkStar were all ordinary goods in the universe.

At the same time, a warning signal was given in the enemy's flagship.

"Warning! The battleship is being infiltrated! Please take appropriate measures! Warning! The..."

The warning sound from the battleship's AI became white noise, and Nakapu's expression darkened.

"Sh*t!"

Hum!

All of a sudden, all the lights shut down, and the engine of the battleship stalled. The speed of the battleship plummeted, and the DarkStar battleships behind it overtook it immediately. The flagship fell to the rear of the formation, and even its communication channel was cut off.

The entire battleship was overly reliant on AI support. The moment the AI was paralyzed, the entire battleship would be paralyzed. If they wanted to pilot the ship manually, their reaction speed could not keep up with that of an AI.

As long as a Virtual Mechanic had the space to show his abilities, he would be the biggest killing weapon in the entire battlefield!

Bang! Bang! Bang!

All of a sudden, a couple of banging sounds could be heard from the outside of the ship as though something had banged onto the body of the ship. However, with the AI of the ship paralyzed, there was no way to know what was going on.

But with a simple guess, the members on board the ship knew what was about to happen and hopelessness could be seen on their faces.

"It's... it's Nagakin..."

Nakapu's fingers trembled. He was finally afraid.

Chapter 542: I'll Give You Another Chance to Repeat Yourself

Seeing Nagakin board the DarkStar flagship, Han Xiao knew that the enemy flagship was finished.

With the flagship in danger, the DarkStar fleet at the front did not turn back to reinforce their comrades. It was almost certain that Nakapu would end up in Nagakin's hands, and the DarkStar fleet was completely helpless. All the officers a level lower hurriedly took over command of the fleet and repeated Nakapu's orders to retreat. They then made use of the opportunity where the attention of the Godora fleet was attracted by their flagship and ran for their lives.

On the other side, the DarkStar assault forces had also broken free from the forty or so Godoran battleships and escaped in a different direction.

The DarkStar fleet abandoned their flagship and escaped with their tails between their legs. Only the flagship was left behind, deep within the enemy formation like a bunch of hunting dogs surrounding a lonely wolf.

The BlackLight Stealth hovered not too far away, and Han Xiao did not join in the fun. With Nagakin causing destruction within the interior of the ship, there was no need for him to take action. At this moment, he had his attention on something else.

"Risda, are you able to connect to DarkStar's main system through the enemy's AI and infiltrate DarkStar's main database?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin as he pondered. All the spaceships in the same organization would usually use a child AI from the main system so that it would be easier to manage the entire battle. Just like how Phillip was in charge of controlling ten or so spaceships in his mercenary group. As long as a spaceship was equipped with Phillip's duplicate microchip, Phillip would be able to open up a new channel of operation.

The child AI would be related to the main AI. Usually, a DarkStar mothership would use a main AI, and all the subsidiary spaceships under its command would use the mothership's child AI. If they are able to track the communication route between the two systems, they might be able to lock onto the position of a DarkStar mothership and find their coordinates in the vast universe.

Risda's voice sounded like a bucket of cold water. "Not possible. Before the enemy's AI was paralyzed, it cut off all its connection with the main system. This is a very common way to prevent infiltration from the enemy. The AI of the other spaceships check its identification number and ensure that the connection is trusted before allowing it to reconnect with the main system."

"DarkStar is still extremely careful." Han Xiao nodded. This was an extremely simple method. If there were two spaceships, A and B, that used the same child AI, the moment A noticed that it had been infiltrated, it would automatically cut off all connections with the main system. It would not be able to share any data with the main system, and the main system would not be able to determine A's position and status.

After A solved its infiltration problem, if B's data its within its range, the child AI of B would automatically evaluate A's AI. Only after ensuring that A was safe would B send the signal back to the main system and allow A to connect back to the main system. Currently, the flagship that had been left behind had naturally severed all of its connections, so it would be impossible to infiltrate the main system.

DarkStar made use of such a system in order to protect the coordinates of its mothership. The Great Mechanic Han was not the only Mechanic Hacker in the universe, and there were plenty of them all around the universe. DarkStar needed to guard against this point.

While he found it to be a bit of a waste, Han Xiao was not too disappointed. If it was this easy to lock on to DarkStar's position, DarkStar would have been long destroyed by Godora.

While he did not take a very long time to paralyze the enemy's flagship, Han Xiao's hacking skills was far from being able to easily infiltrate an enemy spaceship. Risda was an important assistant of his, and the efficiency of this AI lifeform was extremely high. It was far superior to Phillip and greatly strengthened Han Xiao's skill judgement.

It was a pity that Risda was a free man... er, free AI and did not belong to him. Who knew when he would be able to strengthen Phillip to be on the same level as Risda? Stroking his chin, he wondered if he could get Risda to help raise Phillip's level.

After all, the one who understood AIs the most would be an AI. The growth of Risda's species would be determined by the exchange of data and upgrading each other's software. If that was the case, Risda should be able to help Phillip optimize his structure.

Ginette and Sylvia stared at each other. One of them was a Cannon Master, and the other was a Mechanical Pugilist. Hearing a Mechanic and an AI lifeform having a conversation about Artificial Intelligence, they felt a great upgrade in their intelligence.

Sylvia felt as though she had forgotten about something. After pondering for a long while, she came to a realization. She had been too busy being shocked previously, and it was time for her to vomit for a while.

After waiting for a moment, Nagakin finally sent news about his success. He had successfully taken control of the enemy's flagship. Han Xiao and Barette both boarded the enemy's flagship and saw Nagakin in the control room, together with a large bunch of captured DarkStar members.

"Well done! Truly the famous Officer Nagakin." Barette was overjoyed.

Nagakin waved his hands and calmly replied, "This isn't my merit. It is all thanks to Black Star. If not for him paralyzing the enemy's spaceship, it would have been impossible for me to unleash my strength. He is the one with the biggest merit."

"Haha, you are right," Barette said with a smile. "Black Star truly lives up to his name."

"It's nothing. I didn't do much," Han Xiao replied humbly.

After a short conversation, everyone got to work and calculated their gains and losses.

Godora had lost fewer than ten battleships and destroyed a similar number of enemy battleships. Furthermore, they had been able to capture an enemy flagship together with its command team. They would be able to interrogate these members after this and find out about DarkStar's plans. Together with Black Star taking care of the ten or so assault battleships that had appeared suddenly, they had earned a huge amount in this battle!

After suffering from plenty of losses, Godora had finally achieved a victory. The War Bureau could finally heave a sigh of relief.

Nakapu looked up, and his gaze swept over the control room. Barette? A radical commander who had been played a fool by him and could not enter his sights. Nagakin? A famous high-ranking member of the War Bureau. While powerful, he was not the deciding factor in this battle.

Finally, Nakapu's gaze landed on Han Xiao like a nail. This was the person who had decided the result of the battle!

Nakapu felt that his loss was due to the underestimation of Black Star's strength. If not for a problem with their intel, the assault force would have easily ambushed Planet Aquamarine and escaped. At the same time, he would have been able to escape as well.

He had never imagined that he would be caught.

"A single mistake cost us the entire battle..." Nakapu's eyes turned dim. He knew that there was no chance for him to make a comeback.

In the last three minutes of the DarkStar fleet's escape, the loss of their flagship and the news of Nakapu being captured was quickly sent back to DarkStar's headquarters. This was the first time that they had suffered a loss in an ambush mission, and the attention of the upper echelons was immediately drawn.

The entire battle was not too long, and the upper echelons in the headquarters had quickly understood the situation. At this moment, the highest in command present was the vice leader of DarkStar, another doyen who was just as experienced as Anur. His name was Degulish, and he was a stern individual with great prestige.

"Black Star again!"

Degulish frowned with dissatisfaction in his tone. After the incident with Anur, DarkStar harbored great enmity toward Han Xiao, but due to it being the crux of their mission, they did not take their revenge. After all, Han Xiao had Floating Dragon as his backing, and DarkStar was not willing to provoke Ames.

The scene of a DarkStar mothership being smashed into smithereens by an island was still deeply imprinted in their minds.

But now, DarkStar had once again obstructed their plans. Degulish was not as composed a person as the leader of DarkStar. Now that their leader was personally carrying out a secret mission, he was the one in charge of the headquarters. Furthermore, his style had always been extremely aggressive.

"He's provoked us over and over again, and it's time for us to help him understand what kind of an existence he is provoking. I want to make him pay the price for his wrongdoing," Degulish said in a low voice. "Ah, doesn't he want to protect his homeland? Send out two DarkStar motherships and destroy Planet Aquamarine!"

"Vice leader, this isn't in line with our plans. We shouldn't destroy a calamity planet," the one in charge of intel said.

"I remember Ember suggesting that we should get rid of Black Star regardless of the cost, and his words make some sense. We have more than ten calamity planets, and destroying a single one won't affect the big picture," Degulish replied.

If Ember was there, he would definitely have raised both his arms in agreement. It was a pity that he was not present at this meeting.

More accurately, most of the upper echelons were not present in the meeting as they were all carrying out various missions. While ambushing a calamity planet seemed to be DarkStar's only mission on the surface, a large number of their upper echelons were out on missions in secret.

The one in charge of intel shook his head. "This is on the basis that we will be able to kill him. If not, we will only be wasting our ships. He has a BlackLight Stealth that he got from who knows where, and this is a high-quality spaceship from the Federation of Light. It will be impossible for us to capture him."

Degulish frowned. "He can run, but Planet Aquamarine won't be able to escape!"

The one in charge of intel shook his head. "If Planet Aquamarine is his weakness, it would be a waste to destroy it."

"A waste? What are your thoughts?"

"Black Star is only a mercenary. According to my observations, he has always been going against us either because Godora hired him or because we took the initiative to attack him. Of course, I am not trying to speak up on his behalf. Regardless of the reason, he still has to pay the price.

"The problem is, if we destroy his only weakness, he won't have any more apprehensions and will go all out to fight us. He may even seek aid from Ames, and this isn't to our advantage."

"Since when have we been afraid of others?" Degulish said in a cold tone. "I can easily crush a Mechanic of Black Star's standard with a casual clench of my fists. So, what about the Dragon Emperor? Will she be able to find us?"

"What I mean is, since Black Star is protecting Planet Aquamarine, it means that he cares about this planet," the one in charge of intel said with his eyes narrowed. "It would be extremely easy for us to destroy Planet Aquamarine. Why don't we use this as a handle to threaten him when necessary? He will then feel true regret and may even be forced to work for us."

As Degulish heard that, his expression changed and felt that those words made sense.

"My subordinates will continue to gather news about Black Star. Black Star is a subordinate of the Dragon Emperor, and we may be able to achieve an unexpected result by making use of him. The concealed team left behind on Planet Aquamarine have been monitoring his actions. While the Godoran radar is able to use tracking methods within a certain distance, the concealed team shut down the engines of their spaceship, and they're only maintaining their stealth functions. As long as they do not turn on their engines, they won't be exposed. I am prepared to arrange spies in the Black Star Mercenary Group. They are only a bunch of mercenaries. As long as we pay the price, there isn't such a thing as loyalty. We will plant some spies within their group and monitor all of his actions."

The failure of their assault mission was like a spark that caused DarkStar to place their attention on Han Xiao. Since they could not fight head on, they would employ their methods in the dark. In any case, they had many methods up their sleeves.

After thinking for a moment, Degulish finally nodded. "Do as you have planned."

"I recommend you don't attack Planet Aquamarine in the near future. Just as you have said, it is only a single calamity planet, and it won't affect the big picture. Furthermore, we will have to pay a large price if we want to attack Planet Aquamarine with Black Star around, so the losses will outweigh the gains."

As everyone returned to Planet Aquamarine, the BlackLight Stealth landed in the Sanctuary. At this moment, nine DarkStar assault spaceships were parked in the Sanctuary. These were the new spaceships that the mercenaries had captured.

Of the thirty DarkStar spaceships that had attacked, a portion of them had been destroyed, and fewer than ten spaceships managed to escape. The Black Star Mercenary Group had captured all the remaining spaceships. While all of them were damaged in one way or another, all the spaceships still had their basic functions.

Han Xiao was in a pleasant mood. Nine small-sized assault spaceships was a great harvest. If he calculated according to their cost, these spaceships would be worth over a million Enas. The most valuable areas of these spaceships were their energy cores, engines, protective shields, and particle cannons. Taking all these away, the value of the spaceships would be decreased to a fifth of their original value. If the cores of those spaceships that had crash landed were not destroyed, some materials and spare parts could be salvaged, which would be an unexpected gain.

This ambush mission did not result in much of a loss for Han Xiao but allowed him to earn a tidy sum instead. With those assault spaceships, the firepower of his fleet would be greatly increased. Han Xiao was overjoyed and wished that those fellows from DarkStar to come more often and allow him the chance to expand his fleet.

Just when Han Xiao was prepared to board the ship to inspect the assault spaceship, Barette landed as well.

Walking over, Barette's eyes swept over the surroundings. Nodding solemnly, he said, "Black Star, you did well this time. My men will come over and takeover these spoils of war. It has been hard on all of you this time."

Han Xiao's footsteps paused abruptly, and he looked at Barette's confident expression with a frown.

"What?"

Chapter 543: Butterfly Effect

Han Xiao was taken aback and had a strange look on his face.

All of these assault spaceships were obviously his spoils of war. Why did Barette suddenly want them?

A couple of guesses flashed through his head, but he quickly eliminated them all. Just a few small-sized assault spaceships were not enough to make Godora interested. Could it be that Barette wants these spaceships to increase his battle merits? However, that did not seem likely either. According to how Barette behaved when they were fighting together, while Barette could not be bothered about Planet Aquamarine, Barette showed a basic level of respect toward him. At the very least, Barette would not come into a conflict with him because of these little spoils of war.

Barette's face was extremely calm and did not appear guilty in any way. Han Xiao could not help but emphasize. "Are you sure that these assault spaceships are your spoils of war? Why do I remember that I was the one who shot them down?"

"Indeed, that is so." Barette nodded. "According to the procedures recorded, all the losses suffered by DarkStar in the calamity planets will be Godora's spoils of war. This is the most basic requirement for us to protect the calamity planets."

"Procedures?"

"Oh, this is the rule that the War Bureau set."

You want me to follow the rules that Godora set? With a frown, Han Xiao said, "You guys gave up on Planet Aquamarine at the most critical moment, resulting in the enemy's assault spaceships entering the atmosphere. At the very end, I was the one who defeated the enemy."

Barette shook his head and said, "We didn't give up. We were only applying pressure on the enemy's forces. After all, it was too late for us to send reinforcements, and we only made the most appropriate decision in the ever-changing battlefield. If not for my fleet tangling with majority of DarkStar's fleet, you would have faced an enemy many times your size. Thus, it can be said that we exerted a greater amount of strength in this battle. I hope that you will cooperate with me."

Han Xiao narrowed his eyes.

Indeed, without Godora's fleet facing the enemy, he would have had to face more than just a small assault force, and it would have been difficult for him to achieve the current victory. For Godora to protect the planets, they naturally did not want to put in effort for nothing, and all the spoils of war obtained by the calamity planet would have to be given to them.

While it sounded logical on the surface, he would only have to follow the so-called procedures set by Godora if he was a subordinate under Planet Aquamarine's regime. However, while Han Xiao was protecting Planet Aquamarine, he was an independent entity, and Godora's rules would not be able to govern him. It would be impossible for him to comply, and there was no need for him to behave meekly either.

"There seems to be something that you aren't clear about. I am the head of a Mercenary Group and the Field Team of Floating Dragon. I am not part of the regime of a backward planet that you can order around as you wish." Han Xiao's eyes gleamed coldly, and he said slowly, "What right do you have to order me around?"

Barette's face darkened, and he glared at Han Xiao.

This was a conflict of interest, and both parties glared at each other, refusing to give way. While Barette wanted to behave forcefully, he did not have the ability to command the famous Black Star. After all, Han Xiao's status was far superior to his in the universe. Han Xiao was a famous officer under Floating Dragon while he was an ordinary commander in Godora's War Bureau.

The situation there quickly drew the attention of those in the surroundings. The mercenaries, Godoran soldiers, and players all gathered around. Especially the players who had already turned on their recording features with Bun-Hit-Dog standing at the very front.

"What's going on?" Right at this moment, Nagakin walked over after noticing the commotion.

Barette helplessly explained what was going on. He did not feel that he was in the wrong and was only harvesting the spoils of war according to the procedures. Who would have thought that Han Xiao would not accept his request and end up in a face-off with him? Now that the high ranking Nagakin had arrived, he would have more backing, and Barette heaved a sigh of relief.

Yet, outside his expectations, Nagakin roared at him with displeasure after hearing what had happened. "Barette! Are you an idiot‽"

"Ah?" Barette was stunned.

"If not for Black Star joining the battle, we would only have been able to watch as the DarkStar fleet escaped from us. Who do you think is the one who helped us capture the DarkStar flagship‽" Nagakin roared at Barette. His rank was higher, so he had the right to reprimand Barette. When Barette refused to listen to his previous commands, Nagakin had already been dissatisfied with him. Now that he had the opportunity, he naturally would not show any mercy.

Black Star's status and strength were not to be estimated. Nagakin was not willing to ruin his relationship with Black Star over something so small. His status was higher than Barette's, and with him representing Godora in reprimanding Barette, it provided a way out of this stalemate.

Barette had initially thought that Nagakin would help him say a word, but never had he imagined that Nagakin would stand on Black Star's side. He was immediately depressed but could not interrupt Nagakin.

After a round of scolding, Nagakin looked at Han Xiao and said, "This is a misunderstanding."

"I guessed so." Han Xiao chuckled.

"You can deal with your spoils of war as you wish, and we won't interfere. Godora will never mistreat our friends." Nagakin nodded and dragged Barette away.

With the mini storm being settled, everyone in the surroundings heaved a sigh of relief. If the two protectors had broken out in a fight, all of them would definitely have felt anxious. Han Xiao's eyes narrowed as he witnessed the Godorans leaving without saying another word. He then called his fellow mercenaries to enter the assault ships and check the damage.

One would only gain respect with sufficient strength. If he had been an ordinary individual today without any fame, Nagakin would not have spoken up for him. This was something that Han Xiao was extremely clear about. He did not feel gratitude toward Nagakin because of today's event. Those Godorans were all the same. They were usually high above and would act according to the situation, afraid of the strong but bullying the weak. In fact, the majority of civilizations were as such, so it was nothing strange.

Nagakin's attitude today proved that his actions had finally given him a status that Godora would treat seriously. Han Xiao would not become proud because of this but would maintain his usual cool. As long as he had sufficient strength, everyone else would take the initiative to give him the respect that he deserved.

The small conflict that had happened there was quickly spread to the Six Nations through various channels. When the upper echelons of the Six Nations witnessed the respect that Godora gave Han Xiao and thought about their own status, they were certain that their previous promise to Black Star was the right decision.

On the forums, a couple of players asked around about the entire battle and managed to recreate the battle. They naturally did not like DarkStar, who caused them to have a drop in their Main Storyline Mission progress, and were even more dissatisfied with Godora, who had abandoned them at a critical juncture.

Only Han Xiao's performance did not disappoint the players. Not only was he able to defeat the enemies, he had even managed to capture the enemy flagship. While it could not be said that he single-handedly turned the entire battle around, he was definitely a large contributor toward the outcome of the battle. The players had always felt goodwill toward Han Xiao, and together with this forum post, all of their goodwill was increased even further.

People with a reliable vibe like him had always been popular. Together with his charisma, good public image, and suave appearance, Han Xiao was certain that he would be able to attract a great deal of female fans this time!

In actual fact, he would not mind if his fans were boorish men either. As long as they were fans, he would not reject them.

However, this did not result in more players wanting to join the Black Star Mercenary Group. From the very beginning, almost everyone had wanted to join the Black Star Mercenary Group. After operating for such a long period of time, the entire player market of Planet Aquamarine pretty much belonged to Han Xiao. He only needed to continue increasing the goodwill that the players felt toward him.

If he wanted another avenue of players, he would have to open another market, and it naturally was not time for that.

When the players were happily chatting on the forums, Han Xiao checked the interiors of the nine assault ships. The mercenaries had been too enthusiastic in their attacks, and the interiors of the spaceships were badly damaged. Furthermore, the AI systems would also have to be replaced and a series of maintenance done before the spaceships could be used.

Thankfully, the various spaceships that had crash landed on Planet Aquamarine were precious materials, so Han Xiao did not need to purchase replacement parts.

The destroyed spaceships were spread across almost half the planet. Some had fallen into the ocean while the others had fallen on earth. Through the radar of a spaceship, the locations of those spaceships could be located. Han Xiao sent out a portion of his mercenaries to salvage all of the spaceships. In a short two or three days, he would be able to recover all of the wreckages.

Han Xiao did not follow the mercenaries to take action. After upgrading his class to that of a Mechanic Hacker, he was able to merge a few valuable blueprints. Thus, he stayed behind in the Sanctuary and began building new machineries.

After this ambush, DarkStar would not attack Planet Aquamarine again in the short run, and he should be able to relax for a while.

On the Andrea continent, in the old address of the Germinal Organization...

Not too long ago, a meteor had landed from the skies and charred the entire earth. At the same time, a hundred-meter- long gorge had been created. When the dust settled, the only thing left behind had been a pile of wreckage. It was the DarkStar spaceship that had been shot down by the mercenary group.

A skeleton sat not too far away from the landing site, which stood up slowly, walking over unstably toward the wreckage.

The Mutation Source that was attached to the cervical vertebra could feel the powerful energy reaction from the wreckage. It was the energy core of the spaceship.

The radiation from the Germinal Organization had already been mostly absorbed by the Mutation Source, and the destroyed spaceship was just like a pie dropping from the skies.

The skeleton climbed into the cockpit of the spaceship and found the leaking energy core through its senses.

Countless hair-like black tentacles extended out from the Mutation Source and wrapped around the energy core of the spaceship like a spider about to devour its prey. The entire space around the region became distorted, and the pure energy began to seep into the Mutation Source. The tentacles began to bloat up and shrink back as it absorbed the pure energy.

The energy core of a spaceship contained a large amount of fuel. As the Mutation Source began to suck out all of the energy, the fuel from the energy core rapidly disappeared. At the same time, the speed at which the Mutation Source sucked out the energy also sped up. From the Mutation Source seemed to come the sound of a heart beating.

The energy core let out a final buzz and fell silent. Its light began to fade away, and it disappeared. The Mutation Source retracted all of its tentacles, and the skeleton remained on the ground.

All of a sudden, the Mutation Source began spitting out copious amounts of a black sticky substance. The sticky substance was extremely thick, but it seemed to have the slipperiness of oil. After releasing this sticky substance for half a day until the sticky substance covered the entire room, this strange behavior stopped.

The next moment, all of the sticky substance that had been shot out began flowing toward the skeleton in the middle of the room as though it was alive.

When the final bit of sticky substance had climbed up on the skeleton, the skeleton already looked completely different. It was no longer a rack of bones but had transformed into a black human body. The sticky substance seemed to have formed the flesh and muscles of the body, and the body looked extremely well built. The facial features began to take form; eyes, a nose, a mouth, and ears roamed around the face for a period of time before finding their appropriate place.

If Han Xiao was here, he would have realized that the appearance of the figure looked like the Germinal Organization's leader. It was just before he was disfigured.

The monster opened its mouth and let out an incomprehensible groan. To think that it even had vocal cords.

After absorbing a large amount of energy, the growth of the Mutation Source had skyrocketed. The Mutation Source no longer needed to convert all of its absorbed energy and could control a portion to go through cell division. Thus, that small pile of Mutation Source was able to spit out an entire room full of sticky substance.

The Mutation Source could enjoy the senses of numerous animals and understood the structure of different life forms. With the skeleton as the base, it was able to recreate the human body. This monster was not leeching onto a human body but simulating a human body. Apart from its entire body being black and the lack of sexual characteristics, it was no different from an ordinary body. The Mutation Source was wrapped up deep within the simulated body.

The simulated body lowered its head and observed its body through its eyes while touching all over its body curiously. While it could share the senses of all those infected, it was now able to control its own body, and this was an entirely different feeling. It could not help but have a strange feeling.

Freedom!

The intelligence of the Mutation Source had originally been operating only from instinct, but its thoughts began to form as it looked at the world around it.

Like a three-year-old child suddenly having memories, the world in front of it seemed so different.

"Air, hands, body..."

The simulated body let out a barely audible voice, and through the numerous shared senses it had, a massive wave of memories flooded its head, and the sense of fatigue quickly assaulted it.

The simulated body walked out of the cockpit. Looking in a direction, its figure disappeared over the horizon.

In another region of Planet Aquamarine, the concealed troops of DarkStar detected a rapid increase in the energy levels of the Mutation Source. All of the members were stunned.

Their information journal had recorded such circumstances. This indicated that the Mutation Source had absorbed energy to the point that it was saturated and was beginning its next stage of evolution!

The Mutation Source had evolved far earlier than in Han Xiao's previous life!

Chapter 544: Second Phase of the Mutation Disaster

A couple of days later...

"Ahhh..." The older Volga brother yawned and casually played a card. He then looked at Herlous and asked, "Oi, how much longer are we going to stay on this backward planet?"

At this moment, the mercenary group was playing cards and having a chat in the main hall. Upon hearing that question, they all turned around to look at Herlous.

"We can only leave this place after dealing with the problem on this planet. This isn't something that I can control." Herlous shook his head helplessly.

Everyone then looked toward a military factory outside the window. That was Han Xiao's machinery modification room. At this moment, Han Xiao was repairing the assault ships that they had just obtained.

The mercenaries had already stayed on Planet Aquamarine for more than a month. Apart from choosing new players, they did not have anything else to do, and all of them were extremely bored.

With the sights of these galactic mercenaries, they naturally found the entertainment located on Planet Aquamarine extremely boring. Apart from playing cards, a few of them felt as though their bodies were rusting. If their current mission had a reward, perhaps most of them would still be able to bear with this boredom. However, this was Black Star's command, and they had no choice but to obey his orders while looking forward to the matter being resolved.

After the failure of the previous ambush, DarkStar did not send anyone else to Planet Aquamarine again as though they were wary of the combined strength of Black Star and the Godoran fleet. But from time to time, news of the other calamity planets being ambushed could be heard.

As Godora sent more reinforcements to the other calamity planets, the ambushes of DarkStar were usually ineffective. Just like Planet Aquamarine, there were almost three hundred spaceships awaiting their orders outside Planet Aquamarine's atmosphere, and this was the same even around the other calamity planets. However, as the size of the DarkStar fleet grew larger, they also applied pressure to the Godoran forces.

Godora had to split up their forces to protect more than ten calamity planets. Their fleet was spread thinly, and their soldiers were insufficient. However, DarkStar did not have such a restriction, so they held the initiative.

The entire Garton Star System was like an abyss of suffering. On the other hand, Planet Aquamarine managed to defeat the enemies after suffering an ambush. Thus, their ability to cope with the calamity was pretty good, and the Six Nations were prospering.

In the military factory...

Clank!

A couple of mini assistive robots climbed up and down the body of the spaceship while attempting to repair the outer armor of the spaceship. Sparks could be seen flying all around, and the sound of hammering reverberated without end.

Han Xiao controlled a large mechanical arm, and it transformed into various different kinds of tools to repair the spaceships' damage. Apart from helping him in battle, this large mechanical arm could also be used to repair large spaceships. It was as though he had a huge hand that could be controlled like his own limbs.

The spaceship wreckages that the mercenaries had collected brought him sufficient materials. As such, he began to repair the spaceships that he had captured, and he was about eighty percent done. While repairing those spaceships only gave him a little bit of experience, it was better than nothing at all.

Han Xiao stopped his actions and said, "Damage check."

"Initiating a system check... Damage levels of the spaceship are at 0%..." The AI system of the ship had already been changed to Phillip.

Apart from repairing the assault ships, Han Xiao had also created a couple of delicate machines that could improve his hacking skills. It strengthened Phillip's calculation speed, and Risda had also restructured Phillip's calculation structure, allowing Phillip to be three times more efficient than before.

The machines under Phillip's control became much more efficient, and it also allowed his hacking skills to go up another level. Phillip was still a distance away from Risda, but strengthening and grooming one's own AI was a long-term job of a Mechanic Hacker. At the same time, he would be able to receive a great deal of benefits from doing so.

"The final spaceship has been repaired, and it can be used normally." Han Xiao nodded with satisfaction. Giving out a command, all the repair bots began to pack themselves up.

At this moment, the Black Star Mercenary Group was mainly using spaceships that were rented. These nine assault spaceships would be able to supplement their firepower and belonged completely to him.

After drinking a mouthful of water, Han Xiao took out his communicator and began browsing the mercenary group portal out of habit.

The size of the mercenary group was already a few hundred times larger than before they returned to Planet Aquamarine. After this operation period, there were over a hundred thousand players whom he had hired, and this number was increasing by the day. They were undeniably a super large mercenary group!

While the players were not sufficiently powerful at the moment, the speed at which the players could grow meant that they were all full of potential.

"After entering the universe, I will be able to give them an endless number of missions and resources. At the same time, they will also give me an endless amount of wealth. The sheer number of players will allow my Black Star Mercenary Group to take another step forward, and the name of Floating Dragon's Field Team will be truly respected!"

Thinking about the strength of a few hundred thousand mercenaries, Han Xiao could not help but look forward toward it.

Because of the Mutation Disaster, his mercenary group needed to remain in Planet Aquamarine temporarily. They were currently accumulating their strength, and their true might would show when they re-entered the universe once the Mutation Disaster was taken care of.

Han Xiao had always paid attention to the actions of DarkStar. He was waiting for DarkStar to carry out the next stage of their plans as that would be the best time for him to hand over the mutation source in his hands.

After leaving the military factory, Han Xiao walked toward the conference room. According to the schedule, today was the day for Godora to have a conference with all the upper echelons of the Sanctuary to discuss their disaster relief efforts. Such a meeting would be held once every few days, and he was already used to it.

Coming to the conference room, Bennett, Nagakin, and the others had already arrived long ago. After Han Xiao sat down, a couple of leaders then began the discussion of their disaster relief efforts. Since Han Xiao was not concerned about the topic, he did not interrupt their conversation.

After half an hour, they finally changed the topic, and Nagakin said, "Godora is in a stalemate with DarkStar. The enemy has continued to ambush the calamity planets, and the War Bureau has been sending out reinforcements endlessly. Both the forces are closely matched."

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao said, "It doesn't sound good."

"We do not know how many fleets are under DarkStar's command, but we have to spread our forces to protect the calamity planets," Nagakin replied helplessly. "Our forces are truly lacking. This is DarkStar's scheme to force us to split our forces. While the battle is currently a stalemate, as long as DarkStar is willing to send out the majority of their forces to attack a calamity planet, it will be impossible for us to block them. Thus, the situation isn't good."

"Do you guys have a way to deal with that?"

"We do." Nagakin nodded. "With regards to our forces being spread thinly and the distance being far, the War Bureau decided to set up a Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station. It will be set up in a few days' time."

"What is that?" Bennett asked with doubt.

Han Xiao thought for a moment before saying, "You can treat it like a transportation portal for military use."

The Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station was a strategic weapon during intergalactic battles. Within a certain range, it was able to lock onto the coordinates of two different regions and create a transportation channel between the two locations. It would allow fleets that were far away from each other to quickly reinforce their allies.

This station was like a large space fortress, and the technical requirements of constructing it were extremely high. Only advanced civilizations that knew how to construct a stable stargate would be able to construct it. The Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station of Godora had been purchased from an advanced civilization within the Shattered Star Ring and was extremely precious.

In order to construct a Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station, the transportation coordinates of the various locations had to be anchored down properly, and the Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station needed to be situated in the middle of these coordinates. It was like the middle of a spider web with the web spreading far and wide.

With this facility, Godora would be able to cover up its weakness of having its fleet being scattered across the various calamity planets. These fleets would be able to aid each other, and if any of the planets were attacked, reinforcements would be able to arrive within two to three minutes. As such, the ambushes of DarkStar would no longer be a threat to them.

Since the War Bureau was willing to make use of this strategic weapon, it meant that they did not wish to be on the passive side.

Han Xiao frowned and said, "This is an expensive strategic weapon, and DarkStar will definitely attack the station."

"The enemy will definitely do so." Nagakin was not worried.

Since the War Bureau dared use the station, it naturally meant that they would arrange sufficient protection for the station. It could be said that they had even grasped the initiative. Even if the whereabouts of DarkStar could not be traced, they would definitely attack the station. As such, they would be able to grasp the enemy's actions and make preparations.

A flash could be seen in Han Xiao's eyes, and he shook his head.

In truth, Godora was not truly anxious yet. While the DarkStar ambushes had resulted in some loss for Godora, the ones who had suffered the most were the calamity planets. Godora's foundations were not shaken, and the Godorans thought that they were still able to control the situation.

However, he knew that DarkStar would not be so easily dealt with.

With the appearance of the station, DarkStar should be moving on to the next step of their plan.

Just when Nagakin wanted to say something else, a commotion sounded from the outside from afar.

The next moment, the commotion grew larger and larger as it approached them. Like a tsunami, the commotion covered the entire Sanctuary!

Boom!

The ground began to shake, and the windows could be seen trembling slightly from the commotion. Bennett stood up with a face full of doubt.

"What's happening‽"

Bennett hurriedly turned on the screen in the conference room, and the images of the various locations in the Sanctuary were shown. The Sanctuary that had been in an orderly state was in complete chaos, and the Mutation Disaster had exploded once again. Even those refugees who had been injected with the suppressants began to act up.

The situation on the outside of the Sanctuary was even worse, and even the guards of the Sanctuary began to fall ill.

Without anyone to maintain security, the calm that had been formed through great difficulty collapsed.

Millions of people turned violent, and their voices flooded the Sanctuary like a tsunami!

Squeezing, roaring, fighting...

Apart from a messy battle, the majority of them were running around crazily, and they tried to escape from the Sanctuary. It was as though the Sanctuary was a frightening location, and they wanted to escape to the outside. Those escaping formed a long trail, and they charged out of the Sanctuary in all directions. There were some who tumbled onto the ground and were instantly swallowed by the endless crowd.

The players were completely dumbfounded. Very quickly, some of them realized that the mission progress of their [Mutation Disaster] mission had fallen rapidly!

"Th—This..."

This sudden chaos stunned even Bennett and Nagakin.

Han Xiao's gaze turned cold, and he stood up with a solemn expression.

"This is... the second phase!"

Chapter 545: Sensory Organs

The first phase of the Mutation Disaster was an irregular outburst across the entire planet. It signified the first time the Mutation Source controlled its strength. The first symptom of the second phase was all the infected individuals acting up together. Compared to the first phase, the Mutation Source would not be limited by controlling ordinary individuals. Certain elite soldiers and weaker Supers could also become targets of its control. The most obvious change would be the fact that the infected individuals no longer acted randomly but acted as though they had a goal.

The objective behavior of the infected individuals was the first sign of the Mutation Source gaining intelligence. Compared to the chaos in the first phase, the escape of all the refugees was due to the control of the Mutation Source.

"For the Mutation Source to command all of these refugees to escape, it probably doesn't want these infected individuals to gather together. Furthermore, it may have detected that someone has been trying to help these infected individuals escape from its grasp. Thus, it wants to get the infected individuals far away from this place. To the Mutation Source, every single one of these infected individuals are a 'sensory organ'," Han Xiao said with a frown. In his previous life, something similar had also happened. While there was no official explanation given, the various players had come up with their deductions and conclusions. Thus, he was able to guess the thoughts of the Mutation Source.

The only problem was, the second phase had broken out much earlier than in his previous life.

It may be due to a random chance, or it may also be because of the butterfly effect, Han Xiao thought to himself. Because of his actions, there were plenty of events that had developed extremely differently from his previous life. This was not the first time that he had met such a situation, and Han Xiao quickly regained his cool after a short moment of shock.

While it was outside his expectations, he did not become completely flustered.

Walking out of the conference room, the commotion on the outside became larger and larger. Han Xiao immediately sent out all of the mercenaries and the players under him. The first thing that he had to do now was control all of the infected individuals. With the Mutation Disaster in the second phase, the strength of the Mutation Source would be stronger, and the original suppressant that they gave to these infected individuals now required three times the dosage. They naturally did not have enough medicine on hand, and the only thing they could do was forcefully subdue the infected refugees.

The Sanctuary and Godora became busy, and the players all received a new mission. Seeing the mission progress of the Main Storyline falling, none of them dared delay and hurriedly got to work.

In comparison to the tens of millions of refugees in the Sanctuary, the number of available manpower was not high. Together with the players, there were only a million or so. However, since all the players were Supers, it was not too difficult for them to subdue ten ordinary individuals at once.

The refugees nearest the outside began escaping in all directions like an expanding circle. The spaceships on standby all took off immediately and flew toward the outermost rim of the circle while firing white colored doughnut-shaped vibration waves.

Ohm!

The white colored rings swept past the crowd, and the refugees all collapsed onto the ground, jolted unconscious.

Since he had known that there would be this explosive phase during the Mutation Disaster, Han Xiao had already arranged the corresponding measures to deal with it. He had equipped all the spaceships with large-scale Vibration Cannons. While the effect of these Vibration Cannons was extremely weak and could not daze a rank C Super for even half a second, it was just right for dealing with ordinary individuals. It would shock them unconscious and not harm their lives.

Because he had these measures up his sleeves, Han Xiao was not concerned about the number of refugees that he kept in the Sanctuary. Even if they all broke out in illness at the same time, he was confident that he would be able to reduce the losses to the bare minimum. Rather, it might be more convenient for him to gather them all together.

A couple of spaceships jolted the refugees unconscious from the inner circle to the outside and worked together with the players to clear up the refugees nearest the center before clearing up those refugees on the outside. The refugees on the outermost rim of the circle escaped the furthest, but Han Xiao could not start by knocking them unconscious as they would end up being trampled by those behind them.

Ka ka.

A mechanical arm suddenly stretched out, and Han Xiao sped across the city walls. Looking at the commotion on the outside, the running refugees were like a black wave rising and falling as they dashed outside, kicking up a large dust cloud.

Taking out a communicator to contact the other spaceships of the Six Nations, the scene being shown on the communicator was similar. Not only in the Sanctuary, the entire Six Nations was also a similar scenario.

With the Mutation Disaster spreading rapidly, it means that the pressure of their disaster relief efforts will also be greater. Oh, even if DarkStar doesn't come to ambush us, the situation on Planet Aquamarine isn't too optimistic. Planet Aquamarine is probably the first planet that has reached the second phase of the Mutation Disaster among all the calamity planets. But with my help, the different Sanctuaries on Planet Aquamarine and the Six Nations should have the appropriate measures to deal with this chaos. It is must better than the storyline in my previous life at the very least.

Han Xiao calculated the losses in his heart. If the Mutation Source did not have a consciousness before this and was only acting on instinct, from the second phase onward, it would be an opponent with a target and much more difficult to deal with. Furthermore, the Mutation Source would grow even more rapidly after the second phase.

"Thankfully, it is about time for me to hand the original mutation source in my hands to Godora. As long as Godora is able to formulate the appropriate antidote and weapon to deal with the Mutation Source, the Mutation Disaster will be solved." Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

...

The sun set in the distance, and the evening sky was dyed orange.

The chaos in the Sanctuary began to die down, and after spending a few hours, the majority of the refugees were finally subdued. Those that had escaped the furthest had managed to run a few dozen miles, but thankfully, the Sanctuary was located in the wilderness without any vegetation in the surroundings. Thus, it was impossible for the refugees to escape the detection of the spaceships.

In the surrounding ten miles, the refugees were scattered all over the ground. Some players were moving around according to the missions issued by the Sanctuary to inject the guards of the Sanctuary with three times the usual dosage so that they would be able to increase their manpower. All others were taking care of this huge mess but carrying all the scattered refugees back into the Sanctuary.

On the city wall, Bennett had a solemn expression as he asked his assistant, "How are our losses?"

His assistant shook his head in response, indicating that they had not been calculated.

"'The losses of the Sanctuary are the lowest," Han Xiao interrupted. "The Six Nations are still trying to quell the chaos, and they are almost done."

"At least it isn't the worst-case scenario." Bennett heaved a sigh of relief.

Han Xiao shook his head. "The Mutation Disaster has already grown, and we will be facing an even more perilous situation after this. Not to mention whether or not the suppressant will still be effective after this, just the ability of the Mutation Source to control the infected individuals will be the greatest danger. We have captured so many of its 'sensory organs', and it is very likely for it to control a bunch of animals to attack the Sanctuary or Six Nations. It may also choose to control the infected individuals to create destruction and attack our facilities from within."

Hearing that, Bennett's face turned dark, and he felt a lingering fear in his heart. He was not an unduly humble person, but he was clear that without Han Xiao being around, it would be impossible for the natives of Planet Aquamarine to cope with the disaster on their own.

"What are you getting ready to do?"

"Nothing." Han Xiao raised his bows. "The mercenaries under my charge are extremely bored, and a beast tide won't be a big issue. We shall observe the situation first for the other problems. You must try to adapt to the new situation quickly."

"I understand." Bennett nodded.

It was possible for the Mutation Source to be hiding underground or in the ocean. The radar database also did not have any records of the Mutation Source's fluctuations, and it was difficult to locate it. Trying to search for it was no different from searching for a needle in a haystack. Because of the uniqueness of the Mutation Source, before having a cure for it, it would be extremely difficult to deal with it. The Mutation Source was capable of absorbing energy and was able to absorb most attacks as fertilizer for its growth, rendering ordinary attacks completely useless against it. Furthermore, it was able to split apart rapidly and was extremely difficult to catch.

Currently, Han Xiao did not wish to deal with the Mutation Source personally as it was far too disgusting and was not in his interest. Apart from giving Godora a headache so he could reap some benefits, there was another reason. The Mutation Disaster was a temporary protective charm. If the Mutation Disaster was quelled on Planet Aquamarine, he would not be able to predict what DarkStar's next move was. The enemy might choose to destroy Planet Aquamarine directly.

While there was nothing for him to be afraid of since he could easily leave, it would be impossible for him to fit Planet Aquamarine into his pocket and take it along with him to escape. The only ones with such an ability were probably the three great Universal Civilizations or beyond Grade A Supers that had special abilities.

After putting aside his thoughts, Han Xiao gathered his subordinates, and his gaze swept over all of them. With a heavy voice, he said, "According to my estimations, there may be a large beast tide in the next few days. Take some men to patrol the area. The moment there are signs of beasts gathering together, destroy them early and don't allow the beasts to approach the Sanctuary."

Everyone's face lit up. After being idle for so many days, they finally had something to do.

The happiest person was definitely Harmon. Carrying his large axe, he said in a gruff voice, "I like hunting."

After thinking for a moment, Han Xiao added, "Right, take the Inhumans who have just joined for some training. Do not let them be too bored in the Sanctuary."

The majority of the players were currently staying in the Sanctuary. While it was not because they were forced, the daily repetitive disaster relief missions would bore them as well. Apart from the daily selection trials, there was not much of an opportunity for them to fight. Those who were already in the Black Star Mercenary Group naturally were not able to join the selection trial and did not have a chance to do battle at all. Thus, it was likely that they were extremely bored as well.

During the second phase of the Mutation Disaster, the attacks of the beast waves would definitely be more frequent, and it was the best chance for the players to go out and hunt some beasts. They would be able to let off some steam while allowing the mercenary group, which was a few hundred times larger, to build some bonds.

Furthermore, if they did not fight monsters, the players would not be in urgent need of equipment.

...

In some location on Planet Aquamarine, a black figure was seated cross legged in a cave like a statue. After a long while, its pure white eyes spun around.

"Trapping... my... sensory organs... irritating..."

The simulated body began talking to itself. It had only gained this body a few days prior, and it still could not speak fluently.

After obtaining a body that belonged solely to itself, the Mutation Source felt a sense of freedom. While it could share the senses of the infected individuals and even control them to a certain extent, it was only able to have absolute control of the simulated body.

Just a while ago, the Mutation Source had evolved successfully, although it did not even know about its own evolution and only felt its senses toward the 'sensory organs' becoming much clearer.

Every infected individual was a 'sensory organ' in the eyes of the Mutation Source. The infected individuals were like the different body parts of a human, and the Mutation Source treated them like part of its body. When it could not move around in its infant stages, it could only understand the world through these 'sensory organs'.

Right now, it could clearly feel many of its 'sensory organs' being trapped in a few different locations. Just when it wanted to order its 'sensory organs' to spread out and not gather together, it saw the refugees being suppressed by Han Xiao and the others. As such, it immediately understood the situation.

They are my enemies! They are harming my sensory organs!

In the original thoughts of the Mutation Source, there was no righteous or evil nor any sense of moral standards. It did not have much common sense either and only had the basic instinct of a living being. It could even be considered to be extremely pure.

To the Mutation Source, the act of suppressing the refugees was akin to controlling his 'sensory organs'. It felt as though its limbs were being restricted without being able to move one bit. With these 'sensory organs' being gathered together, it was not able to understand the world around it.

Furthermore, some of the 'sensory organs' had been injected with some kind of substance, severing its connection with the 'sensory organs'. It was akin to blinding it or making it deaf.

Thus, it was extremely displeased.

Its instincts told it that if it was attacked, it had to retaliate.

Chapter 546: DarkStar's Next Move

The Colton Star Cluster consisted of many different Star Systems, and Godora's territory was in the Gavin Star System. From the star map, Godora was located in the south-west of the Colton Star Cluster and shared borders with three other Star Systems. The Fawn Star System, which was controlled by Holy Stone and Black Raven; Hutt Civilization controlled by the Skywalker Star System; and the Hyde Star System, which did not have a dominant ruling party.

The Hyde Star System was in a state of conflict, and a local high-grade civilization had not appeared. Its development could not be compared to a Star System that was ruled over by a civilization, but the entire Star System had abundant resources. Be it mining planets or energy planets, there was sufficient resources to last them for thousands of years.

The geographical location of Hyde was pretty special as it was connected to the territories of six different high grade civilizations. In the eyes of those high-grade civilizations, Hyde was undeniably a fat piece of meat. Regardless of whether if it was because of their resources or strategic location, this was a region that they had to fight for. The six high-grade civilizations expanded their territories, and each occupied a part of Hyde.

Hyde was not under the control of any civilization, and the six high-grade civilizations treated Hyde as new land for them to conquer. They divided Hyde up, but because they could not come to an agreement on the borders of the division, conflicts were extremely common between those six civilizations. Hyde was an important point among the foreign affairs department of the six civilizations, and none of them were willing to take a step back.

Of the six civilizations trying to slice up the Hyde Star System, Godora and the Hutt Civilization were included. Because these two civilizations shared a border, the conflict between the two civilizations was extremely intense.

Just when news of the Mutation Disaster in the Garton Star System was spreading rapidly, the Hutt Civilization welcomed a special visitor.

On an isolated planet without any inhabitants, a small spaceship landed in a black field. The hatch to the spaceship opened, and the leader of DarkStar drew a pattern on the ground with his finger casually while waiting for the individual whom he had contacted.

Xiu!

Not too long later, a loud shrill could be heard, and a spaceship landed from the sky. A man dressed elegantly walked down from the spaceship with dozens of guards following behind him.

The leader of DarkStar looked up, and dozens of lights were floating in the sky. Those lights were the protective fleet of the person whom he was about to meet. The person before him was an envoy who had been sent to communicate with him. The leader of DarkStar had contacted the Hutt Civilization and arranged this meeting.

The Hutt envoy waved his hands for his guards to retreat and walked forward alone. After sizing up the DarkStar leader, he said, "You truly are bold. You actually dare enter the Skywalker Star System without any men. Aren't you afraid that I might catch you and hand you over to Godora?"

"I came alone to show my sincerity, and you definitely won't deal with me," the DarkStar leader replied without a trace of fear. "The presence of DarkStar is able to keep Godora busy, and the enemy of my enemy is my friend. Alright, I also know that DarkStar's reputation is poor, and Hutt definitely won't be willing to have any relationship with us. However, no one will say no to benefits for sure."

"A confident person usually dies because of his confidence," the Hutt envoy said expressionlessly.

"Since you were willing to meet me, it means that you are interested in what I said. I shall just get straight to the point. The chaos that DarkStar has created will attract the main elites of Godora, and this is the best chance to seize territory in Hyde. As long as the two civilizations don't break out in an all-out war, the peace treaty can go to hell..."

"You want to borrow our strength to give Godora pressure from the outside and in turn help you guys?" the Hutt envoy said coldly. "Humph, you are thinking too highly of the conditions that you raised. Face Godora in battle just for that little bit of territory? The risks are too large. The Star Cluster grade civilizations in the Shattered Star Ring will not allow us to break the rules as such. If we draw the attention of the three great civilizations, things will be even worse. The warring era is already over, and things aren't as easy as you said."

"A civilization without ambition does not have a future," the DarkStar leader said calmly. "The situation in the galaxy is already fixed. If you do not think of a way to climb up, you will forever be a plaything for those above you in the food chain. Even if everyone hides their fangs, there isn't a civilization that will truly accept their fate as such. The road ahead will get more and more narrow, and it is impossible to avoid competition. It is just that the lawful civilization will ensure that the loser won't lose everything.

"Every minute, hundreds or thousands of battles are happening all over the universe, and you are clearer about this than me. To a certain extent, there is a silent consent toward war up to a certain level. Only an idiot would believe that a single piece of paper is able to wipe out all forms of conflict. Apart from submitting to the strength of the three great civilizations, the reason everyone chooses to follow this rule is because the rule ensures the safety of the loser. As long as the strength of a civilization reaches a certain level, the civilization will be able to avoid the fate of being wiped out, and this is beneficial to everyone."

The Hutt envoy did not say a word. This was indeed something that was tacitly agreed upon. As long as creatures of intelligence were not wiped out, battles would never disappear. The only thing that would change was the way they chose to compete. The imagination of a living being brought with it endless possibilities, and since it was endless, it meant that it was impossible for all the different species to understand each other fully and coexist in peace.

While it was written on the peace treaty that the peace treaty protected all civilizations, when it was truly carried out, there would be an implicit understanding of the rules that only a civilization at the Star System grade would be qualified to receive this privilege. The universe was vast, and plenty of species disappeared every minute. Only civilizations that had a certain degree of strength and status had the right to be treated with importance. Being of the Star System grade was the minimum requirement.

Hutt and Godora were both at that level. Despite there being numerous conflicts between the two civilizations, their conflict would be controlled within a certain scale as they were clear that they could not do much to the other party. Thus, their focus was largely on the battle of benefits. Since they had a competitor whom they are unable to slaughter, they could only choose to scrap over benefits. In truth, the Hutt envoy had been extremely interested in the suggestion of the DarkStar leader from the start.

After a moment of silence, the Hutt envoy asked a question that caused the DarkStar leader to have a slight change in expression.

"DarkStar's objective is to overturn the pureblood tradition of Godora and create a new Godora. However, the destruction that you've caused Godora has exceeded the bottom line, and you are recognized as a terrorist organization. Do you still think that you will have any chance of becoming a ruler?

"Your only chance will be a change in the regime, but not to mention the little possibility of that, the moment DarkStar comes into power, the punishment from the Star Cluster grade civilization will immediately come. Do you guys really think that you will be free of all sin after ruling over Godora? Unless you are able to stand shoulder to shoulder with a Star Cluster grade civilization, there will come a time when you will have to pay the price for your actions!

"I am truly curious what your DarkStar is thinking about."

"This is none of your business," the DarkStar leader said in a strange tone.

...

According to the degree of prosperity of the planet, Godora would allocate a different rank to the planet. The mother planet and a few other planets were Grade S. Below that was Grade A; Juberly Hub and Planet Golden Gate were examples. Another grade down was Grade B, and below that would be Grade C.

In the Garton Star System, an old looking spaceship descended onto a Grade B colony planet, and it seemed extremely insignificant in the busy space port.

Ember, who was in disguise, stepped out of the spaceship and looked around at the bustling crowd and troops not too far away.

The corner of his mouth then curled up coldly, and he raised his arms up to eye level.

"Reduce to dust."

His voice was transmitted through a miniature communicator to a fleet not too far away from the colony planet awaiting their orders. There were three DarkStar motherships lying in wait.

The scale of this fleet was on a completely different level from the ambush that they had carried out on the calamity planets!

Chapter 547: The Time Has Arrived

In the few days after the second outbreak of the Mutation Disaster, there was an obvious increase in the number of beasts lurking around the Sanctuary. In order to prevent a beast tide from being formed, Herlous and the other officers finally had something to do. They led the players who had just joined the mercenary group to wipe out the beast nests and set up different defense strongholds in various locations around the wilderness.

The players were the main force in wiping out the beasts, and the strongholds quickly became locations for the players to form parties and sell items.

The majority of the beasts were much more easily controlled than humans. According to Han Xiao's understanding of the Mutation Source, after entering into the second phase, the Mutation Source would consciously control the beast tide to attack the various Sanctuaries, resulting in the attack of the beasts becoming more organized.

This was a form of retaliation from the Mutation Source, but Han Xiao was not too bothered by it.

The Mutation Disaster was only a huge threat to Planet Aquamarine, but his own level had already exceeded the upper limit of Version 2.0, so the Mutation Disaster could only pose a limited threat to Han Xiao.

Han Xiao did not treat the Mutation Source as an important opponent. After all, he had the trump card to deal with the Mutation Source. His aim was to make use of this opportunity to complete his recruitment plan; any other matters such as dealing a blow to DarkStar and resolving the Mutation Disaster were not as important.

But from the players' perspective, the Mutation Disaster was the first Main Storyline Mission after the launch of Version 2.0, and it was extremely challenging.

For the progress of the Main Storyline Mission, the players took on plenty of missions every day. The Sanctuary, Black Star Mercenary Group, and Godora did not lack missions and opportunities.

During Version 1.0, players developed a basic understanding toward Planet Aquamarine, and during the Mutation Disaster, they all worked together for the [Mutation Disaster] mission. For once, there was this strange feeling of a collective community. The players were usually in a competitive relationship with one another, but this time, they were required to work together as one. It was a strange feeling.

Han Xiao did not need to personally take part in the disaster relief operation. On the contrary, the players stood on the frontlines for the operation. They met many different events and characters every day, and their lives were extremely plentiful.

The various actions of Black Star and Godora were no more than a part of the storyline in the players' eyes.

At this moment, the players of Planet Aquamarine still could not participate in the events at Han Xiao's level.

Apart from recruiting players, Han Xiao would not pay too much attention to the overall situation of the players. He understood the players. Regardless of how things were, the players would always be able to find the space to display their strengths and create enjoyment for themselves. They were the most proactive bunch, and there was no need for Han Xiao to worry at all.

...

A few days later, just as Nagakin had told him, Godora set up the Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station and connected all the calamity planets. As long as DarkStar dared show themselves, they would be faced with a thunder like strike.

However, DarkStar suddenly retreated and no longer launched any ambushes. The storm in the Garton Star System seemed to have calmed down... but this was only a misperception.

Not too long later, a piece of news shocked the entire Star System!

"Godora's colony planet, Long Arc, suffered from a large-scale assault by DarkStar. The enemy sent out three DarkStar motherships and over four thousand battleships. The local Godora forces fought an intense battle with the enemy and suffered heavy losses. Long Arc was bombarded with cannon fire, and over forty cities were flattened with the other cities being severely damaged. The estimated death toll may exceed three hundred million.

"According to the report, the assault began when a DarkStar member unleashed his destructive Esper abilities. This person has the ability to reduce a human's body to dust, and thousands of individuals perished under his abilities. The Godoran Civilization responded to this assault immediately and sent three waves of reinforcements. They finally managed to destroy more than a thousand enemy battleships and one DarkStar mothership.

"Godora's colony planets have suffered from many probing assaults historically, but this is the only time when a colony planet has almost been wiped out. DarkStar's actions have been seen as an extremely sinister terrorist attack, and this is the most frightening event over the past ten years in the Garton Star System. We have reason to believe that this is the signal for DarkStar to start a war again. Tracing this incident to its root, it is likely that the cause of this incident is the dozens of civilizations that suffered from a calamity at the same time. Godora's reaction to the matter still isn't clear at the moment..."

After watching the news broadcast, Han Xiao let out a long breath.

"Things have finally developed to such a state..."

The damage that DarkStar had caused by targeting a colony planet was far greater than them targeting all of the calamity planets. Furthermore, DarkStar went all out this time and sent out three DarkStar motherships. According to the information revealed in his previous life, even at their peak, DarkStar had no more than fifteen motherships.

Furthermore, there was the little b*stard Ember who aided them from within.

Ember's Esper ability was truly perverse when dealing with ordinary individuals. With a single thought, he was able to reduce his surroundings to ash. He was the sharpest 'massacre tool' in DarkStar's eyes, and this was the first time that Ember had displayed his abilities to the entire Star System.

DarkStar did not have thousands of military factories like Godora. Every mothership that they lost was definitely a large blow, and they could only fill the gap by spending an enormous amount of money. Attacking Long Arc had cost them a mothership, definitely a huge loss.

However, Han Xiao knew that DarkStar had achieved their goal.

The terrifying Long Arc incident shook the entire Godoran Civilization. After the incident, a theory was quickly formulated. There were those who believed that DarkStar was only attacking the calamity planets to draw Godora's attention. Their true motive was to attack the various colony planets.

As such, the Godoran citizens from the other colony planets began to feel threatened. The support for disaster relief operations on the calamity planets fell to rock bottom in a single night. Many of the citizens even strongly requested for Godora to pull out the troops sent to protect the calamity planets to protect them instead.

Because this matter was related to their own safety, almost all of the Godoran citizens could accept such an explanation, and their sympathy toward the calamity planets was thrown out of the window.

In truth, the Long Arc incident was not related to the disaster relief squads. The reason for Godora's defeat was because DarkStar displayed superior military strength. They brought out three motherships, and such a force was not something that a Grade B colony planet could resist. The Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station was not connected to the colony planets, and it would take a large amount of time for them to set it up again.

While Godora was a powerful civilization, their troops were scattered among more than a hundred colony planets. It was impossible for every single planet to have a powerful defense. If DarkStar really went all out, they would definitely be able to destroy a few colonies. If not, Godora would not view them as such a huge threat.

This time, DarkStar also suffered the loss of one mothership. However, the majority would not focus on the loss of a terrorist organization. Instead, their focus would be drawn to the destruction that DarkStar caused and the Godora's losses.

The Godoran citizens were not able to maintain their rationality, and many of them were consumed by their fear. Furthermore, DarkStar was still fanning the flames in the shadows.

Not only was chaos being created, conflict between the pureblood and mixed blood was incited again. Many Godorans had their friends or relatives living in Long Arc, and since their deaths had been caused by DarkStar, this hatred was directed to the mixed bloods living among them.

DarkStar had always fought under the banner of the mixed bloods. Under such circumstances, the mixed blood Godorans who were living in Godora became substitutes for the purebloods to vent their anger. The conflict among the citizens was a result of their deeply entrenched discrimination toward the mixed bloods, and this was almost a part of their tradition. As such, even the government was helpless against it.

The Hutt Civilization always paid attention to Godora. Upon realizing that Godora was having a huge headache because of their internal affairs, Hutt willingly played the role of an 'external threat'.

The Hutt fleet that was stationed in the Hyde Star System began to take action. They began sending out probing attacks on the Godoran borders and continued to apply pressure on them.

The blows that came one after another made it difficult for Godora to catch their breath.

DarkStar's shadow could be seen behind all of these incidents, but this was only the start. The Long Arc incident was only the spark to a full series of schemes.

However, Han Xiao did not intend to let DarkStar continue with their plan.

Godora is probably feeling the disgust of eating sh*t.

Han Xiao shook his head. While he did not like Godora, he would not gloat over their misfortune. After all, DarkStar was their common enemy.

The Mutation Disaster is key to this incident. It is taking up far too much of Godora's energy, and Godora will quickly realize that time is running out. The best way to solve this problem is to deal with the Mutation Disaster at its roots. This way, they will be able to pull their disaster relief squads back, and the internal conflict will slowly be resolved...

I have a copy of the Mutation Source in my hands, and as long as I provide it to Godora, they will be able to come up with the antidote quickly, and the Mutation Disaster will be solved.

As long as he solved the most pressing matter at hand, Godora would be able to catch their breath and focus on dealing with DarkStar.

The more urgent their needs, the more benefits the Mutation Source in his hands could be exchanged for.

It is almost time. While Godora will be willing to offer a much higher price if I drag this matter on, there isn't a need for me to wait until DarkStar reaps a huge harvest before taking action. As long as Godora understands how important time is to them, they will understand the consequences of not stopping DarkStar.

Han Xiao then sent a communication request to Nagakin. After waiting for half a day, the other party still did not pick up his call.

Han Xiao was puzzled and decided to personally visit the Godora camp to find Nagakin. However, he was stopped by Nagakin's assistant.

"Black Star, Officer Nagakin instructed me not to let anyone disturb him if there isn't anything important. Please return."

"What happened?"

"He is in a meeting with the upper echelons and does not have the time to meet you," the assistant said with a stern tone.

Nagakin would not have rejected him outside of the door in the past. After thinking for a moment, Han Xiao immediately understood what was going on. With Godora facing both internal and external troubles, a high-grade officer like Nagakin naturally had many things to do. In Nagakin's eyes, Han Xiao was not that important anymore.

Han Xiao stroked his chin and suddenly thought about something. He did not insist on seeing Nagakin but left the Godoran camp instead.

He realized that even if he wanted to hand over the Mutation Source, his timing could not be too right. If not, he would be suspected of having the Mutation Source beforehand but not taking it out earlier.

Thus, it was best that he put on a show.

Since my excuse will be that this Mutation Source came from Floating Dragon, why don't I take a trip back to put on a show?

Han Xiao then mentioned the matter to his Officers and left Planet Aquamarine on the BlackLight Stealth.

After two hours, Nagakin ended the meeting and heard that Han Xiao was looking for him.

"Black Star didn't manage to find me and left on a spaceship?"

Nagakin frowned for a moment before shaking his head. Since Black Star did not insist on seeing him, it should not have been anything important. He did not wish to waste his time on such a small matter.

The various departments were in a complete mess because of the Long Arc incident, and the higher ups wanted to pull him out from Planet Aquamarine. Nagakin was also extremely busy, and he did not have the time to bother about Han Xiao.

...

"The plan is being implemented, and we will definitely be able to greatly exhaust Godora's strength this time."

In the DarkStar's headquarters, the vice head was giving his speech in a conference, and his tone was filled with delight.

"We created quite a huge trouble for Godora, and it will naturally be impossible for them to pull out their disaster relief squads. Since they have already begun their disaster relief operations, giving up halfway will only shake their reputation in the galaxy. However, if they insist on carrying on with the disaster relief operation, the conflict within their nation will only become more intense.

"If they choose to give up, we can go all out and easily wipe out these few calamity planets. Not only will we be able to get rid of the civilizations that submitted to Godora, we will be able to create the misunderstanding that their destruction was a result of Godora giving up on them..."

"This is only a simple example," the person in charge of intelligence said. "In other words, regardless of what Godora chooses, we will still be the winner and hold the initiative."

"The Mutation Disaster, Hutt Civilization, and internal conflict will occupy Godora's strength," Degulish sneered, "and we have sufficient opportunity to prepare our next plan. The Mutation Disaster has stalled a large portion of Godora's troops, and the longer this matter drags, the more serious the matter will become. If this matter can persist for one to two years..."

"The exact time is difficult to estimate, but with Godora's research abilities, they won't be able to solve the Mutation Disaster anytime soon." The person in charge of intelligence also laughed. "My men have already confirmed that Godora haven't obtained the Mutation Source that we lost previously. They only managed to get an empty Secret Message Bead. The Holy Stone Civilization should have snatched it in secret, and Godora is still in the dark about what was hiding in the bead."

Chapter 548: Greed

After leaving Planet Aquamarine, Han Xiao asked Wilsander about the current location of Floating Dragon Island. During that period of time, Floating Dragon had drifted to the Rain Star System.

Han Xiao left on the BlackLight Stealth alone, and he just wanted to put on an act of making a trip back to Floating Dragon Island. He had originally intended to tell Nagakin before his departure but did not manage to see the other party. Since Nagakin did not take the initiative to ask him about the matter, Han Xiao decided not to reveal it first. As such, he did not contact Nagakin on his journey. Instead, he spent his time thinking about the conditions that he should raise to Godora.

Furthermore, he also wanted to personally witness what sort of effect DarkStar had on the Garton Star System. In his previous life, he had been a player who could only remain on Planet Aquamarine and only found out about the storyline after everything was over. He had not been able to personally experience the changes in the Garton Star System. Now that he had the chance to personally witness the turmoil, he widened his eyes to have a good look. After all, the Great Mechanic Han was extremely curious about the unknown storyline.

The Black Star Mercenary Group had received a few missions in the Rain Star System, so Han Xiao was familiar with the route. It was simple; he had to first make a resupply stop at Juberly Hub before going through the stargate to the Rain Star System. Following which, he would make his way directly to Floating Dragon Island. With the speed of the BlackLight Stealth, his return trip would take less than half a month.

He did not need to remain on Planet Aquamarine. After all, Godora's Military Orbit Quantum Leap Station was not just there for show. Even if DarkStar wanted to launch an assault, they would only attack the other colony planets.

He threw the affairs of the mercenary group over to Herlous. Herlous was the first officer to join the mercenary group and also the captain of the Sunil Division. When Han Xiao was in seclusion to construct his machines or skiving off, Herlous had always been the one in charge of managing the mercenary group. He was a professional assistant, and Han Xiao had always believed in making his secretary do the work.

The BlackLight Stealth went into hyperdrive and through the stargate of Star Zone 9. He then flew out from one of the many stargates of Juberly Hub. Without any troublesome passengers, Han Xiao had a good time piloting the spaceship.

In the control room, Han Xiao was looking at a 3D star map.

"That's right. Planet Golden Gate is nearby, so I can take a trip there to get a look at the base since it won't take up too much time."

The spaceship changed direction, and not too long later, Han Xiao arrived at Planet Golden Gate. Looking through the windows, the situation on Planet Golden Gate was extremely different compared to before. A large number of Godoran battleships were hovering around the planet, and all the battleships were prepared for war.

Han Xiao frowned and thought to himself, That's right, DarkStar's attack on Long Arc made Godora feel threatened. All the colony planets of Godora will have battleships patrolling outside the planet, and it can be said that they are in a state of high tension.

The free port of Planet Golden Gate was also locked down, and spaceships could only land after a strict identity check. This was due to Ember's threat. The strength that he had displayed had put Godora on high alert, and they did not dare let anyone from DarkStar sneak in.

The entrance and exit of the planet had a long queue, and Han Xiao smoothly passed through the check. However, he did not have any special privileges this time, so he had to queue up for a long time before being allowed to land at the port.

Walking on the streets, Han Xiao realized that the atmosphere was extremely different. In the past, the streets would be filled with commotion, and prosperity could be seen all around. But now, almost nobody could be seen on the streets, and a nervous atmosphere permeated the air. Even if there were a few occasional passersby on the street, they would be silent with looks of worry.

The most commonly seen individuals on the street were the Godoran patrol squads. Their faces were solemn without any banter or laughter. Their footsteps were in sync, and Han Xiao could not help but feel the urge to trip them up whenever he saw them.

The changes on Planet Golden Gate were a result of DarkStar's terrorist attack. While the attack was aimed at another planet, no one could be certain that they would not be the next target. There were even some who felt that it was too dangerous to remain on a colony planet and decided to drift in the universe to avoid the danger.

However, because of the conflict between Godora and DarkStar, the security in the Garton Star System was not like before, and it was even riskier to travel out.

Many Wanderers and space pirates felt that this was a good opportunity. They felt that Godora did not have the strength to deal with them, so they all arrived in the Garton Star System. With a large number of pirates roaming around in the Garton Star System, many Godorans who attempted to escape ended up being kidnapped. This gave the Godoran Public Security Team an even greater headache.

In the past few days, Han Xiao had received thousands of new hire missions from the Mercenary Alliance, and all of those missions were related to various kidnapping cases. It could be seen just how terrible the situation was. It was almost like a pirate's paradise.

It can be said that DarkStar had set off a large chain reaction with their attack. DarkStar did not collude with those space pirates, but the space pirates were vile scum who took advantage of such opportunities. With Godora revealing their weakness because of DarkStar, there would naturally be others who wanted to take advantage of the situation as well. After all, openings could be seen all around Godora, and it was almost akin to them taking off their pants. The space pirates would naturally find it a waste if they did not show up.

"The situation is truly terrible." Han Xiao shook his head.

When he returned to the base, everything had been functioning as it should have been, and he had not found any problems. Despite Han Xiao being on Planet Aquamarine, the assembly line had not stopped its work. The program was controlled by Phillip, and Han Xiao could control it remotely from Planet Aquamarine.

The large quantities of equipment being constructed by the assembly line piled up into a small mountain in the warehouse. Han Xiao did a brief calculation, and the amount of equipment in the warehouse was sufficient to supply 230,000 players. This was all of his stock, and when the players entered the galaxy, the only problem would be that he might run out of stock.

After supplying the assembly line with a fresh batch of materials, Han Xiao left Planet Golden Gate and headed to Juberly Hub.

The BlackLight Stealth entered the port and slowly parked. He only needed to replenish his BlackLight Stealth and stock up on additional fuel for the other spaceships on Planet Aquamarine.

After refueling, he would continue his journey.

Juberly Hub was still bustling with activity and did not seem to have been affected by DarkStar. Han Xiao made his way to the Hub Center before taking an exit that led to the merchant district.

At the same time, a few others recognized him. They were all dressed in simple battle outfits that were a common sight in Juberly Hub.

The few of them were together in a group. Looking at Han Xiao departing, they exchanged gazes and discussed softly.

"Was that Black Star?"

"That's right, it's him!"

"Hehe, who would have thought we would find a large fish while replenishing our supplies?"

"Hurry up and inform the boss."

Located near the periphery was a certain, not at all high-end, bar.

The few fellows who had spotted Han Xiao rushed over, and after scanning the place, they walked up to a seat in the corner of the bar. A burly human was seated there, wearing thick, heavy combat attire. He was drinking a bottle of strong liquor, which dripped down from the corner of his lips, wetting his messy beard.

"Boss Befuli, we found an enemy!"

The person who was called Boss Befuli slammed his bottle of wine down, and his body leaned forward. Under the dim lights of the bar, his malevolent face was revealed. If one were to judge his appearance by the standards of a normal space humans, his appearance would be a perfect fit for the description 'wanton and unrestrained'.

His eyes did not have any whites and were dark red in color like burning flames, and his pupils were completely white in color.

'Fiery Eyes' Befuli.

He was a ferocious space pirate who operated in the Fawn Star System and was a Grade B Super. He belonged to an infamous space pirate group that belonged to the Fawn Star System called the Purple Snake Space Pirates.

The Purple Snake Space Pirates had more than a dozen spaceships, and their captain was a Calamity Grade Super who had a bounty of 2,800,000 Enas issued by the Black Raven Civilization. When Han Xiao received the mission to kill a Grade A Super, the captain of the Purple Snake Space Pirates was a targeted whom he had considered. But since he had managed to get a Mission Completion Card, he did not take the risk.

More than two years ago when Han Xiao was completing missions with Frenzied Sword and the other players, they had once killed an officer of the Purple Snake Space Pirates, and the grudge had formed then. As a mercenary, having enemies was unavoidable, and Han Xiao was already used to it.

Befuli was an officer in the Purple Snake Space Pirates, and he had led a team to the Garton Star System so that they could make use of the chaos in Godora to rob others. At that moment, the team that he was leading were concealing their identity in Juberly Hub to rest and resupply. In the past, they had mainly operated in the Fawn Star System, so it was extremely easy for them to disguise themselves in the Garton Star System.

"Enemy? Who‽"

"Black Star!"

"I see." Befuli began chuckling sinisterly. "A few years ago, he got rid of Maddow's team. Even though I did not like that fellow, our captain has not forgotten about this debt."

"Boss, Black Star is alone. Shall we make a move?" a space pirate asked softly with his eyes glowing fiercely.

As Befuli heard that, he burst into laughter. "Hahaha, do you think that it is so easy to get rid of Black Star? Are you looking for death‽"

As he said that, Befuli's expression suddenly changed, and he choked the space pirate in front of him. "Brat, you do not have the right to set your sights on such a character. You'd better learn some respect for the strong!"

This space pirate gulped in horror and hurriedly agreed with what Befuli had said. Befuli's temper was unpredictable, and he did not dare provoke Befuli.

Befuli released his grip and held up a wine glass. After finishing the wine in the glass, he stood up and walked toward the door.

"Little ones, follow me."

The few space pirates hurriedly followed behind him and asked carefully, "Boss, what are we going to do now?"

Befuli licked his lips, and a look of greed could be seen in his eyes. "I hear that Black Star's spaceship is a high quality one. While he is still in the Hub Center, let's snatch his spaceship. Heh, I am sure that it will fetch us a tidy sum."

Chapter 549: Seeking Death

As an officer of Floating Dragon and the only armed division of Floating Dragon operating on the outside, Han Xiao was no longer the nameless individual from many years back. News about him was all around, and the model of his spaceship was naturally no secret.

All the spaceships being parked in Juberly Hub were placed in a warehouse region. The warehouse was connected to the port, and looking in from the outside of Juberly Hub, the port was like a gigantic window.

The BlackLight Stealth was akin to the Ferrari of spaceships, boasting a huge head turning effect. After some asking around, Befuli easily found out where it was parked.

"Warehouse AD-0074sd. Juberly Hub indeed gave him a high-class warehouse."

Befuli grew excited. The serial number of this warehouse was located in the high-class region, and it was like the best spot in the car park. The security was much tighter, and the facilities present were better. For example, Befuli's own spaceship could only be parked in an ordinary slot that started with 'E'. His treatment was completely different.

After all, Han Xiao was a famous mercenary in the Garton Star System and had been stationed in Juberly Hub for a few years. Furthermore, his spaceship was also a high grade one, so Juberly Hub naturally gave him the best treatment. This made it even more difficult for Befuli to snatch the spaceship.

Befuli understood very clearly that he would not be able to deal with Han Xiao. Black Star had already proven his strength over the past few years in the universe. A year prior, he had even worked together with Godora to get rid of a Calamity Grade Super. His fame was towering, and Befuli did not dare underestimate him. Being a space pirate, his judgement was extremely important.

However, Befuli did not plan to give up. The BlackLight Stealth was far too tempting, and since Black Star was not near his spaceship, they would not have to face him in a battle. The entry record only had Han Xiao's name, which meant that there was no one else on the ship. Thus, this was the best opportunity.

While he did not dare fight Black Star, he still had the guts to steal something.

Befuli brought his space pirates subordinates to weave through the complicated passages of the warehouse. Arriving at the warehouse where the BlackLight Stealth was parked, they were greeted by a thick alloy gate and could only enter after having their identities verified. However, that was the ordinary method, and the space pirates obviously chose the violent method.

Befuli's eyes widened, and his reddish eyes began to burn with a red flame.

Whoosh!

The next moment, a pillar of fire was shot out from his eyes at a frightening temperature. The part of the door in contact with the pillar of flame quickly turned red, and the alloy softened.

Using his eyes to shoot out flames was Befuli's Esper ability and also the source of his nickname. The heat of the flames increased as his ability developed. At the start, the temperature of his flames had only been a few hundred degrees. Now that his was a Grade B Super, the temperature of his flames was a few thousand degrees, akin to the surface temperature of a star. Thus, it was not difficult to burn a hole in a door.

Ka ka ka!

The sirens sounded, and the walls in the surroundings suddenly opened up. Defensive turrets popped up from the walls and opened fire on Befuli.

In the face of the intense firepower, the space pirates took out their shields. A yellow glowing light could be seen on their shields; it was a layer of energy shield, blocking the attacks from the turrets.

The Befuli's armor changed its form rapidly and transformed into heavy armor that covered his entire body with defense as the priority. The turret fire could not penetrate his armor, and the only opening was located at his eyes. Furthermore, the armor even had the ability to strengthen his Esper ability.

Hu!

The fire pillar expanded and gradually became dark blue in color with the temperature rising rapidly.

Befuli's gaze swept past the turrets, and the fire pillars swept through the turrets as well. In less than two seconds, all the defensive turrets were destroyed.

The alarm continued to ring, and the guards were rushing over. However, Befuli had already created a hole large enough for them to fit through.

Walking into the warehouse, the BlackLight Stealth stood silently in front of the space pirates. All of their faces were full of excitement at the moment.

"Hahaha... this ship is ours now!" Befuli halted his Esper ability, and a look of greed could be seen on his face. Taking out his communicator, he shouted, "Is the fastener ready?"

The projection of his subordinate appeared on the communicator. "No problem, boss! Our spaceship has left the port, so as long as you pilot the BlackLight Stealth out of the port, we will be able to drag it away!"

There were two main steps to robbing a spaceship. The first step was entering the warehouse and fixing on a propulsion equipment and electromagnetic device. After leaving the port, the second step was to make use of their own spaceship to drag the robbed spaceship away through the electromagnetic device.

The space pirates would not be able to disable the AI system of the spaceship in a short period of time, and they could only make use of a disrupter to prevent any transmissions from being sent or received by the spaceship. This was to prevent the owner of the spaceship from controlling the spaceship remotely. As such, the spaceship would then become a metal block that was under the mercy of the space pirates. As long as they could capture the spaceship, they would have more than enough time to work on remodeling ship.

Even if they were not able to disable the AI system, they would still be able to sell the spaceship on the black market for a high price. The merchants of the black market would then hire Mechanics to install a new AI system. Almost every black-market merchant would have a Virtual Mechanic under them.

The space pirates were extremely familiar with this procedure, and almost all of them robbed spaceships in this manner. Befuli's subordinates did not delay and rapidly installed all the relevant tools on the body of the spaceship.

On the other side, Befuli had thrown out the signal disrupter to temporarily disable all forms of communication. Even if Black Star knew that his spaceship was being robbed, he would not be able to do anything about it.

"By the time he rushes back, we will have left with the spaceship already."

Befuli then walked toward the hatch with his eyes glowing, prepared to breach the spaceship.

He was confident that, with the temperature of his flames, he would be able to burn a hole in almost all spaceships. It was definitely difficult for the defenses of a spaceship to defend against a Grade B Super like him.

Thus, this spaceship was as good as his!

Boom!

Right when Befuli was about to unleash his abilities, the BlackLight Stealth suddenly moved. Its engine was suddenly activated, and it suddenly hovered in midair.

Bang!

The BlackLight Stealth cut off all the equipment that was connected to the belly of the ship. Spinning three hundred and sixty degrees in midair, it sent everyone in the surroundings flying.

Befuli's body slammed into the wall of the warehouse, and upon looking up at the floating BlackLight Stealth, he saw a laser beam expanding rapidly.

"What‽"

The blinding laser beam swallowed the stunned Befuli.

Boom!

Chapter 550: It's Time to Take out the Dusty Juicer

In the Hub Center, Han Xiao was busy purchasing materials through the store. In addition to fuel for the spaceship and replacement parts, the Logistics Department of Floating Dragon also got him to purchase some items when they received word that he was returning.

While he was engrossed in shopping, his communicator suddenly beeped. Glancing at it, Han Xiao's lips involuntarily curled up in response before he nonchalantly threw his communicator back into his pocket and continued his shopping.

He slowly picked out his items and paid for his goods leisurely. Han Xiao casually stood at the side whilst the staff loaded his items onto a suspension aircraft. At this time, an aircraft from the hub stopped at the door of the store.

A member of staff hurriedly ran out from the aircraft, rushing up to Han Xiao.

"Your... Your Excellency Black Star! Your spaceship...."

Han Xiao waved his hand dismissively, cutting off the other's speech as he smiled. "No problem, isn't it just a group of petty thieves trying to steal my spaceship? How many of them are still alive?"

The staff from the hub was startled and hurriedly nodded in response. "When we arrived, only one of them was still alive. He's severely injured, and we've already captured him. Your spaceship is also undamaged..."

"Let's go and take a look." Han Xiao nodded, and sitting in the hovercraft loaded full of his goods, he proceeded with the staff close behind. After a short while, they arrived at the crime scene.

The first thing he saw was that the hangar door had been blown to pieces. The outside passage was full of black scorched marks, with many guards surrounding the area.

Next to the hangar, a burly man was tied up tightly by electromagnetic bindings. The battle suit on his body was riddled with holes, with his whole body full of scars. He looked like he was on his last breath.

Han Xiao leaned forward to get a look. The interior of the hangar was a mess, with the wall having been shattered in places, exposing electrical wires that sizzled and sparkled like fireworks.

The lights flickered on and off intermittently, and the ground was covered with bloodstains. Lying around were over ten corpses covered with white cloth. The BlackLight Stealth remained motionless on the ground like an obedient child, sleek and smooth like a mirror with no blemishes.

"This is the guy who wanted to steal my spaceship?"

Han Xiao walked up to the severely injured Befuli, his eyes full of sympathy.

His BlackLight Stealth was the current host for Risda. Having long received the news from Risda, he was not worried at all.

This bunch of petty thieves had actually dared covet Risda, so they had definitely been asking for death. They were facing a spaceship with consciousness, one such as the BlackLight Stealth with high end specs and superior weaponry at that.

Even for Han Xiao himself, it would be easier to face off against a group of Grade B Supers than to face off against the BlackLight Stealth. Its fighting strength was off the charts, and one was unlikely to succeed unless they were a Calamity Grade Super with too much time on their hands. Besides, even if there was a Calamity Grade Super, the BlackLight Stealth could still escape from them even if it could not beat them.

Thus, Han Xiao was assured about the safety of his spaceship. Unless pigs could fly, the ship would remain safe and sound.

"Your Excellency Black Star, we've checked the database. This person is a galactic pirate from the Fawn Galaxy..."

One of the staff carried a transparent handheld screen with him as he explained. Before he could finish, however, Han Xiao directly took the screen.

Glancing through it, Han Xiao was startled.

"Befuli, with an Esper ability of shooting flames from his eyes... eh, isn't that Laser Eyes? To think that it's someone from the Purple Snake Space Pirates... I seem to have dealt with them in the past..."

Han Xiao began to recall that the leader of this band of pirates should be a Calamity Grade Super but on the weaker side.

His eyeballs moved while deep in thought. Han Xiao finally hefted Befuli up, saying, "Since this guy wanted to steal my spaceship, leave him for me to handle."

"That goes without saying. To have you face such inconvenience, it's our mistake. We have failed in our roles." The staff nodded in response.

After allowing the staff and guards in the hub to disperse, Han Xiao stepped into his spaceship, and found a room before unceremoniously throwing Befuli onto the ground.

"You didn't do your intelligence research properly, and you still dared make a move. If it was a normal spaceship, you might have succeeded, but you're really unlucky. Do you have any thoughts about this?" Han Xiao poked fun at the other party.

Befuli's wounds were still fresh, causing him to grit his teeth in pain. He was in too much pain to even open his mouth.

They had clearly blocked the signal of the spaceship, but the whole ship had powered up as though it had a life of its own, firing a whole bunch of lasers and cannons. His battlesuit had quickly shattered.

Befuli expertise lay in offense, but his laser eyes could not negate the laser cannons that were similarly comprised of energy. Because his physical defense was not up to par, he could hardly withstand the damage dealt by the cannon. If not for the fact that the guards had reached the area on time, he would also have lost his life to the spaceship.

Having fallen into the hands of Black Star, Befuli felt so much regret that his intestines were twisted up. He did not know what Black Star was going to do to him.

Since Black Star has not killed me, he probably thinks that I am of some value to him. This is a good idea. He probably wants to use me to obtain intelligence. I need to cooperate and cement my value so that he won't think of killing me! The killing power of my ability is extremely strong, so long as he is negligent, I can escape!

Befuli's palms were sweating as all kinds of thoughts flashed through his head. While he was a famed ruthless galactic pirate, when faced with life-threatening danger, his thoughts spun rapidly.

As long as he did not die, he would have another chance!

Han Xiao patted the shoulder of Befuli. "You should be an officer of the Purple Snake Space Pirates. I presume to put this debt on the head of Purple Snake then. Right now, I have no time to deal with them, but it's fine. Currently, my Mercenary Group requires sparring partners, and Purple Snake seems to be a good choice. When the time comes, I'll personally visit your head.

"As for you..."

Han Xiao looked straight into Befuli's eyes before letting out a playful smile. "Since you came straight to my door, don't blame me for what I'm about to do."

Befuli felt a chill run down his body, but before he could process the meaning behind Han Xiao's words, he suddenly felt a sharp pain in his arm. He only saw Black Star holding onto a round shaped machine, pressing it into the blood vessel of his arm. There seemed to be a needle that had pierced into him.

"This is..."

Before Befuli could express his surprise, he suddenly felt his strength rapidly diminish. He only saw the round machine being filled up with his blood. He could not help but widen his eyes as a sense of weakness rose up within him.

An Esper's ability was part of their body, just like the arms or legs. To have this ability forcibly stripped away, it was as though stripping him of his abilities. At this point, even his last assurance was gone.

"What's this‽" Befuli's facial expression greatly changed, showing distress. His current condition had fallen drastically short of his expectations.

Super-Gene Extractor!

In the past year, Han Xiao had rarely had a chance to use his juicer. The main purpose was because he did not manage to capture any evildoers. The former captive Rezar had long been sucked dry. Since there was no way for him to continue, Han Xiao could only set him free.

Currently, other than juicing himself once in a while to form the Ability Potions, he did not perform it on anyone else.

Since Befuli had wrapped himself up and gone over, Han Xiao would definitely not feel guilty. They were enemies, and thus, he had to fully utilize his worth. The ability to shoot lasers from one's eyes was handsome yet strong—how could he resist?

Very quickly, three tubes of crimson Ability Potion were produced. Han Xiao took one of them, drinking it all in one go. The moment he swallowed it, a heat was produced almost instantly.

You have obtained [Character Summon Card - Befuli (Temporary)].

[Character Summon Card—Befuli (Temporary): [Incandescent Eyes], sprays a column of heat from the eyes causing burning damage.

Aim with Sight, Maximum Range of 400 m

Attack Range: 510 – 1360

Duration: 5 seconds, a total of three attacks will be inflicted per second.

Usage: 0/1 (This Character Summon Card will exist for: 15 days)

Yo, this damage is sick. Definitely a pure offense Esper ability!

Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

If one could burn a target for the full five seconds, they would inflict at least 7,600 damage. The highest would be... painful, so painful. Furthermore, the skill was an AOE[1] attack!

Even when faced against a Grade B Super, after deducting the damage resistance, one could inflict at least 3,000 to 4,000 damage. Furthermore, the ability was shot from one's eyes, which meant a free gift of damage since it did not hinder one's actions.

Han Xiao lowered his head, looking at Befuli with a smile.

"Let's get on well."

Befuli lay weakly on the ground, muttering disconsolately to himself. Looking at Han Xiao's eyes that had the intention of raising a lamb for the slaughter, in Befuli's eyes, Black Star was worse than himself by more than a hundred times!

He suddenly had a sort of premonition, that his future life... would be spent wishing he was dead!

...

Han Xiao had knocked out the information of Befuli's accomplices from him; however, the moment Befuli had failed, the rest of the galactic pirates had long taken their ship and escaped. Han Xiao did not wish to delay his trip, so he did not bother to pursue the pirates.

He was already treating the Purple Snake Space Pirates group as nourishment for the players, so he was in no hurry to deal with his problem.

The BlackLight Stealth set off again. After this little episode, they did not stop at all along the way, and naturally, there were no other problems.

A few days later, Floating Dragon Island appeared on his radar.

Han Xiao navigated his spaceship to descend. Floating Dragon had long been informed of his return, with Wilsander waiting at the dock to welcome him. The logistics manager, Haier, was also present. What gave Han Xiao a surprise was that Jenny was standing by the side, albeit with a black face, obviously also there to welcome him.

"Hahaha, Black Star, you're finally back." Wilsander laughed, his tail swishing as he came up to give him a hug.

Han Xiao turned his head slightly and was almost blinded due to Wilsander's devil horns.

"Ji ji ji ji..." Haier let out words of a weird language before realizing that he did not turn on his translator. After activating it, he said, "Black Star, did you bring the materials I requested?"

"They're all onboard." Han Xiao nodded in return. After pondering a bit, he added, "Please remember to compensate me. They were pretty expensive."

Following which, Han Xiao turned to look at Jenny, putting on a weird expression as he said, "How come you also came over to welcome me?"

"Do you think I want to?" Jenny was expressionless, reluctantly replying. "Ames wishes to see you."

"Oh, how rare." Han Xiao was a little surprised. After helping Ames with the problem of searching for Aesop the previous time, they had not had any contact since. He did not know why she was looking for him."

Just as the few of them were chatting, the various people present at the dock turned over to look, their gazes filled with curiosity and surprise.

"It's the four officers of Floating Dragon! To think that they are all gathered together!"

"That guy in the black suit should be the Head of the Field Team for Floating Dragon, Black Star. I heard that the Dragon Emperor wishes to expand her influence, and Black Star is currently expanding her armed forces. His authority is huge."

"I heard Black Star has set foot in the Garton Star System. Is that the intention of the Dragon Emperor? Does she want in as well?"

The expansion of Han Xiao's mercenary group had raised some suspicions in the galaxy. Many people felt that Ames was supporting him from behind, sending a signal to everyone. The Dragon Emperor, who had never contested for anything, was finally wanting to obtain the influence deserving of her status as a Beyond Grade A Super.

Black Star was the General leading the vanguard to express the Dragon Emperor's intentions!

[1] AOE: Area of Effect. Think a grenade or maybe a fart in the middle of a crowd. Back

Chapter 551: Ames' Curiosity

After handing the goods over to Haier, Han Xiao said goodbye to the three of them. Leaving the dock, he entered the city district and went straight to the Dragon Emperor's palace.

For Ames to request a meeting, there are two possible reasons. First would be Aesop and second the expansion of my mercenary group. Er, perhaps it may be because she hasn't seen me for so long and misses me greatly. Maybe she just wants to take a look at this handsome face of mine.

Along the way, Han Xiao pondered. Ames had never been bothered about any responsibilities and rarely summoned her subordinates. Thus, the chances of it being a serious conversation was slim.

Han Xiao's eyes suddenly lit up. Right, it's difficult for me to meet her, so it would be great if I could get another Dragon Emperor Character Summon Card.

The mission of digging out Planet Aquamarine's history had given him another Random Reward chance. He was not that confident in his luck and had been prepared to save it up to roll several in a single go. However, his plan could not keep up with the changes, and it would be best if he could draw an empty Character Summon Card now.

The previous summoning of the Dragon Emperor had helped him get rid of a Calamity Grade Super, and he would never complain about having too many such trump cards.

Opening the interface, Han Xiao immediately started to roll the random reward.

Randomizing... draw complete.

You received the Random Reward Type: [Talent].

Eh, my luck is pretty good. Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

While it was not a Character Summon Card or tool reward, gaining a talent could only be something good for him. Regardless of how trashy a talent was, it would definitely have some use.

Randomizing.... Randomization completed.

Please choose one option from the following:

Tough Spirit Barrier: +20% Willpower Resistance

Flexible Weapon Usage: When using any type of weapon (including but not limited to cold weapons, firearms, mechanical weapons, magical weapons, rare treasures, etc.), +12% base weapon damage.

Haste: Movement Speed and Dodge Rate increase. Effect dependent on DEX attribute and increase no more than 30%.

After looking through the options, he quickly made his choice. He already had [Advanced Mental Toughness], and the effect of it was +35% Psychological Resistance and 30% reduction in negative status from psychological attacks. Furthermore, it was able to lower the Psychological Resistance needed to be immune from negative status. [Tough Spirit Barrier] had an overlapping effect, so its value was less.

[Haste] was not a bad talent. However, only an agility type Super would be able to fully maximize the talent. His own battle style did not rely too much on speed. With [Void Travel], he did not need to worry about dodging, and his mechanical suit was able to give him greater mobility. The majority of the time, he relied on positioning and use cannon towers or protectors.

As a Mechanic, he needed to use his machinery to fully display his strength. Thus, [Flexible Weapon Usage] was the most suitable for him. While a twelve percent bonus was not high, it was not useless either. Damage was just like a man's height. A single point of it was welcomed, and even a centimeter more was something great.

Most importantly, this talent was different from Machinery Affinity. Only weapons that used Mechanical Force were able to enjoy the buff of Machinery Affinity, and it consumed energy. While the energy consumed was very little, when using the Army Tactic, it was difficult for him to use his own Mechanical Force to sustain all the machines. On the other hand, this talent was able to boost all different weapons.

Han Xiao immediately chose [Flexible Weapon Usage] with a face full of satisfaction.

After all, the talents in Random Reward were more common; it was rare for an uncommon talent to appear and impossible for a Molding Ability to appear. Such an effect was already pretty good.

Talking about Molding Abilities, both of his Molding Abilities, [Intermediate Strengthened Life] and [Steel Body], had been obtained completely by luck. Players were not able to obtain Molding Abilities, and there had been no information on them in his previous life either. However, with regards to Molding Abilities, Han Xiao had some vague ideas.

The easiest way to level up would naturally be [Intermediate Strengthened Life]; that could be achieved by injecting himself with powerful genes. However, there would be risks of his genes mutating, so he did not take such a risk.

Currently, [Intermediate Strengthened Life] gave him additional HP from his Endurance stat at a ratio of 1:30. This was also the reason for his tankiness. If he could upgrade this talent again, his HP would probably be even higher than the bosses at his level. He would probably be able to kill his enemy by drowning them in his blood.

...

Ames' Palace was truly majestic. When the guards saw Han Xiao, respect could be seen on their faces, and they all gave way to allow Han Xiao into the hall.

In the large hall, a black throne was floating in midair. Looking around, Han Xiao could not see Ames' figure at all.

Hu!

All of a sudden, a light green Force Field gushed forth. It was like a large cluster of transparent green crystals, with the width of the force field being ten meters wide.

Boom!

The atmosphere in the surroundings was compressed, and explosions could be heard.

Han Xiao's eyes narrowed. Placing his palms together, six large mechanical hands stretched out and formed a mini protective shield around him. The thrusters on the wrists of these mechanical hands spewed out blue flames, and he blocked the might of the force field!

Boom!

Both forces collided, and a muffled sound could be heard.

The force field and mechanical hands were equally matched. The mechanical hands then slowly gained the advantage, pressuring the force field to the point it changed shape. The energy of the force field began leaking out and created green waves on the surface of the ground.

Boom!

The next moment, the force field exploded, and a larger wave shot out in all directions. Like a stone being thrown into a lake, the dust on the ground rippled outward and formed a dust cloud that could reach one's thighs.

Han Xiao's hair was blown into a mess, and with a gust of wind blowing in his face, he could not help but squint.

Ames then appeared from a small door by the side of the throne and sat on the throne. She was once again dressed in a long, purple dress with her hair cascading down like a waterfall. Her delicate beauty was like a face that was frozen in time, and not the slightest wrinkles could be seen. Holding her chin with her hand, her sleeves slid down her forearm and revealed her snow-white wrist as she looked at Han Xiao with a smile that did not seem like a smile.

"The first time I saw you, you were almost crushed by my force field. I used the exact same strength previously, and you are now able to block it easily. It has only been two years; the speed of your growth has truly shocked me."

Ames laughed, and her lazy voice sounded with the unique hoarseness of a lady.

The moment the force field appeared, Han Xiao knew that this was Ames testing him. If it was before he entered the universe, it would have been extremely difficult for him to block such an attack. However, he was able to do so now without any pressure.

Ames' charisma was too stunning, and Han Xiao could not help but be astounded by her beauty every time he saw her. However, he was extremely experienced and quickly took a look at Ames' washboard figure. His heart immediately calmed down, and he nodded.

"Lord Dragon Emperor, what did you wish to see me for?"

"Didn't I say before? You can call me Ames." Ames' lips twitched. "Actually, it isn't much. Recently, Jenny has been protesting against you expanding the Field Team. Let me ask you, what are your thoughts?"

Of the four beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring, Floating Dragon Island was the weakest. With Han Xiao expanding his forces, there were many organizations in Shattered Star Ring that misunderstood his intentions. They felt that the Dragon Emperor wanted to mimic the other three beyond Grade A Supers and expand her own forces to make them an untouchable existence. Ames was not too bothered by their thoughts, and she was not interested in the other organizations.

Originally, she did not care about Han Xiao expanding his mercenary group and silently consented to Han Xiao using her name. Furthermore, she had always given him a great deal of trust.

However, Jenny always complained about this matter, and the reason for her rejection made Ames dumbfounded. Jenny said that Han Xiao's expansion had resulted in a chain effect, and all the other organizations are trying to show their goodwill and work out their intentions. As a result, her workload was many times greater than before. With the pressure of work being unbearable, she was losing hair every day and felt as though she was aging rapidly. Thus, she strongly opposed Han Xiao's actions. She even added that if Ames did not want to hire another manager, Ames should not allow Black Star to expand his forces any further.

Thus, Ames wanted to know Han Xiao's thoughts. She personally did not care about the outcome. If Han Xiao had a reasonable plan, Ames would not mind supporting him. In any case, Aesop, who had been caught by Han Xiao, was currently spending his retirement on Floating Dragon Island, and he would be the best choice to share the workload with Jenny.

Hearing that, Han Xiao was moved.

"Do you remember Aroshia?"

Ames thought for a while. "She is an undying Space Wonder. I saw her on the island before, and even I couldn't kill her. You were the one who took her away, right?"

"I found millions of Space Wonders with the same special physique as her. Furthermore, they are all full of potential, and it is possible to communicate with them like normal beings."

"Millions‽" Ames was stunned, and a curious gaze could be seen in her eyes.

"They are from my hometown and appeared a couple of years ago. I have a feeling that they will become a force in the universe that cannot be underestimated. Thus, I want to recruit them early." Han Xiao did not lie. He understood the players' potential, and his tone was filled with confidence.

"There is actually something so fun!" Ames said joyfully. "I have to take a look personally."

Han Xiao's mouth cramped up, and he immediately felt a headache coming on.

He had dug a hole for himself this time. While bringing Ames with him would be a form of insurance, his return this time was to find an excuse to bring out the mutation source. If Nagakin ended up asking Ames about this, would he not be exposed?

Coughing, Han Xiao tried to persuade her otherwise. "Ames, DarkStar and Godora are fighting again, and the situation in the Garton Star System is pretty complicated. My hometown is part of this mess as well. Why don't you come after this mess is over?"

"DarkStar again? What's there to be afraid of?" Ames said with dissatisfaction. "I hate waiting. I will return with your spaceship. If DarkStar dares appear, I will smash them to bits."

Han Xiao slapped his forehead and did not know whether to laugh or cry.

It seems like DarkStar is in for a ride again.

He truly did not intend to call Ames over this time!

...

Jenny returned to her office. Taking off her spectacles, she rubbed the bridge of her nose and let out a sigh.

"Dragon Emperor requested a meeting with Black Star, and she is definitely talking to him about the problem of the Field Team. Black Star has her trust, and Ames probably won't stop his actions. Jeez..."

Thinking about Han Xiao, Jenny could not help but be filled with pent up rage. After her dissatisfaction over the loan the last time, she was filled with enmity toward Han Xiao. After that, despite trying many different methods, she had not been able to reduce Ames' trust in him.

Now, regardless of how dissatisfied Jenny was, she could only accept the presence of this colleague.

Putting on her spectacles again, Jenny browsed through the many documents before her. Suddenly thinking of something, Jenny took out a document with regards to the Garton Star System.

The Garton Star System hasn't been calm in recent times, and there are many organizations paying attention to this. According to news on the black market, even organizations more infamous than DarkStar are placing their attention on this matter. This is the hottest topic in recent times.

Black Star is also operating in that region and has been dragged into this incident. As of now, he is standing on Godora's side. Humph, at least he knows not to enter the fray in the name of Floating Dragon. If not, I wouldn't let him off!

Jenny snorted coldly.

Since Floating Dragon wanted to maintain neutrality, it would be best for them to stay far away from such a sensitive affair. While she did not like Han Xiao, she did not have the ability to order him around. On the surface, both of them were at the same level and were managing different departments.

Godora and DarkStar are in a chaotic war, and who knows when it will end? In any case, this mess has nothing to do with Floating Dragon and won't give me any trouble, Jenny thought to herself.

Chapter 552: Hang in There, We Will Win!

On the dock, many Floating Dragon wanderers were hanging around with the galactic pirates, eyeing the BlackLight Stealth with envy and greed in their eyes.

A high-class spaceship from the Federation of Light!

A pity, this valuable spaceship was Black Star's personal ship. On Floating Dragon Island, there were not many who dared create trouble, and they could only look at it with envy.

"Move aside."

Han Xiao's voice reverberated from outside the crowd, and the hundreds surrounding the spaceship turned around to take a look. Their faces immediately turned pale, and they all backed off as though they had seen a ghost. All of their eyes were fixed on the lady beside Han Xiao. She was the owner of Floating Dragon Island.

"It's the Dragon Emperor!"

Cold sweat drenched the onlookers. It was rare for outsiders to be able to see Ames personally. Upon thinking about her strength and status, those pirates felt their legs turn to jelly and an immense amount of pressure.

The two of them ignored the crowd surrounding them and boarded the spaceship.

Hu!

BlackLight Stealth took off and disappeared into the universe like a ray of light.

Everyone had watched as Ames followed Han Xiao onto the spaceship dumbly, and they only reacted after the spaceship took off.

"Dragon Emperor is has left again!"

"She is actually going out with Black Star this time! He is the leader of Floating Dragon's Field Team. Could it be that Ames is going to take action personally?"

"Not too long after his arrival, Ames followed him away. I have a premonition that something big is about to happen!"

Ames' status was elevated, and all of her actions and words would cause speculation. All of those pirates who were stopping at Floating Dragon had their own network of information, and this news would rapidly spread.

Very quickly, this piece of news spread all across Floating Dragon Island and made its way into Jenny's ears very quickly.

Jenny was dumbfounded.

When she found out about this piece of news, her mood crumbled.

It was extremely common for Ames to go out and play, but she usually left alone. Yet, this time, she had actually run away with Black Star!

Just what did Black Star say to Ames‽

Jenny was angered to the point her lips began to tremble. She could predict that in the upcoming days, various problems would come her way, and her workload would increase many times over!

However... Ames was her boss. In the past, she could still complain about Black Star, but if her boss was the one creating trouble, who could she complain to‽

Jenny's face cramped up, and she almost felt like fainting.

This was what despair felt like!

After entering space, Han Xiao activated the autopilot function and stood up from the pilot seat.

"It will take about ten days for us to return to Planet Aquamarine. There are only the two of us on the ship. If you don't want to sleep, I am willing to accompany you to kill time."

"This spaceship isn't too bad." Ames then looked around the ship before looking at Han Xiao with a smile. "Is there anything to drink?"

The two of them then went into the resting hall, and Ames sat down lazily. Her legs were placed on the sofa as she lay sideways on the sofa with her left hand supporting her head. She did not mind displaying her sexy side before others at all. She enjoyed this comfortable position the most.

Han Xiao opened up his storage shelf and took out a bottle of good wine that Herlous kept inside. Taking out two glasses, he filled them up before sitting opposite Ames.

Ames lifted her finger, and the wine glass on the table levitated toward her. Taking a sip, she complained with a smile, "Tastes terrible."

"Really? I think that it's fine..." Han Xiao's mouth cramped up. Herlous was not a human after all, so his taste was probably unique.

Ames blinked and said, "Talk about yourself. Ever since you joined Floating Dragon, I have not gotten to know you."

On Noriosse, Han Xiao had helped her to catch Aesop, and Ames was extremely thankful. She was not the kind of person who felt as though it was only right for her subordinates to do everything for her. Compared to the other three beyond Grade A Supers in the Shattered Star Ring, her personality was more easygoing.

A couple of years ago, she did not think highly of Han Xiao and only allowed him to join Floating Dragon because of Aesop. In just a few years' time, not only was Black Star able to firmly secure his place, his strength had increased rapidly as well. While it was still far from her current strength, the speed of his growth had still surprised her.

Ames could not help but be interested in this subordinate of hers. Only then did she realize that she did not understand much about him.

Hearing that, Han Xiao began narrating his past. Naturally, he left out about the news regarding the players. Starting from the Germinal Organization, he then continued to talk about the Inhumans on Planet Aquamarine and his own subordinates.

Han Xiao only stopped after half a day and drank a mouthful of wine to moisten his throat. He was not against the idea of sharing his stories. This was the best time for him to spend some time together with Ames alone, and it was a good opportunity to bring their relationship closer. Furthermore, Ames was a beauty, and while Han Xiao naturally would not be controlled by his desires with his strength, he still enjoyed admiring a beauty.

At the very least, it was better than looking at the hairy and stocky Harmon.

Hearing Han Xiao's narration, Ames tapped her thigh with her finger and said, "A pair of sisters controlling the strength of life and death... I seem to have heard of it before."

She was not interested in politics, nations, or wars. Instead, Aurora and Hila caught her attention.

He did not hide the story of Aurora and Hila. In his previous life, the Hila who descended into darkness had been even more terrifying than Ames. Hila was still extremely weak, but there seemed to be something strange. Ames usually would not be bothered about the happenings on a backward planet. If she had heard about something similar before, it had to have come from an extremely high level.

"You said that Aroshia is an AI lifeform. Are the millions of Space Wonders from your hometown the same?"

Han Xiao shook his head and pretended to ponder. "They should be different."

After finishing his sentence, a change suddenly occurred in the resting hall.

Hum!

A ray of light transformed into a human form, and Risda made his appearance, sitting beside Han Xiao.

"Why are you out here?" Han Xiao asked with doubt.

Ames also looked toward Risda with curiosity.

Risda stood up slowly and bowed deeply toward Ames with sincerity.

"Lord Dragon Emperor, I wish to plead with you about something. Please help my civilization and save my brethren! I am willing to offer myself as the price and listen to your commands forever!"

When Han Xiao mentioned AI civilizations, Risda found out that Ames was a powerful individual on the same level as the Mechanic who occupied his homeland.

This was a chance for him to seek help. Even if the chance of the Dragon Emperor agreeing was only one percent, Risda was not willing to give up. If Ames was willing to give her aid, everything would become simple. What seemed to be previously impossible would now become possible.

"Fighting?" Ames raised her brows. "Who is the opponent?"

"He is a Mechanic who snatched my homeland and enslaved my tribe, turning them all into his weapons. I will never forget his name. He is called Manison. The Ancient One. Papachi!"

"Oh, so he is someone from the [Mechanic Empire] of the Primeval Star River. He is also a member of The Ancient Ones." Ames shook her head. "I reject your request."

The Primeval Star River was another large star field just like the Shattered Star Ring. The status of Manison's [Mechanic Empire] was just like Ames' [Dragon Emperor] in the Shattered Star Ring.

'The Ancient Ones' was a special organization, and Ames' foster father, Aesop, had once belonged to 'The Ancient Ones'. However, he had left afterward.

While Risda had already been prepared for rejection, he was still very disappointed and could not help but ask, "May I know the reason for your rejection?"

"I can't win against him," Ames replied casually.

Risda's light figure became unstable, and he gasped in shock. "Even... even you aren't his match..."

Han Xiao was not too surprised. Beyond Grade A was a general category, and there were naturally those who were stronger and weaker. While Ames was powerful, she was not invincible. Ames had also never thought that she was invincible.

Ten days passed by in a flash. Without much to do on the spaceship, Han Xiao chatted with Ames almost every day, and the relationship between them became much better than before.

Planet Aquamarine appeared outside the window, and a large number of Godoran spaceships could be seen outside the atmosphere of Planet Aquamarine. Upon noticing the BlackLight Stealth approaching, they immediately sent out a warning.

"State your identity!"

"It's me," Han Xiao replied.

"Black Star, you may land." The other party's tone eased up. While danger was all around at the moment and they had to be extremely careful, Han Xiao was someone who had fought with them before, and it was already proven that he was not an enemy.

After gaining clearance, BlackLight Stealth landed in the Sanctuary. Looking down at the Sanctuary, it seemed as though there were even more refugees at the moment with the majority of them being tied up. While Han Xiao had not been around, a couple of incidents had taken place on Planet Aquamarine, but they had all been taken care of. The players had plenty of things to do, and they spent their time extremely well.

DarkStar did not ambush the calamity planets again, but they went to harass the other colonies instead, causing the situation to become even more precarious and the Godorans to become more and more frustrated. However, none of that affected Han Xiao.

Opening up the hatch, Ames drifted out and looked around. "This is your hometown? How nice. It is a pity that my hometown is already an abandoned planet."

"The Inhumans are all gathered in the plaza. I shall not accompany you. I have some things to deal with," Han Xiao said.

Ames nodded and floated to the plaza alone as she looked at the players with curiosity.

A player turned around and was immediately dumbfounded, gawking in shock.

"A,A,A,A... Ames‽"

"You recognize me?" Ames was surprised. She had thought that these Inhumans were a backward bunch and had never expected them to recognize her.

The number of people who noticed Ames increased, and the players were all shocked.

It was as if magic had been cast over the originally noisy plaza. With Ames as the center, the 'magic' spread out in all directions, and the entire plaza became silent. All their emotions were brewing.

Boom!

The next moment, the players erupted into cheers!

On the other side, Han Xiao did not follow Ames and hurried his way over to the Godoran camp, requesting to meet Nagakin.

The Godoran guard shook his head, and his answer was no different from half a month ago. "Black Star, Sir Nagakin is currently in an emergency meeting and does not have time to meet you. Please leave."

Han Xiao's objective was set this time, and he said in a deep voice, "Go and tell him that I have a new mutation source in my hands! I don't care what he is doing. I want him to see me immediately!"

The faces of the guards changed, and they did not dare make the decision. One of them hurriedly informed Nagakin.

After waiting for less than two minutes, a golden light flashed out from the depths of the Godoran camp and stopped in front of him. All the fixtures in the way of the golden light was smashed apart, and a long running trail could be seen behind. The golden light was Nagakin.

Knowing the purpose of Han Xiao's visit, Nagakin had been shocked to the point he had almost fallen off his chair. How could he be bothered about continuing the meeting? He had rushed out without the slightest bit of delay and did not even wish to waste time walking as he hurried to welcome Han Xiao.

"Is what you said true‽" Nagakin asked anxiously.

Han Xiao took out the transparent ball with the mutation source sealed within it, and it attracted Nagakin's gaze like a powerful magnet.

"Let's go in and talk."

Han Xiao waved his sleeves to block Nagakin's vision and chuckled.

It is time to turn the tables around!

Chapter 553: Negotiations

The two of them proceeded into the spare conference room; the original one already had a huge hole smashed within it.

Nagakin ordered his guards not to allow anyone in before closing the door. Staring at the mutation source that Han Xiao had placed on the table with a burning gaze, Nagakin walked over to the table and studied it.

A black liquid substance was sealed in a transparent sphere, and its shape slowly changed.

"Are you sure that this is the source of the Mutation Disaster?" Nagakin paused for a moment before continuing. "It isn't that I don't trust you, but I have to be certain because this matter is extremely important."

Han Xiao could understand Nagakin's careful attitude and slowly said, "Don't worry, this is a Mutation Source that has not been unsealed. Two years ago, when carrying out a mission, I coincidentally met the carrier from DarkStar with this item on him. I somehow managed to snatch it from DarkStar, but since I didn't know what it was, I passed it over to Floating Dragon Island.

"Only when the Mutation Disaster erupted and I searched for some information was I certain that this black gluey substance is the Mutation Source. I came to find you half a month ago because of this matter, but you were busy at that time. Thus, I went back on my own to fetch this item."

Upon hearing that, Nagakin slapped his forehead with regret. "You should have contacted me earlier!"

Han Xiao waved his hands to show that he was also extremely helpless and purposely asked, "With this source, you guys should be able to develop the antidote, right?"

"I am not a researcher, and I will have to wait for the conclusion of the research department..." Nagakin clenched his fists and could not suppress his excitement. "However, it will definitely speed up the research progress!"

Godora's researchers had been researching the Mutation Disaster from the start and were attempting to create an antidote. However, they could only study the infected individuals and did not have any data on the Mutation Source. As such, their research had been delayed.

With the original source of the mutation, they would be able to carry out more experiments and develop an antidote to deal with the illness! The progress of the research would definitely be sped up greatly!

The earlier they resolved the Mutation Disaster, the earlier they could prevent the situation from becoming worse!

This meant that with the item that Han Xiao had handed to them, Godora would be able to break the situation that DarkStar engineered and turn the tables!

At this moment, Han Xiao interrupted Nagakin's dreams and said with a smile, "Don't misunderstand me. I never said that I would give this thing to you guys."

"What‽" Nagakin's gaze shot over immediately with a trace of enmity within it. This was an item that Godora had to obtain at all cost. Even Black Star...

"Don't be so nervous. What I mean is, you can have the item, but I need a reward. I am a mercenary, and I like to solve my problems with transactions. In other words..." Han Xiao stroked his chin as he said, "How much is Godora willing to pay for this Mutation Source?"

"I see." Nagakin's eyes narrowed, and he calmed down. At the same time, a thought flashed through his mind.

In this tense situation, Black Star had suddenly been able to take out an item capable of breaking the stalemate... This is truly fishy!

It was possible that Black Star wanted to gain riches from the chaos, but there was another very small possibility—Black Star had ties with DarkStar.

Black Star had made DarkStar suffer quite a number of losses, and the impression that an ordinary person would get was that both parties were enemies. It would be impossible for the past events to be a set up. However, if DarkStar was willing to endure humiliation and, instead of taking revenge, contact Black Star personally and pay him a high price to work together, this was also a possibility.

Black Star was a mercenary who fought for riches, and Nagakin never had held too much expectations toward mercenaries. It was not him thinking too much; he had no choice but to be extremely careful. The problem with DarkStar was extremely delicate, and he had no choice but to consider all possible sources of risk. After all, Black Star had been able to suddenly take out an item that was the key to resolving their crisis. Even if the other party was able to explain the origins of the item clearly, it was not very convincing to Nagakin.

As these thoughts flashed through his head, Nagakin said in a deep voice, "Is Floating Dragon aware of your actions?"

He decided to contact Floating Dragon personally. It was impossible for Floating Dragon to work together with DarkStar, and he would only be at ease if Floating Dragon acknowledged Han Xiao's words.

"Of course they're aware." Han Xiao had anticipated this question and shrugged his with a smile. "If you are worried, you can go and ask Ames personally. I brought her over."

Plop!

Nagakin slipped off his chair and fell onto the ground.

He then crawled back up pathetically.

"You you you you... you brought Dragon Emperor to this planet‽"

"That's right, she is in the plaza."

Nagakin looked at Han Xiao in disbelief.

Oh my goodness! What kind of a figure is Ames? And she has actually been called over by Black Star? Just how much authority does this fellow have on Floating Dragon Island! Am I playing Wayne Cards‽

"I don't have anything to ask..." Nagakin laughed bitterly. For Black Star to bring such a character over, he was obviously unafraid of Nagakin verifying his words with Floating Dragon. If that was the case, what was the point in him suspecting anything? No matter what, it was impossible for him to doubt the relationship between Ames and Black Star. Black Star did not have those rights yet!

Han Xiao's expression remained calm. On the way back, he had told Ames about the Mutation Source. Since it was not something disgraceful, there was no need for him to hide it from Ames. Han Xiao understood her and knew that she would not bother about these little details. If she was Jenny, Jenny would definitely have slammed the table.

Just as he expected, Ames had been completely uninterested in this matter, and Han Xiao naturally did not have any concerns.

"Black Star, this is an extremely important matter, and I have to inform my superiors. You can raise your conditions to them."

Nagakin did not delay any further and contacted his superiors with his communicator.

A wave of disbelieving gasps could then be heard on the communicator. All the different departments in Godora had been racking their brains over this problem, and the timely news was like the biggest relief that they had over the past few days. Not just the War Bureau, this piece of news had even spread all the way to the desk of the highest leader in Godora!

The upper echelons in Godora were shaken!

Very quickly, Godora sent out a couple of individuals with sufficient authority to handle this matter. A couple of images then appeared, and they all looked at Han Xiao.

"You are Black Star? Be direct. What are your conditions?" Their expressions were grave, and they were fully prepared to pay a huge price.

However, the upper echelons of Godora were not dissatisfied about it at all. Since it was a transaction, it was only right for them to pay a sufficient price. Making Black Star hand over the mutation source without any payments would be the actions of a gangster. Even if Ames was not there, they would not have behaved in such a manner. Being in their position, they would not casually make enemies for themselves.

Could a problem that could be resolved with money be called a problem?

Han Xiao's eyes glowed, and he said with a smile, "Let's talk about it in detail..."

Over the next hour, an intense negotiation took place. The Godoran representatives argued to bring down the price, and they slowly inched toward a price that both parties could accept. In front of those upper echelons, Nagakin did not even have the right to interrupt.

A long while later, their discussion finally ended.

"We accept your conditions. When this incident is over, we will fulfil the promise we made today."

While he was taking advantage of the other party's misfortune in this transaction, Han Xiao did not extort an exorbitant price from Godora. The conditions that he had raised were the ones that he had already thought about, and it was within an acceptable range for the other party. This attitude of his made the upper echelons feel much more comfortable.

Han Xiao nodded and was in an extremely good mood. The negotiations had gone much smoother than expected.

Just as he had guessed, Godora understood their predicament and urgently needed something to break out of their current situation.

Godora displayed great sincerity and accepted his conditions generously. Furthermore, the ones who participated in the negotiations were those with sufficient authority in their hands.

The Mutation Source was exchanged for many things. First was a sum of money. 3,000,000 Enas were immediately transferred over, and his wallet, which had almost been flat, was fattened up again. The next was the supply of materials for the next few years, including a few special Godoran products, raw materials for machines, quality products produced by their factories, and completed spaceships. All of these would be sold to him at their cost price.

Apart from those material benefits, the rest would be his status, treatment, and request for clearance in certain areas. The motive of this would be to raise the fame of his mercenary group. All of those conditions required Godora to fulfil them in the long run.

He was not afraid that Godora would go back on their word. His backing of Floating Dragon Island was his assurance.

Furthermore, Han Xiao had hinted that Floating Dragon Island supported his actions and used this to build up diplomatic ties between Floating Dragon Island and Godora. This was not an alliance between the two, only the two parties sharing a closer relationship. After all, it was always better to have an additional friend.

Ames was respected by many, and there were plenty of organizations that gave her plenty of face. However, this did not change the fact that Floating Dragon Island was far too weak. All of Floating Dragon Island's influence could only be seen on the surface. For the organizations of the other beyond Grade A Supers, they all had deep relationships and cooperative deals with many civilizations. Han Xiao naturally would not break Floating Dragon's stance of neutrality, but being neutral did not mean that they could not make friends.

The Great Mechanic Han was extremely willing to help Floating Dragon Island form relationships with other organizations. This should have been Jenny's job, but that cold lady was obviously too conservative, and Han Xiao did not mind giving her more things to do.

The stronger Floating Dragon was, the more he would benefit.

Godora was naturally willing to be on good terms with Floating Dragon, and it could be said that they would die for that opportunity. They could naturally catch Han Xiao's drift and formed a tacit understanding.

"Godora thanks you for your contributions, and we will never mistreat our friends." The upper echelons looked at Han Xiao emotionally.

These figures of authority in Godora felt that it was time for them to reevaluate Black Star's importance.

Du...

The image disappeared, and only two people were left in the room.

Reaching a satisfactory outcome, Han Xiao threw the Mutation Source over to Nagakin.

"Take it. Send it back to Godora secretly, and don't let anyone rob you."

"I understand." Nagakin nodded heavily. He was already looking forward to the day when Godora broke out of DarkStar's disgusting scheme. Currently, he felt that Han Xiao was extremely pleasing to the eye.

Han Xiao then stretched lazily in the chair.

He had finally handed the Mutation Source over, and Godora would be able to quickly solve this crisis. The crisis would be solved a year earlier than in his previous life.

DarkStar was still kept in the dark. When they found out that their plan had failed, who knew what their expressions would look like?

If the players could finish this Main Storyline earlier, they would not have to waste time on Planet Aquamarine. Entering the universe as part of his mercenary group, they would definitely be far more valuable than in his previous life!

The experience of the players and the development of the storyline would definitely take a completely different path!

The future... who knows what it will be like?

Countless individuals would have their futures rewritten. Han Xiao shut his eyes, and his body tingled with an excitement that he had not felt in a very long time.

Chapter 554: It Is Time to Show My True Imagination

The Sanctuary was filled with an endless sea of people, and countless players surrounded Ames. Those who were far away were either standing on tiptoes, stretching their necks, or jumping up and down with excitement.

The majority of the players on Planet Aquamarine had seen Bun-Hit-Dog's videos before, and they all recognized the Dragon Emperor. Her fame among the players was only slightly inferior to that of Black Star. It was not only because of her beauty and sexy long legs. Most of the players had also seen many pretty female NPCs. The most important point was her strength. She was like an Empress with exalted status and the most powerful character that those players on Planet Aquamarine had seen.

With the huge gap in their status, her popularity had soared and never come back down. On the forums, there were even fans who had created a 'Dragon Emperor leg licking group'.

Talking about the name of fan clubs, Han Xiao's 'Black Star little mercenary family' and 'Captain love me once back up group' were not any much better.

In the past, the players could only see Ames through videos, but this time, she had actually descended personally. The entire Sanctuary was immediately overwhelmed with shock, and many players called their friends and brought all their family members over to witness Ames in person.

While they really wanted to rush forward and hug her smooth legs, the players all kept their distance from her. Not to mention whether or not they were able to activate the 'taking off their pants' and 'lick NPC' features, just witnessing Ames casually flattening a bunch of players who went near her was a huge deterrent. After all, none of them wanted to lose experience for nothing.

What a joke! She was a character who could destroy a star! What if she ended up destroying their Novice Village!

Ames looked at the endless players with curiosity. Those Space Wonders that Black Star had mentioned seemed to know her, and they all had excited looks on their faces. She could not help but feel that they were all treating her like an animal in the zoo.

After using her ability to scan the players, she found nothing special with the physique of the Inhumans. However, the couple of fellows who she had slapped to death previously had transformed into a white light and disappeared, not leaving behind a corpse. Her force field was able to differentiate between the millions of individuals, and in less than ten seconds, the few Inhumans whom she had slapped to death had entered the vicinity of her senses again. They had indeed revived.

If all of them had an undying body, even if they were slightly weaker, they could not be underestimated.

After this thought surfaced in her head, she immediately threw it to the back of her head. At her current realm, there was no need for her to pay too much attention to them. However, those Inhumans were truly intriguing, and they were pretty different from Aroshia.

It isn't a bad thing for Black Star to gather them, Ames thought to herself.

Since she would not be able to discover anything in this short period of time, Ames looked around before flying out of the crowd and toward the location that Black Star had told her.

The players in the plaza had already taken numerous pictures from all possible angles.

After she left, all the players began to chatter excitedly.

"I never expected to see the Dragon Emperor in person. How beautiful..."

"I seem to have fallen in love..."

"How useless! A single beauty caused all of you to lose all composure! Unprincipled and without a bottom line! Can't you guys learn from me? I will love Feidin forever!"

Apart from those uploading Ames' pictures onto the forums, there were a few who were guessing the reason for her appearance.

"How strange. Ames should be someone at the very top of the food chain. Why did she come to Planet Aquamarine? I feel that we shouldn't be coming into contact with someone like her at this phase..."

"Do you still need to guess? It is already written on the Wayne Cards. Go back and copy the effects of the Black Star card a hundred times as punishment."

"Black Star is Black Star indeed. So what if she is his boss? He will pull her along if he wants to."

Everyone knew that the Black Star Mercenary Group had the title of Floating Dragon Island's Field Team. They had powerful backing. When the Black Star Mercenary Group shot forward in fame and prestige, Godora would not even be able to see their taillights.

To a certain extent, Han Xiao's faction enjoyed a portion of Floating Dragon Island's fame with the most important factor being Ames' personal charisma. Joining the Black Star Mercenary Group was akin to having an opportunity to grow closer to Ames. This logic had attracted endless people to fight for the opportunity to join the mercenary group.

"However, why did Black Star call the Dragon Emperor over? Is it for the Mutation Disaster?"

"That can't be right? The Mutation Disaster shouldn't be enough for Ames to take action, right?"

The players continued their discussions, and the platform of their discussions changed to the forums.

The majority of the players were extremely excited about the Main Storyline of the Mutation Disaster, and they all felt as though an amazing reversal would suddenly take place. However, this guess of theirs was not without any basis. With the appearance of Ames, she was the best 'evidence' for their guesses.

Talking about Ames, Han Xiao naturally would not be left out of the conversation, and his fame was also increased even further. Han Xiao bringing Ames over gave the players of Planet Aquamarine a great deal of face. They could look at the other novice planets with the pride of 'my novice planet might explode, will yours?'

...

Nagakin did not delay for a single second and personally escorted the Mutation Source back to the Godoran mothership. After the negotiations with Godora, Han Xiao had a carefree expression on his face as he walked toward the Sanctuary's gathering point while considering his future development plans.

Godora needed time to carry out their research, but this was not a big problem to Han Xiao. Han Xiao's level of patience had reached the point where even when a fish was on his hook, the fish would become more anxious than him.

I only need to wait. Godora will need about a month or so to develop the antidote, and DarkStar can behave arrogantly for a little while longer. However, their plans won't be able to cause much trouble with so little time.

After handing over the Mutation Source, Han Xiao did not have anything to do before Godora developed the antidote. The safety of Planet Aquamarine was not an issue either. The intelligence network of DarkStar would definitely have noticed Ames' arrival, and it was impossible for them to create trouble at this moment.

"What should I do over the next month? There isn't a need for me to worry about disaster relief, and the hiring of players is already on track. The Mutation Disaster won't change too much within a month, and the benefits that I can gain from imparting those skills are also dwindling. With the players all leveling up, there isn't much I can extract from them like before..."

Could it be that he also had to join the club of killing time with cards?

No! He could not! Even if he was bored to death, he would not play cards!

It seems like I can only go into seclusion and manufacture machineries.

I earned 3,000,000 Enas from Godora, and together with my remaining 1,000,000, the funds on my hands exceed 4,000,000 again. Hmm, since I have money, I can buy some new Class Knowledge and increase my combat equipment...

Han Xiao's eyes lit up.

That's right, I still have to create a base on Planet Aquamarine and connect it to the universe officially. Only then will I have a never-ending supply of new players. It seems like I can move my plans forward.

He did not even need to think about the location and could just remodel the Sanctuary. Bennett definitely would not mind.

The materials were all readily available, and he could purchase some important facilities from the merchants in the universe. As for the construction progress... he would be a fool if he did not use the endless free labor. He could still issue them missions to ensure that they had a wholesome player life. Afterall, even the healthiest crops needed to be fed fertilizer.

He would model it after the equipment used in his first base, and even if the Six Nations wanted to send an atomic missile, his base would remain standing.

I now have something to do in this period of time.

With the idea in his mind, Han Xiao went back to the main hall of the gathering point, and when he was about to inform Herlous about this matter, he realized that Ames was already waiting there with Herlous and his other subordinates standing by the side respectfully. In the distance, there were many players looking over with faces full of excitement.

Ever since the players displayed enough strength to wipe out the beasts, his subordinates had returned to the Sanctuary to skive off. Under their lead, the entire hall had been transformed into a large room for them to play cards. A couple of players who were bored would occasionally come over to play some cards with them.

"You're here." Herlous hurriedly greeted. With Ames beside him, he felt an immense sense of pressure. Every single word that came out of his mouth had to be said with caution as he was afraid that he might end up offending Ames.

Han Xiao walked over and looked at Ames with a smile. "Have you seen the Inhumans?"

"You're right; they are very interesting." Ames looked at Han Xiao and retracted her aura. She no longer tested the subordinates under Han Xiao, and all the mercenaries felt their body ease up immediately.

"I will have someone arrange a room for you. Since there isn't anything for you to do, there will be plenty of time for you to observe them."

Ames smiled and said, "Alright."

Since she was already there, she naturally did not leave immediately after seeing the players. She would take the opportunity to take a look at Black Star's hometown as well.

"Right, I just negotiated with Godora using Floating Dragon's name. They are very thankful toward you."

"Hmm."

"The Godorans should come and visit you later. I will make arrangements."

"Alright, you can just manage it yourself."

"You seem to be interested in Aurora and Hila's abilities. I will introduce them to you later."

"Sure."

The both of them smiled.

Ames was an easy-going person and was not someone who put on airs. Since Han Xiao had already made arrangements, she would just accept them. After a few days of interaction, she was also used to interacting with Han Xiao in such a tone.

Besides, she did not dislike Han Xiao.

However, this resulted in a misunderstanding in the eyes of others.

The Dragon Emperor had always been mysterious, and the others did not understand Ames' temperament like Han Xiao. The majority of them had not even met this boss of theirs. In their minds, the Dragon Emperor should be an imposing expert who would turn their legs to jelly with a single glance. She should not have been someone so easy to talk to, no matter what. Furthermore, she had obviously given them a huge amount of pressure previously, and the pressure had only disappeared after Han Xiao's appearance.

As for Herlous and the few who had met the Dragon Emperor before, they realized that Ames' attitude toward Han Xiao was extremely different from before. She was more than ten times gentler than previously.

It could be said that she completely listened to Han Xiao's words, and her gentle tone was completely different from the persona of the high and mighty Dragon Emperor. Furthermore, the tone that she used to speak to them previously was obviously different. Only someone deaf would not be able to notice this difference, and it was impossible for them to not overthink it!

Could it be that the two of them...

Had that kind of a relationship‽

Herlous' eyes widened as he looked at Han Xiao's back in disbelief.

The Volga brothers were dumbfounded.

Feidin touched his cheeks subconsciously.

At that moment, the heart of those few officers were stirred.

Harmon could only feel the strange atmosphere. Looking left and right, he did not understand what was going on.

The jaws of those players watching far away dropped.

In the crowd, Bun-Hit-Dog witnessed this scene and his eyes lit up as inspiration immediately came to his head!

No wonder Black Star was able to casually call Ames over! So, this is the reason!

The Wayne Card didn't lie to me!

Bun-Hit-Dog's breathing became heavy as a large essay was formulated in his head.

This... picking up his superior, gaining both wealth and backing.

He was even able to subdue someone like Ames! Black Star's charisma is too frightening!

"BIG NEWS!" Bun-Hit-Dog prepared the recording excitedly.

...

After an hour, in some remote region of Planet Aquamarine was the hiding place of the DarkStar spies.

"Eh, after leaving for half a month, Black Star has come back. I wonder what he went to do."

One of the spies then turned on the satellite image, and after giving it a casual glance, it was as though a hammer had struck his head, and he was frozen in place.

Rubbing his eyes, he rewatched the footage more than ten times from different angles. Only after rubbing until his eyes turned red was he certain that he did not imagine it.

Did I just see the Dragon Emperor Ames‽

That monster who is able to destroy a DarkStar mothership?

"Quick quick quick... report this up to our superiors! Emergency report!"

The spy immediately ran over to his captain and was frightened to the point he almost wet his pants.

Chapter 555: Reactions from All Sides

"What did you say! Dragon Emperor‽"

Degulish's eyes froze in place, and he gulped in shock. His chest also tightened as though he had just been struck by a hammer.

Twenty minutes prior, the spies left behind on Planet Aquamarine had sent an emergency report. The intel officer had then hurriedly searched for the current commander of the organization, Degulish, and reported this matter with a pale expression.

Ames had appeared on Planet Aquamarine!

The upper echelons of DarkStar were shocked.

The Dragon Emperor had always been neutral. For her to appear in the Garton Star System suddenly, did it mean that she wanted to enter the fray? No, this was not likely. It was more likely that it was Black Star, that b*stard, who had called Ames over. But why Planet Aquamarine?

After giving the matter much thought, Degulish still could not understand Ames' intentions.

After analyzing the matter for a while, he felt that this issue was filled with oddities. The other party had chosen to land on Planet Aquamarine, not the mother planet of Godora. It did not seem like she was there for DarkStar but on vacation.

"Black Star is the leader of Floating Dragon Island's armed forces, and I heard that he has been expanding recently. Perhaps Ames is here to check on her forces' development," the intel officer said. "This is the most likely possibility."

Degulish nodded slowly and solemnly said, "We cannot let our guard down. We have some grievances with the Dragon Emperor, and she could be a possible unknown in our plan. However, as long as we don't provoke her, she won't be able to do anything to us. Even if she is a beyond Grade A Super, that only refers to her personal strength. She won't be able to resolve the current situation."

Saying that, Degulish let out a small sigh of relief. Previously, he had been frightened by Ames' reputation and instinctively felt that the matter was grave. But after thinking about it for a while, he realized that it actually was not a big issue.

So what if the Dragon Emperor could fight? They would just have to avoid facing her. Could her personal prowess resolve Godora's problems?

Even an expert like the Dragon Emperor would not be able to resolve the internal and external problems of Godora with her strength. She was just a single individual, and the vast universe would never be conquered by a single individual!

Degulish then began to ease, and after some thought, he instructed, "Order the spies on Planet Aquamarine to observe Ames' actions. Make Planet Aquamarine a forbidden location for now; no one is to go near Planet Aquamarine."

"Er, we didn't have any intentions to ambush Planet Aquamarine..." The intel officer was extremely helpless. The scene of their assault ships being destroyed by Black Star was still fresh in his memories. He would be a fool to send men over at this moment.

"Right, how is the progress of planting moles in the Black Star Mercenary Group?"

"I bribed some free mercenaries and asked them to apply to enter the Black Star Mercenary Group. Black Star Mercenary Group doesn't seem to hiring, but if he wants to expand, the moles that I bribed will have a chance to enter.

"As for bribing the members of the Black Star Mercenary Group, I haven't begun doing so. Without being certain of their backgrounds and having enough information, I wouldn't know which mercenary is the most likely to be bribed. I do not wish to alert them."

Degulish's eyes glowed, and he laughed coldly. "Very good. This is a plan to kill two birds with one stone. We will be able to infiltrate both the Black Star Mercenary Group and Floating Dragon Island."

The meeting then continued. Regarding the threat of the Dragon Emperor, Degulish only informed his troops to leave Planet Aquamarine and did not give any other orders. He felt that those measures were sufficient. Even if Ames was powerful, she would not be able to affect the plan that they had designed over many years. The most important thing was for them to carry out their plans.

What Degulish did not know was that the situation had already changed.

He still thought that he had plenty of time... the whole of DarkStar still felt so.

...

The fleet escorting Nagakin had returned to Godora's mother planet. This was a large planet that was more than ten times the size of Planet Golden Gate. Tens of defensive satellites surrounded the planet, and the security was extremely tight.

As the spaceship landed, the officers of the War Bureau who had already received news were waiting by the dock. The moment Nagakin disembarked from the spaceship, they all walked over to welcome him.

"How's the item?"

"Perfectly fine."

"Great, we don't have any time to waste. Head to the research department immediately."

Nagakin walked toward the research facilities under the guard of a large number of troops and two other Calamity Grade Supers. The roads toward the research facility were completely locked down, and no one was allowed to pass. Even the leader of Godora did not have the authority to enjoy such a treatment.

Nagakin walked over to the research lab carefully and successfully handed the Mutation Source over to the researchers. They would research the antidote for the Mutation Source at a location with the highest possible security and confidentiality. A leak was absolutely not allowed to happen.

As the key personnel who facilitated the trade between Black Star and Godora, he was allowed to wait for the results of the test. After waiting for half a day in the waiting room, he finally received news about the initial tests on the Mutation Source.

This item was indeed the source of the Mutation Disaster!

With the sample that Nagakin had brought back, the speed of developing the antidote would be increased rapidly.

"That's great..." Nagakin could finally be at ease. He had been extremely worried that the sample that Han Xiao had handed to him was useless.

"Amazing job!" The War Bureau head slapped Nagakin on the back.

"I didn't do anything. It is all Black Star's contribution." Nagakin laughed bitterly. He had never imagined that the key point to breaking them out of their current situation would actually be an outsider.

A bright smile could be seen on the head of the War Bureau's face, which was always solemn all year round. He was like a blooming chrysanthemum flower, be it in terms of shape or color.

"Indeed. Black Star has given us a huge surprise. I really never thought that a mercenary would be one to resolve our emergency."

After pausing for a while, he then said in a solemn tone, "This piece of news must be kept confidential, lest DarkStar comes up with another sinister scheme. It would be best if we can maintain the current situation."

In order to deal with the numerous attacks of DarkStar, all the departments of Godora were busy to the point where they did not even have time to sleep. The sudden aid from Han Xiao had truly surprised the whole of Godora's upper echelons, and even the highest leader of Godora paid attention to Black Star and even wanted to personally thank him.

The War Bureau had simulated their current circumstances, and the result left many of them in cold sweat.

If DarkStar had been allowed to continue behaving without any restraint, the situation would only have become worse. If the situation persisted for a year or two, Godora's progress would have been greatly delayed, and the entire Godoran Civilization would have taken a step back. The accomplishments of the Garton Star System that they had built up over the years would also go to waste. The worst situation would be an internal fracture within Godora.

Because they knew what the outcome could have been, the upper echelons of Godora were extremely excited! Black Star providing them with the sample would allow them to avoid massive losses, save countless citizens, and turn the entire situation around!

Han Xiao had become the biggest savior in the eyes of the upper echelons.

"Black Star is an important character from Floating Dragon Island. We can treat his aid as aid from Floating Dragon. Ames seems to place a great deal of importance on him... Perhaps we will gain some benefits from this misfortune and have the opportunity to befriend an organization like Floating Dragon Island."

The head of the War Bureau was extremely excited, and his eyes were glowing as he slapped Nagakin on the back again. "Black Star's strength is out of our imaginations, and you must maintain contact with him. If you can, it would be best to take your relationship to the next step."

Nagakin's mouth began to twitch as he asked, "Take the next step, meaning..."

"Make use of our advantage as Godorans and become his best friend!" the War Bureau head said with a serious expression.

Nagakin silently raised his fists, and a golden flame covered it.

"Don't think I won't dare to beat you up because you are my superior."

...

Ever since Ames landed on the planet, the atmosphere had become extremely odd.

Be it the players, refugees of the Sanctuary, mercenaries, or Godorans, they were all extremely curious about Ames. Ames also did not intend to hide anything, and her actions were for everyone to see. Han Xiao was also always beside her.

Han Xiao naturally did not mind being Ames' tour guide. After all, he was extremely free, and for the Dragon Emperor to make a personal appearance, he naturally had to show her some hospitality.

Ames was mainly interested in the players. However, in consideration for the fact that she was on Han Xiao's home planet, she acted in a low-profile manner and did not dissect the players as she wished.

Those from the Sanctuary would often see the two of them walking down the streets together, and when they thought about the hot rumors spreading around, their gazes could not help but become strange.

As Han Xiao noticed the odd gazes of those around him, while he did not display any expression, he was extremely speechless.

The brains of his officers must have been flooded with water. To think that they would actually dare spread rumors about him and Ames... While he was not bothered about such rumors, this was not necessarily the case for Ames. If she was not happy, she would be able to easily beat up all of his subordinates who were spreading the rumors.

At that time, should he help her whack them or help her beat them up?

However, over the next few days, Han Xiao's worries did not come true, and Ames did not react. Her expression was still the same, and she walked around with a smile on her face. If someone had told him that Ames did not notice the expressions of those around her, Han Xiao definitely would not have believed it.

Thinking about it carefully, how would an expert of such a level be affected by such silly rumors?

Han Xiao felt that he had been worried for nothing. At the same time, he was thankful that Ames could not see what was written on the forums.

The strange gazes of passersby was nothing. There were already more than a hundred fan fictions written on the forums about his 'love and hate' story with Ames. The content of the stories and perverseness of the characters made his hair stand on end.

The source of all of that was Bun-Hit-Dog's newest release. He had carefully analyzed the relationship between Black Star and the Dragon Emperor. Not only did he have photos to back his stories, he had even come up with extra stories on his own.

Bun-Hit-Dog was truly talented in this respect, and even Han Xiao almost believed what he had written. All of the players exploded in excitement and chaos, and the members of Black Star's fan club cried out in victory. The battle between the fans and flamers quickly spread to the other novice planets, and all the players from the other countries cried out for peace!

Thus far, Bun-Hit-Dog had been his publicity angel, but for the first time in his life, Han Xiao truly wanted to strangle Bun-Hit-Dog to death. Such a reporter was only interested in creating sensational news every day, creating stories out of his imagination, and twisting the truth. It was as though he was afraid that the world was not chaotic enough. If any player spread what was written on the forums and Ames ended up seeing it, was he not afraid that he would have to take responsibility‽

However, all of the ridiculous guesses aside, it could be said that Bun-Hit-Dog's post was truly superb. Despite Han Xiao being angered without having a place to vent his anger, he had to admit that the post was excellent.

"I am truly in awe..." Han Xiao smacked his forehead. Over the next few days, he had no intentions of visiting the forums again, afraid that his blood pressure would end up shooting up.

Ames had floated around beside him for the past few days, and they went around for a walk again that day. Han Xiao calmed himself down as he looked at the walls of the Sanctuary far away. The players climbed up and down the wall like ants as they attempted to rebuild it.

A few days ago, he had instructed Herlous and Bennett to issue a mission to upgrade the Sanctuary. The upgrading process had officially begun, and the players had a new job. They fully showed off the fine tradition of being able to work hard without complaining about fatigue, doing hard labor wherever it was required.

Now that the players had a certain degree of strength, their efficiency was far higher than when they built the Sanctuary. Han Xiao estimated that they should be able to complete the upgrade of the Sanctuary within a month.

"No wonder you want to hire the Inhumans. It seems like you hold a very high status in their hearts. You definitely place great importance in them." Ames smiled.

"There aren't many in this world that I view with such importance. Just that few million." Han Xiao shrugged.

The corner of Ames' lips curled up, and after letting out a soft chuckle, she suddenly turned and looked in a direction. Han Xiao also looked over, following the direction of her gaze.

Aurora and Hila were walking past, and upon seeing the both of them, their footsteps also stopped.

Recently, Hila and Aurora had been busy checking on the infected individuals. They had only heard that Han Xiao had brought back a bigshot from the universe but had not had a chance to meet her officially.

This time, it was a coincidental meeting.

"Are they the sisters that you are talking about?" Ames looked at the two ladies.

"Yeah." Han Xiao raised his brows.

On the other side, Hila was expressionless as she looked at Han Xiao and Ames. After pausing for a while, she then grabbed Aurora's hand and walked over to them.

Chapter 556: An Experienced Individual Indeed

"What a coincidence. Let me make the introductions. This red-haired lady is called Hila, and the one beside her is Aurora." Han Xiao looked at the two ladies and introduced them to Ames.

Hila walked up to the two of them with her gaze fixed onto Ames, completely ignoring Han Xiao.

Why is the atmosphere so awkward? Han Xiao's mouth contorted slightly, and he continued his introductions. "Cough cough, this is a top-notch expert in the universe, the leader of Floating Dragon Island, Land Ripper, Absolute Power, Dragon Emperor Ames. I am temporarily working for her."

"Top notch expert in the universe?" Hila's eyes narrowed. This description from Han Xiao immediately simulated Hila's nerves. "How powerful?"

Ames' eyes lit up, and a trace of pressure was exuded. "What do you think?"

Han Xiao coughed dryly and slotted himself between the two. He then rubbed Aurora's head and tried to change the topic. "Where is your little bear?"

Aurora snuck a glance at Ames before saying with tacit understanding, "It is sleeping at home. Han Xiao, this big sister is really beautiful. Is she a bigshot?"

She was asking the obvious with the intention of changing the topic. She could already sense the strength of Ames' life force with her Esper abilities, and Ames' strength was one that she had never seen before. She was like a frightened deer who did not dare approach Ames.

Aurora understood Hila's strong personally and knew that her elder sister was never afraid of any powerhouses. The word 'fear' was not in her dictionary. Seeing her sister's lousy attitude, she was afraid that this bigshot might end up enraged. Thus, she hurriedly played along with Han Xiao, hoping to break the tense atmosphere.

Hearing those words, Ames' gaze was diverted away from Hila, and she looked at Aurora. Seeing Aurora's adorable appearance together with a look of fear on her face, Ames' gaze softened, and she said with a smile, "Your body is full of life; I like that feeling."

Feeling the pressure being retracted, Aurora's heart eased up, and she smiled. "I also like the scent on big sister's body."

"Big sister..." Ames let out a merciful smile. "It has been so many years since someone last called me that."

With Aurora's interruption, the atmosphere was no longer awkward, and Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. He understood Hila's stubborn temper very well. Apart from her sister, she did not care about anyone else, and she also lacked any form of reverence toward experts. On top of that, she pursued strength greatly, and if no one restrained her, Hila would probably want to test the strength of this top-notch expert from the universe. If she ended up in a conflict with Ames, her death was almost certain.

Ames was considered pretty easygoing. If it was any other beyond Grade A Super, they would definitely have slapped anyone who dared provoke their prestige to death. Just like the old saying, a grandmaster cannot be humiliated, one who acted cool should get struck by lightning. This was probably the reason.

While Han Xiao paid attention to Hila's potential, her potential did not equate to strength. While Hila was much stronger than she had been a couple of years back, she would still be easily defeated by Ames. After all, Hila had not left Planet Aquamarine, so her sights were limited.

Hila frowned. She was not an overconfident frog in a well. From the very start, she knew that she would not be a match for Ames. She was only curious about how powerful a top-notch expert would be and how far away she was from that realm.

Since her words had been interrupted, Hila also threw away the idea and looked at Han Xiao. "You left Planet Aquamarine a few years ago. Have you been working for her the whole time?"

Han Xiao stroked his chin. "Almost."

"Aren't you a mercenary?" Hila asked doubtfully. She had always been extremely curious about Han Xiao's experience in the universe. While she had heard Han Xiao's introduction of Ames previously, she did not understand what those titles meant. Thus, she was extremely curious just how powerful Ames was and what kind of a background she had.

"About this, it's a long story." Han Xiao laughed awkwardly. He naturally would not talk about his embarrassing past easily.

At this moment, Ames placed her hand of Han Xiao's shoulder and said with a smile, "Black Star is extremely capable, and I really need him. He has helped me greatly these past few years and is someone reliable."

Ames still remembered that Han Xiao had only joined Floating Dragon because his life was in danger. Talking about this topic, she was afraid that Han Xiao would have a knot in his heart and thus felt that there was a need to display her trust and reliance on him. She was someone with a light case of mysophobia, but Han Xiao was not an outsider to her. From the moment Han Xiao helped her to capture Aesop, she had treated Han Xiao as one of her own.

"Er..." Hila's gaze suddenly narrowed as she looked at the palm on Han Xiao's shoulder.

She then thought about the recent rumors that had been spreading in the streets.

She originally did not think much about those rumors, but it seemed like the rumors were not wrong...

Hila observed Ames' appearance carefully. Ames was wearing a long dress and had an elegant appearance. Her beauty had the charm of age, and while she did not seem too stunning on the first glance, the more one looked at her, the more beautiful she got.

Being vain was the nature of a lady, and Hila subconsciously compared herself to Ames. Feeling that she was not a match for Ames' beauty, she did not feel too good inside. However, when she looked down at her chest, her confidence immediately returned.

Hila's gaze then swept past Han Xiao coldly.

Humph, all men are the same. As long as they go into the flowery world, not a single one of them will be able to withstand temptation.

Han Xiao had a strange look on his face.

What is this? Why is this darn lady always glaring at me?

At this moment, Aurora broke the stalemate and asked, "Big sister, why did you come to our planet?"

Ames' expression became gentle again, and she said with a smile, "Actually, there is a reason for me coming to Planet Aquamarine. I am very interested in both of your Esper abilities."

Hila's face changed abruptly, and her memory of the Germinal Organization flashed through her mind. Protecting Aurora behind her, she said with a wary look, "What do you mean?"

"One of you in charge of death, and the other in charge of life. Furthermore, the both of you are sisters. Very long ago, there were two similar characters in the galaxy. In the historical records toward the end of the war, the first appearance of a beyond Grade A Super seemed to have broken some sort of limit. Plenty of Calamity Grade Supers achieved a breakthrough in the various Star Fields after that. Perhaps they were already at a bottleneck, and the first beyond Grade A Super showed them the way. Or perhaps there were other reasons. In any case, plenty of beyond Grade A Supers appeared one after another during that period.

"After the war ended, these first batch of beyond Grade A Supers were recorded in the history books and called the [Primordial Ones]. Among them was a pair of sisters with abilities extremely similar to yours. Millions of years later, the both of you have appeared. Thus, I am very interested in the both of you."

While Ames was extremely lazy, she still had some basic knowledge of the universe's history. With Aurora and Hila being siblings and their Esper abilities being so similar, this coincidence was too stunning. Perhaps there was only a one in ten thousand chance of something like this happening. Paying attention to something that had such a low probability of happening had always been Ames' interest.

However, there had been many others with similar Esper abilities in the past, and she did not think that Aurora and Hila were related to the Primordial Ones. She only felt that it was a shocking coincidence.

Hila and Aurora had shocked expressions on their faces. This was the first time that they had heard about the history of the universe.

However, Han Xiao's eyes began to glow. As a resident of Earth who had read many different web novels, he immediately thought about the possibility of reincarnation.

Thinking about the storyline in his past life, Aurora had been reduced to meat paste very early on in the game, and she did not have a lucky halo or any fate protection. If she was truly a reincarnated being, her outcome was a little too pathetic.

Han Xiao shook his head helplessly and felt that he was thinking too much. This was probably just a coincidence.

"Then... then what do you want to do to us, big sister?" Aurora could not help but shrink back.

Hearing that, there was a moment when Ames' gaze turned distant as though she thought about some memories. She then quickly snapped back to reality and looked at the two sisters.

"I wish to... take the two of you as my disciples! Are the two of you willing?"

"What?" Han Xiao, Hila, and Aurora all looked at her with a strange expressions on their faces.

Ames was very interested in the sisters, and the thought of taking them in as her disciples was not a sudden one. When she was young, Aesop had taken her in, and this favor had always been in her heart. For a long period of time, her goal had been to find Aesop.

After Han Xiao found Aesop and fulfilled Ames' long time wish, she had another thought. Ames also wanted to take in a few kids like Aesop but had not managed to find anyone suitable.

When Black Star mentioned the two sisters to her on the spaceship, Ames had immediately grown interested. Aurora and Hila's parents had died when they were young, and they had huge potential. Furthermore, there was such a huge coincidence at the same time. Her age was sufficient to be the foster mother of the sisters and perhaps even sufficient to be their grandmother!

However, both of them were already all grown up and did not need another foster mother. As such, Ames decided to accept the two sisters as her disciples instead.

Both Hila and Aurora were stunned. They had never imagined that Ames would have such a request. Upon looking at each other, they could see the shock in each other's eyes.

"This..." Just when Hila was about to reply, she suddenly seemed to think about something and rubbed Aurora's head. "What do you think?"

She rarely made decisions on Aurora's behalf and largely respected her sister's opinions.

Aurora had a complicated look on her face. She did not understand Ames but felt a sense of closeness to Ames from the depths of her heart. She then turned around to look at the carefree Han Xiao and asked, "Uncle Han, what do you think?"

"Call me big brother," Han Xiao corrected with a helpless tone. "If you are asking me whether or not I encourage this, I definitely do. She is a peak level expert in the Shattered Star Ring after all."

It was a huge opportunity for a powerful individual like Ames to accept a disciple, and it was definitely beneficial to both the sisters.

Most importantly, Ames was his boss! He could not wreck her matters in front of her, right? Could he even give another answer‽

Silly lass, Han Xiao muttered in his heart.

"I shall listen to sister this time." Aurora dodged the bullet.

Hila fell silent for a moment before opening her mouth slowly. "I wish to know what kind of strength you possess and whether you have the rights to be my teacher."

Ames smiled gently and pointed her finger at the sky.

Nothing happened.

"What are you doing..." Hila frowned. Before she could finish her sentence, a large commotion came from the sky.

Boom!

In the sky, a few hundred meteors broke through the atmosphere from different directions and shot toward the ground rapidly. The destination of all the meteors was the same and they all shot toward the Sanctuary.

It was an extremely majestic scene, and it was as though the end of the world had arrived. All the players and refugees in the Sanctuary raised their heads with immense shock.

A loud cry sounded.

Just what's going on‽

Is DarkStar attacking again‽

Where's the Godoran fleet‽

With the few hundred meteors tearing through the sky and rapidly approaching the Sanctuary, there was nowhere for them to hide. As the meteors approached the Sanctuary, it became obvious what those 'meteors' actually were!

All of those meteors were actually the Godoran battleships on standby outside the atmosphere!

Hu!

Just when the meteors were only a thousand meters away from the Sanctuary, their ferocious momentum halted, and they froze in midair.

All the Godoran battleships floated above the Sanctuary.

Ames then tilted her head and said to the dumbfounded Aurora and Hila, "Do you think I have the right?"

Catching the battleships with her force field was a piece of cake for Ames. She had the title of 'Land Ripper' after all!

"Hahaha." Han Xiao lit a cigarette and laughed as he smoked with admiration in his eyes.

Ames is truly good at acting cool. Who would have thought that she was an expert in this field as well?

Looking up at the Godoran battleships, Han Xiao had a look of schadenfreude on his face. The fleet commander Barette is probably peeing his pants from fright at the moment.

Chapter 558: Fight for Time

It had only been a short time since the players began earning Enas, and their funds were limited. The players who could afford to buy equipment from Han Xiao were relatively rich.

However, regardless of how small their savings were, taking out three Enas was no problem at all. Many of the players did not have enough money to buy equipment, but they would definitely be able to afford the 'cheap' detector. Those poor players were Han Xiao's targets. Even if they could not afford a nine-course meal that cost thousands, they would be able to afford a simple bowl of soup that cost a few dollars.

Han Xiao intentionally set the reward of the mission to be extremely high to create the possibility effect in all of the players. This was just like buying a lottery ticket. When Nagakin described the detector to him, Han Xiao had already sensed the great opportunity.

While he could choose to provide the detector for free and issue it to the players automatically when they accepted the mission, what was the point of doing so? With the opportunity to make money being presented before him, how could he not seize the opportunity to harvest the players? The Great Mechanic Han would have let himself down if he did not do so.

The mission reward was a full 10,000 Enas. However, as long as enough players accepted the mission, not only would he be able to recover his costs, it would be possible for him to make a profit of over a thousand percent!

Three Enas was not much, but the players did not know that the cost of the materials was actually very low. As long as he had the blueprint, the detector could be completed with the most ordinary materials. In truth, this price was already ridiculously high, and it was almost akin to making profits without any cost! Han Xiao was extremely clear that this situation was necessary. As long as he kept the core technology in his hands and monopolized the knowledge, making money was an extremely easy affair. This money-making method was one that would be effective even at the national and civilization level.

Ordinarily speaking, even if the players could afford the 3 Enas, they would not buy such an item because the cost of the detector was far too low. However, the current situation was completely different. Because the detector was a mission essential, the detector suddenly seemed much more valuable. Using 3 Enas in exchange for a chance to earn 10,000 Enas seemed extremely worth it.

Everyone knew that the chance was slim, but many of them wanted to try their luck. Before truly experiencing failure, they all had that trace of hope in their hearts and felt that they might be the lucky one.

To the players, they only had to pay a small price, and there was no price for them to pay if they failed. Under such circumstances, many players were naturally willing to take the gamble.

Phillip quickly handled all of the payments, and the stock of detectors depleted rapidly. Han Xiao could see the balance in his account increasing rapidly.

5 million... 5.2 million... 5.4 million...

It only began slowing down after 5.4 million Enas.

"I earned about 600,000, which means about 200,000 players bought the detector. Hmm, the stock of the detectors should be depleted soon, but the production process of the detector is extremely simple, so the assembly line can start anytime."

Making use of the temptation of 10,000 Enas to get back so much more in profit. The margin was truly too good, and after eating this fat piece of meat, Han Xiao felt completely content. He already had enough to repay the debt. Of course, it was impossible for him to repay it now as he could use the money to grow more money.

Almost twenty percent of the players had chosen to take this gamble. Not everyone enjoyed gambling, and the majority of players did not join in the fun. However, the guilds definitely would not let go of this opportunity. Han Xiao loved such players who had ambition.

Han Xiao sent out ten or so spaceships under his charge, and all the players who accepted the mission were sent to the various regions of Planet Aquamarine. However, those few players were like a drop in the ocean compared to the size of Planet Aquamarine. Nevertheless, through Phillip's planning of all the player's search radius, together with the 2,000 meter radius of the detector, the efficiency of the search was not too low.

However, luck still played a huge role.

Not just the players, the Six Nations also sent out their armies to search for the Mutation Source and received a batch of detectors. However, those detectors were provided for free.

With the solution in their hands, be it Bennett, the Six Nations, or Godora, they were all extremely anxious to resolve the Mutation Disaster. As long as the trial on Planet Aquamarine succeeded, Godora would be able to wipe out the Mutation Disaster on the other ten or so calamity planets, and their internal mess would be resolved.

The hype of searching for the Mutation Source swept over Planet Aquamarine, and apart from land, the sea was also being searched. The navy of the Six Nations searched the seas, and Godora's spaceship didn't remain idle either, diving down into the deep sea to search for the Mutation Source. This was a region that the land forces would not be able to reach. Furthermore, the ferocious sea creatures underwater would not be able to cause any damage to the spaceship.

The entire planet sprang into action and conducted a thorough search of the planet!

"Who knows how long we will take to find the Mutation Source? It shouldn't take too long, right?"

In the office of the Black Star second base, Han Xiao shook his leg and looked at the projected Planet Aquamarine map on his communicator. At that moment, there were plenty of green lights on the map, which represented every single detector moving around.

He had improved the detector, and the moment any of the detectors locked onto the position of the Mutation Source, the coordinates would automatically be sent to him.

In the past, the players and Godorans had been the main force to deal with the Mutation Source.

But now, in order to prevent accidents and to save time...

Han Xiao had decided...

He would take action personally!

"Just what is with the people on Planet Aquamarine? Why are they suddenly searching all around the planet as though they are looking for something? Could it be that they are looking for the Mutation Source?"

In some corner of Planet Aquamarine, the DarkStar force that was in hiding noticed the strange actions of those on Planet Aquamarine and could not help but be shocked.

"There is this possibility. However, the entire planet is so large. How will they be able to find it?"

"We cannot rule out this possibility. It can't be that they created equipment to help search for the Mutation Source, right?"

"We can't be sure yet. Record it for now."

"If they continue with their search, there is a chance of them finding our hiding spot. Godora's fleet is outside the atmosphere, and we won't be able to retreat. Our situation is extremely dangerous."

The members of the DarkStar squad fell silent. When they received their mission, they had all known that chance of survival was slim and could only pray that their disguise would not be seen through. Their small spaceship was currently disguised as a rock, and there was a certain degree of concealment.

Every calamity planet had a small team to report on the planet's developments.

"We should just report this matter to our higher ups anyway," the captain, who was the only Grade B Super, said.

The report of the Planet Aquamarine squad passed through many hands before finally entering the hands of the upper echelons. However, Degulish and the head of the intelligence department only briefly went through it before placing the report to the side.

This was not the first time that those on the calamity planets had tried to search for the Mutation Source. The way Degulish saw it, it was no more than a waste of time, and such a report was of no significance.

Godora had managed to maintain a high level of confidentiality, and news of them developing an antidote had not slipped out. They kept up with appearances and pretended to be extremely anxious and fatigued.

Thus, DarkStar did not notice anything out of the blue and was kept in the dark.

Degulish naturally was not be able to see any problems from the report of the squad left on Planet Aquamarine. His attention was not on the calamity planets but on another important event.

During this period of time, DarkStar was preparing for their next step, and Degulish's attention was focused on this matter.

Their target this time was Planet Golden Gate!

Planet Golden Gate was a Grade A colony planet and was located near Juberly Hub. Furthermore, Juberly Hub was the central transportation hub that led to the different Star Zones and Star Systems. Thus, Planet Golden Gate was like Godora's bridgehead and had strategic importance. At the same time, the security was extremely tight.

This time, DarkStar's plan was not just to massacre the inhabitants of the planet but to destroy the entire planet!

Without Planet Golden Gate, the Godoran fleet would waste more time traveling to the various Star Zones.

"As long as this mission is a success, we will be able to severely wound Godora and create even more fear!"

Degulish's eyes glowed ferociously.

The assault was a very important part of their plan, and the DarkStar leader had allowed him to mobilize more than half of their fleet!

They were truly going all out!

Coincidentally, Black Star's base was also on Planet Golden Gate. In the past, they did not destroy the base due to considerations for their plan. Now that they no longer had to be wary, they could destroy it to their heart's content.

At the meeting table, a figure who was half concealed in the shadows asked, "Are you in charge of this operation?"

Degulish glanced at him and said in a deep voice, "That's right. Including you, everyone participating in the mission has to listen to my orders regardless of their rank and status."

This figure leaned forward, and his face was revealed from the shadows. He was Ember. The aura emanating from him was even colder than before. After massacring millions in their previous operation, he had become extremely silent, making everyone wary of him.

During the Noriosse incident, Degulish had once mocked Ember for returning in defeat, but now, he did not wish to provoke Ember. This was the deterrent effect of massacring millions.

"Call me when you take action." Ember nodded slowly. He then stood up and left the meeting room, not bothering about the fact that the meeting was not over.

Looking at Ember's back, Degulish began to frown, and the other upper echelons looked at each other with a strange look in their eyes.

Ever since the Long Arc massacre, Ember's personality had slightly changed. He had become extremely cold, and even the upper echelons could not grasp his thoughts.

"Then let the meeting end here," Degulish said without allowing any disagreement. "The fleet is already on their way, and we shall attack Planet Golden Gate in three days!"

Chapter 559: Storm. Lock On.

The following day at dawn, a thunderstorm was raging in the wilderness of the Western Continent.

Dark clouds covered the skies, and rain poured down madly. The sky was beginning to turn bright and darkness was being chased away by the light. The vision of anyone there would be blocked by the thick layer of fog and the merciless pouring rain.

Looking down from the skies, one would be able to see countless beasts roaming around the wilderness in stupefying numbers. There were many different species of beasts, and there were some beasts that were more than ten meters in size. Occasionally, the beasts would tangle with each other, rolling around in the mud as they fought. At the same time, skeletons of beast remains could be seen littered all over the place.

Near the periphery of the group of beasts, a player was currently prone on the peak of the mountain, stealthily overlooking the huge herd of beasts.

His ID was 'Nine Tail Fox', and he was a core member of Drizzling Rivers. After accepting the [Mutation Source] mission, he had coincidentally found this herd of beasts.

The herd of beasts stretched across more than ten kilometers, and it was truly a sight to behold. The detector was not able to detect the situation within the basin, so Nine Tail Fox was currently thinking of a plan. It was not realistic for him to even attempt sneaking into the herd of beasts. However, he was a Mechanic and had a small, remote-controlled unmanned drone that he had bought from the Six Nations.

"If the target is within the herd of beasts, it'll be a huge waste if I miss it. Isn't it just a remote-controlled drone? So what if I lose it! I shall gamble!"

Nine Tail Fox took out a small remote-controlled drone and tied the detector onto the body of the drone. The drone then flew up thirty meters and entered the herd of beasts.

The rain was a natural concealment, and the beasts on the outer rim did not notice the drone flying over their heads.

The drone slowly infiltrated the herd of beasts, and after flying for a while, a gluey, black substance struck the drone like a cannon. The drone was instantly knocked out of the sky and fell into a puddle of muddy water.

Clank!

The next moment, the black substance tangled up the drone and rapidly contracted, crushing the drone into smithereens. The detector, which was not able to complete its lock on, was also crushed together.

The black Mutation Source walked out from the herd of beasts, and the beasts around this black figure did not seem to see it. At the same time, the drone was absorbed into the thigh of the black figure as it walked past the drone.

"It was destroyed by something?"

Doubt plastered Nine Tail Fox's face. His control panel displayed a black screen. When the drone was knocked out of the sky, the image from the drone had been cut off. Just when he was pondering over what had happened, the disorganized beasts suddenly stood up in unison and looked in the direction of Nine Tail Fox.

Their growls sounded like thunder!

"My goodness! I've been found!"

Nine Tail Fox was momentarily startled before immediately turning around to run. A black bolt of lightning flashed past and blocked his way.

"What is this? Why is it so fast?" Nine Tail Fox was shocked. The black figure in front of him had a human-like physique and a well-built figure. His entire body was completely black like ink, with his skin being slightly reflective, and not a single strand of hair could be seen on it. At first glance, Nine Tail Fox thought that this was a wax figurine of some important character.

I am at level 62, but I actually can't even see this monster's movements clearly? Nine Tail Fox was shocked and immediately threw out a Detect.

Mutation Source: Half Mature (Red Name)

Level: ?

Type: ?

Danger scale: Fatally Dangerous

Note: Target is the source of the [Mutation Disaster] Main Storyline.

Found it!

Nine Tail Fox's eyes lit up.

However, before he could even react, the Mutation Source shot out a black substance from his arm as though his entire arm was detached. The black substance wrapped around his waist and contracted rapidly the next moment, crushing everything below his waist and dealing more than ten digits of damage to him. His health was instantly reduced by half, and the negative status of being crippled also appeared.

Thankfully, the bodies of the players were special, and they blocked all sense of pain. If not, Nine Tail Fox would have had to join the eunuchs already.

In this life and death moment, Nine Tail Fox did not bother about the Mutation Source's attacks and threw out a spare detector.

One would be able to carry out the mission by buying a single detector, but Han Xiao did not limit the number of detectors that the players could buy. The detector could be damaged, and a small portion of players had bought more than one detector. Coincidentally, Nine Tail Fox was one of those players!

The next moment, his health was depleted, and Nine Tail Fox let out a crazed burst of laughter before he turned into a ball of white light.

"Hahaha, this daddy here got the top prize!"

As long as he completed the mission, so what if he died once?

The Mutation Source retracted his arm and seemed to be puzzled about why there was no corpse. The Mutation Source then stood where Nine Tail Fox had disappeared and fell into a daze. As for the detector that was buried in the mud, it was completely ignored by him.

In the mud, the numbers on the detector shot up, and they finally broke the limit. This electromagnetic current was then sent out wirelessly.

At the same time, all the players on Planet Aquamarine received a notification on their interface.

[Mutation Source] has ended.

Mission completed by Nine Tail Fox.

All around the world, many players were dumbfounded.

"This... it has only been a day, but the mission is over‽"

"Who is Nine Tail Fox?"

"I know him. He's a core member of Drizzling Rivers."

The players broke out in fervent discussion. The end of the mission was truly too abrupt, and the others did not even get a consolation prize. The speed at which their dreams had shattered was too frightening.

However, they had only paid a small price, so the players were not too disappointed. They were only extremely envious of Nine Tail Fox.

Drizzling Rivers immediately questioned Nine Tail Fox and issued a guild notice of the Mutation Source's coordinates. With the mission being over, the coordinates were not important anymore. To a guild, announcing this piece of unimportant information to everyone was the best way to earn goodwill.

All the players began to flock toward the basin. While they had failed the mission, according to the mission introduction, there would definitely be a part two to the quest. None of them were willing to miss out on this.

The players on the other continents were extremely helpless. It was not possible for them to cross over the ocean in such a short amount of time. However, those on the Western Continent could seize the advantage.

All the players took out their mobility equipment or sprinted toward the basin. Very quickly, a few hundred players were gathered around the basin, and they all kept their distance from the herd of beasts.

Among the spectating players, there were quite a few players who were from guilds. The guild leader of Guild of Gods, Jupiter, was also present.

"Guild Leader, what should we do next? Should we attack the herd of beasts?" a member of the Guild of Gods asked.

"After finding the Mutation Source," Jupiter replied, "a battle will definitely follow. We should have the chance to participate in the storyline as well and will probably gain progress on the Main Storyline Mission."

Looking at the players in the surrounding, Jupiter decided to organize them into groups and shouted for their attention.

"Everyone, this is probably the Boss of the Mutation Disaster Storyline. All of you have seen that the number of enemies is immense, and a single guild won't be enough. It would be best for us to work together and not rashly provoke the herd of beasts. We should wait for more people to join us..."

There was nothing wrong with those words. In the face of the endless number of beasts before them, the numbers that they had were far from sufficient. All the players understood this and nodded in agreement upon hearing those words.

At that moment, before Jupiter could even finish his proposal, a loud swooshing sound was heard from the sky.

Rumble!

The few hundred players by the basin subconsciously looked up and saw the BlackLight Stealth slice through the sky and hover above the basin.

"That's... that's Black Star!"

The few hundred players were shocked.

Chapter 560: Boss Mission

The hatch of the BlackLight Stealth opened, and Han Xiao, clad in a black windbreaker, appeared in front of everyone. Due to the distance, he appeared like a little black dot, not unlike an ant.

Han Xiao's body flashed, and the players only saw a black dot fly right into the middle of the beast horde.

Boom!

The next instant, the center of the beast horde exploded outward in a shock wave, raising a wave of muddy black soil. The rain around turned into mist.

The dozens of beasts clustered at his landing point were blown away, tossed hundreds of meters outward, slamming into other beasts.

Boom boom boom!

The beasts fell to the ground one after another, rolling about on the earth, sporting bedraggled looks.

The four giant mechanical hands interlocked with each other, fingers opened and palms facing down. From afar, it looked like a golden lotus, and Han Xiao was standing on top of said golden lotus.

The ground was blasted full of craters, and Han Xiao's surroundings turned into a no-man's land.

The surrounding beasts immediately snarled toward Han Xiao, the breath released by their noses appearing like smoke in the cold rainy weather. Their claws and hooves struck the ground repeatedly, but none of them dared pounce forward. They could only express their dissatisfaction to this unwelcome guest.

"It's only been a few minutes. He came really fast!"

"There's indeed a sequel to this Storyline. Black Star is personally going into battle!"

The players received a boost to their morale. Ever since Black Star returned, the number of times that he had actually stepped up personally was too small—just how strong had he become? This was the greatest suspicion in the hearts of the players. Many of them immediately opened up their video recording function, wanting to broadcast it to the forums for the benefit of the masses.

The thousands of players who were unable to personally be there on scene observed through the forums. Countless eyes were concentrated on Han Xiao, anxious and expectantly looking at his every move.

"I've finally found you. To think that you had assembled a body... huh, why do you look so familiar?"

Han Xiao's gaze extended past all the beasts, locking onto the physical body of the Mutation Source. His face displayed some shock, as he found that the appearance of the mutation source was a little familiar, as though he had seen it before.

His thoughts spun. Those facial expressions, those eyebrows, that physique... why did they looked like the screwed up Germinal Organization Leader? He was probably imagining things.

"I know you..." The Mutation Source opened its mouth, speaking slowly. Its tone was strange, very foreign sounding.

Being able to manipulate the infected was the instinct and nature of the Mutation Source, similar to how a normal person could move their limbs. Having matured to this point, the Mutation Source could gather the infected with a purpose, and all the beasts surrounding it were its 'army'.

The Mutation Source had its own independent thoughts and was able to perceive the surroundings through the sensory organs of every infected. With most of the refugees of the shelter often coming across Han Xiao, it was not surprising that the Mutation Source could recognize him.

"Woah, you can even talk!" Han Xiao was overjoyed.

"A part of my senses... they are dulled... was it done by you? Why... why do you wish to hurt me?"

The talking of the Mutation Source was intermittent. With the suppression device from Godora in effect, a large portion of the infected in the area were unable to be controlled, nullifying its ability. This was akin to the paralysis of one's limbs, making it less 'flexible' than before. As such, it had become dull and harder to manipulate.

In its thoughts, those who robbed it of its sensory organs were all its enemies, but it felt a little wronged. It was merely moving in accordance to how nature dictated it to behave and did not understand why there were people trying to hurt it.

Han Xiao flashed forward, quick as lightning, and slammed his fist into the head of the Mutation Source. He was not interested in answering its questions. The Mutation Source had to be eradicated, and thus, there was no need for pleasantries with it.

At the point of contact, mechanical components unfolded along his arm. His fist turned into an alloyed fist that was more than a meter large, bursting with blue electric sparks.

The fist connected with the target, and at the nexus, a ring of water was blasted outward.

Bang!

The features of the Mutation Source were smashed flat, and akin to a baseball being hit during the home run, it flew far outward.

"Roar!"

The next moment, the Mutation Source decisively infused every beast with the feeling of anger, and the eyes of every beast present turned bloodshot as they went on a rampage!

Taking advantage of this short period of respite, Han Xiao took a glance on interface that provided the enemy's data. His eyes narrowed.

The Mutation Source is only half-mature and is poles apart from its final form. Its attributes have been completely crushed by me. This is good news, but that guy is considered a special lifeform, and in addition, it possesses a Boss template.

Even though its level is only at 75, its HP has reached 12,000! Furthermore, it still has the similar talents as the storyline in my previous life. This makes it harder to kill....

[Super Cell Proliferation Control]: Able to use energy to increase its cells and recover from damage.

Energy values can be converted into HP with a ratio of 1:10

Recovery rate capped at 50% of total HP/second[1].

[Efficient Energy Absorption]: When subject to any physical, energy, magical, or other attacks, a portion of the damage offset by the resistance will be converted into energy value.

[Ability—Special Substance Lifeform]: Damage received is reduced by 75%

Those three abilities were the talents of the Mutation Source. They were all Molding Abilities[2], which gave the Mutation Source extremely tenacious vitality.

The damage done to it previously by the punch was recovered in the blink of an eye. Furthermore, the first talent made its recovery ability frighteningly strong. With enough energy, it could technically recover 6,000 HP in a second!

As for the other two talents, they were meant to provide it with sufficient energy. In theory, if an attack dealt 100 damage, the Mutation Source would only receive 25 damage, and the 75 damage nullified would be added to it as energy. This energy value was fundamentally the lifeline of the Mutation Source.

Converted to HP, the Mutation Source would suffer from 25 damage but would be able to heal 750 HP!

Without the Destruction Serum invented by the Godorans, unless one could deal more than 6,000 damage in a second or kill it in one blow, the Mutation Source was practically unkillable.

Nagakin had mentioned that the serum would be able to insta-kill the Mutation Source, but that was the ideal theoretical outcome of the research. In reality, the Mutation Source would not die just by jabbing it once.

In his previous life, Han Xiao recalled that one injection of the serum would reduce the upper limit of the Mutation Source's HP by 25%, and the three Molding Abilities would also be weakened by half. This was also equivalent to weakening the Mutation Source.

Taking the previous theoretical 100 damage, the Mutation Source would now receive 62.5 points of damage and have the ability to recover 187.5 points of HP, as well as only up to 25% of its total health per second.

If the serum was injected once more, the Mutation Source would be further weakened, and only during the third injection would the Mutation Source collapse. Han Xiao had always felt that it was a problem with the dosage, but with only one opportunity for the decisive battle, there was no chance for trial and error.

In the future, the Mutation Disaster would become a dungeon released by Godora. However, the serum used would still be a necessary item, with its dosage already fixed. The players were unable to transform it privately.

The dose in Han Xiao's hand had already been fixed, and it would not be an easy job to change its components.

The moment the Mutation Source was sent flying by Han Xiao, the spectating players also received a Grade B Mission—[Destroy the Source]!

This was the Boss Mission that came with the Main Storyline of the Mutation Disaster. This was the decisive mission and had appeared a whole year earlier compared to Han Xiao's previous lifetime.

Similarly, it was Han Xiao who had triggered his mission.

The base reward of the mission [Destroy the Source] would be 800,000 experience. The mission requirements were simple—to deal with the Mutation Source and its beast horde. The more beasts that were killed, the higher the evaluation, and thus the chance of obtaining an extra reward.

As for the character that killed the Mutation Source, they would receive the highest rating. The mission introduction mentioned this point but did not state the corresponding reward.

However, Han Xiao was aware that, because only one person could achieve this, the reward was extremely generous. One of the rewards was actually the chance to obtain two of the skills or talents of the Mutation Source.

In his previous lifetime, the various guilds had fought against each other openly and secretly, all aiming for the final hit. Finally, it was Dynasty's King Admiral who had taken its head.

However, Han Xiao could only apologize in advance to King Admiral.

The last hit reward was something that he had to get!

[1] No, this is not an error. It really is that broken. Back

[2] A Molding Ability is the special type of Talent that's usually only seen in NPCs. Han Xiao's Molding Ability is the one which gives him a high HP conversion. Back

Chapter 561: Mechanical Beast Guards Army!

The battle started!

Numerous beasts surrounded Han Xiao, and they flashed their teeth and claws as they pounced toward him. Han Xiao changed the posture of his hands, connecting four of the giant machine hands with Mechanical Force. His twenty giant fingers turned into cannon barrels.

Boom!

The light cannons wildly shot, and even the misty fog was evaporated by the high temperature. The surrounding beasts were riddled with holes and fell continuously. Their blood flowed into the mud, turning into a viscous, nasty-smelling liquid.

For a brief moment, no beasts could approach Han Xiao.

However, the number of beasts numbered above ten thousand, stretching out endlessly. Under the control of the Mutation Source, the beasts were whipped into a frenzy. Other than Han Xiao, who was surrounded by the beasts, the hundred odd players also turned into live targets.

The beast horde rushed out to attack, roaring continuously. The ground shook as they stampeded over, the sound of their roars covering even the sound of the heavy downpour.

Because Han Xiao had brought the storyline forward significantly, the Mutation Source had become much weaker. Thus, the current beast horde was much smaller than in his previous life. However, this also indirectly caused the number of players available to also be smaller, with only a population of a few hundred. The boss battle against the Mutation Source was supposed to be an all-out war, yet it had turned into a sudden encounter with only a few elites involved!

The expressions of Jupiter and the others changed as the surging tide of the beast horde drew closer rapidly. When compared to the huge beast tide, those people felt insignificant, as though they could be swallowed up in the wave at any time.

When the boss battle mission had successfully been triggered in the information interface, each of the few hundred players had actually hoped to be the one to kill the Mutation Source. However, in the face of this avalanche-like beast horde, all their fantasies were ruthlessly crushed.

Are you kidding? With so few of us, we cannot even break through the beast horde. How can we even go against the Boss of this Mutation Disaster‽

A large portion of the players felt their hearts tighten as a feeling akin to that of a mantis attempting to stop a cart appeared in them. They felt weak, helpless, and pitiful. An urge to retreat rose unbidden within them.

The lion beast that was at the forefront opened its bloody maw, showcasing its sharp and ferocious teeth. A putrid stench wafted over as it readied to pounce.

Clank!

Suddenly, the clanking of machinery silenced even the sound of the heavy downpour. The next instant, countless artillery and gunfire bombarded the inner area of the beast horde. The glare of the fire seemed to chase after the gloomy darkness caused by the overcast clouds, illuminating the faces of the players.

The beasts that were originally running toward the players stopped and turned behind to look. The players took the opportunity to run a little further. As they looked back in surprise, every one of their mouths dropped.

They only saw that within the center of the horde, 4,000 to 5,000 machines had materialized. There were hundreds of flying turrets in the sky and densely packed mechanical beasts on the ground—such as the Black Panther series, the Spider series, the Crawler Tank series, and many more. All of them were moving in a fluid manner, as though they were true creatures. From afar, they resembled a colony of armored ants.

The beasts closest to the steel army were shredded without exception, and no one else dared get in close proximity to them. Metal and flesh stood in opposition of each other, with the eight Oathkeepers guarding Han Xiao in a ring-shaped formation. The raindrops splashed off their armor, creating a wet luster.

"Do you think that only you have an army?"

The corners of Han Xiao's mouth hooked up, and his energy built an invisible cover above him, blocking the rain and flowing outward, such that even his clothes remained dry. Compared to the roaring beasts, the mechanical beasts around him were cold and silent, like elite soldiers who followed instructions precisely.

A distance away, the Mutation Source stood on the back of a ten-meter-tall mammoth, unmoving. The facial features that were originally flattened had once again reappeared. Even it was shocked by this change.

A year ago, Han Xiao had obtained a loan from the Noriosse Financial Group, lining his pockets with money. Other than building his base, he had also expanded his mechanical army. The 4,000 or so troops standing there were his current mechanic army... but this was only a part of the complete force!

Its name was his Mechanical Beast Guards Army!

"Are... are all of these his machines‽"

"F*ck me, this is the true opening style of the Mechanic!"

"My goodness, give me a slap to wake me up!"

Hundreds of players rubbed their eyes, looking on with an expression of shock. In the blink of an eye, how come there were so many more machines around Han Xiao?

The group of people suddenly realized that this could be the first time since returning that Black Star had shown his cards!

Regardless of whether it was the hundreds of players present or the tens of thousands of players on the forums, everyone had the same thoughts.

This is the true style of the Mechanic!

One person is equivalent to an entire legion!

On the forums, all the Mechanic players were staring with sparkling eyes. They had already set Han Xiao as their role model, and they were determined to build their own mechanic army.

So what if it's a money burner? The style points for this are through the sky!

Let's not even talk about being strong. If one does not spend money, even appearing handsome would not be possible!

It was unknown, however, just how many players were pushed into the abyss of poverty just by this scene.

"Go, my children." Han Xiao spoke lightly as he activated the legion.

Boom!

The Mechanic Army powered up in an instant, throwing themselves into the beast horde as though they were smashing into bamboo. With various attacking methods, they forcefully carved out gaps within the horde of beasts. The levitating artillery also reacted, firing lasers everywhere. With their strong penetrative power, the era of gunpowder and electromagnetic weapons paled in comparison.

The Void Dragon Mechanical suit covered Han Xiao's body, and its propulsion system at the back spurted out a long tail of flames. Han Xiao broke through the curtain of rain like a rocket, instantly rushing to the back where the Mutation Source was standing on the mammoth's body. The thrusters on the soles of his feet erupted, and the biochemical muscles around his leg swelled, delivering a ruthless knee strike to the abdomen of the Mutation Source.

His knee was buried deep in the abdomen of the Mutation Source, a force enough to break through the strength of a building concentrated within that small area. A shockwave radiated from the point of contact.

Boom!

The body of the Mutation Source curled up like a cooked shrimp. The next second, it resembled a released arrow, shooting up into the sky!

Bending his legs, Han Xiao threw himself up as well. The force from his jump was delivered to the mammoth below him, and it screamed in pain, slamming into the mud below it.

Han Xiao quickly caught up to the Mutation Source whom he kicked high up. A mechanical hand unfolded, assembling into a drill that pierced deep into the chest of the Mutation Source. It lay skewered on the drill. However, despite how severe the injury looked, it had no effect on the Mutation Source.

"This sort of attack... has no effect on me..."

The Mutation Source remained expressionless, mumbling passively as though stating a fact.

The left hand of Han Xiao opened up into a claw shape, with conical needle like tubes poking out of his fingertips. The five fingers viciously pierced onto the face of the Mutation Source, and as the needles penetrated, they released the Destruction Serum through the tubes, injecting it into the body of the Mutation Source.

Bang!

The Mutation Source exploded completely as though it was an overfilled water balloon, spraying out everywhere. It was as though the rain had turned black all of a sudden. With the internal skeleton exposed, it was quickly torn apart by the rotating mechanical drill.

The majority of the black tar like substance disintegrated into a molecular level before it could touch the ground, disappearing without a trace.

As for the remaining parts of the Mutation Source, it splashed into the muddy water, reverting to its original slime form. It sprayed out more slime, constructing its simulated body from scratch once again. However, without an internal skeleton, the process was a lot more difficult. It took a long time for a human shape to be restored. Although it could not show any expressions, its fear could not be hidden.

"Urgh... what happened? You... what have you done‽"

Within its ink black body, white lines could be seen radiating around it, like tiny snakes swimming around. Now that the first injection had taken effect, the Mutation Source discovered that its ability was greatly suppressed. During the instant in which it had been injected, it had lost its connection to all the infected people. It could remember this sort of deep darkness from when it had just been born, without any external senses to manipulate.

There was a moment where all the raging beasts were free from the control of the Mutation Source. Their anger and fury had dissipated, causing them to regain clarity. However, this only lasted for a few seconds before the Mutation Source regained its strength and reasserted its control. However, its control intensity was reduced, and it could detect that it had lost a lot of energy, becoming weaker.

In its short life, it had felt the taste of fear for the first time.

The eight Oathkeepers around Han Xiao were like barriers, separating the beast horde and preventing the Mutation Source from receiving support. Han Xiao landed near the Mutation Source, and looking at its expression, he felt as though he was beating up a small child.

The upper arm of his mechanical suit revealed a cylindrical recess, and the empty serum tube was ejected, dropping into the mud.

Looking at the stats of the enemy, Han Xiao's brows furrowed. He discovered something strange, that the ability of the Mutation Source had only decreased by about a third. This was vastly inferior to the effects that he remembered from his past life.

He had a suspicion and, upon pondering further, realized the issue.

Previously, Godora spent a longer time doing research, and while the circumstances now are different, because I gave them a sample, the research time was still too short. Because I was pressed for time, the sample provided was weaker than in my previous life, so there's a need for a larger dosage.

Nagakin had only brought three serums, and Han Xiao had planned to use all three to quickly eliminate the Mutation Source. However, the effects of the serum were not as pronounced as before, which was something that he had not expected. Most likely, even if he finished injecting all three, the Mutation Source would still not collapse on its own.

Sh*t!

Godora was indeed unreliable. It was still better to use his fists to solve the problem!

Cupping his fists, Han Xiao helplessly shook his head.

"It seems like I'll need to accompany you for some playtime."

Meanwhile, the Mechanical Beast Guards Army cooperated seamlessly under the control of Phillip, pinning down all the beasts on the mountains and plains. Even the beasts who were originally going after the players had turned back to fight the Mechanical Beast Guards Army that was like a meat grinder.

The hundreds of players finally heaved sighs of relief, pausing to look at the blood-soaked battlefield. Seeing that the beast horde was occupied by Han Xiao's army, they started to plot once again.

The beast horde is no longer chasing us!

That's right, Black Star's Mechanic Army is likely to be pinning the beast horde down.

This is as good as helping us restrain them, so we'll have the chance to integrate into the battlefield and fight with the beasts!

Furthermore, we can even kill off the Mutation Source and complete the first kill!

Jupiter's eyes gleamed, and he was overjoyed at this scene.

While Black Star was currently dealing with the Mutation Source, an NPC would definitely not care who ended up killing the Mutation Source. As for them, they would be able to obtain the extra reward by killing the Mutation Source! This was an opportunity to achieve the highest rank for the Ranked mission!

The hundreds of players were eager to move, wanting to be the one that took its head.

...

The moment the detector locked onto the Mutation Source, Han Xiao had immediately taken his BlackLight Stealth out, without having time to inform anyone else. However, all the various parties had been concerned about the movement of the BlackLight Stealth. Han Xiao had only exchanged a few blows with the Mutation Source before the Six Nations, Bennett, Nagakin, and others saw the pictures of the battlefield through satellite imagery. It was then that they discovered the presence of the Mutation Source, and they were all overjoyed by this news.

It had only been a day, but they had already found the Mutation Source! Nagakin was immensely happy and immediately gathered his troops to provide support.

The same was true for Herlous, who immediately gathered the mercenaries to set off. While he knew that Han Xiao would likely not require much help, as his subordinates, to have the leader fight whilst they ate popcorn, what sort of mercenaries were they!

If they were picked on by Han Xiao because of this... Thus, even if it was just to join in the fun, they had to be on scene!

Bennett had absolute confidence in Han Xiao and waved his hand, allowing people on the battlefield to broadcast the scene of the battlefield inside the Sanctuary. All the channels displayed images of Han Xiao fighting on the battlefield, and the refugees were all seated around their screens, nervously watching the fight unfold.

Hila and Aurora also stopped their work of checking for the infected, looking intently at the screen.

"Sis, look, Han Xiao!" Aurora happily exclaimed.

Watching the one-sided fight, Hila's red lips trembled, her expression conflicted.

She thought about how, a few years ago, Han Xiao had destroyed the Germinal Organization and ended the war. To say that he had saved the world was inappropriate, but he had indeed saved her sister and herself.

However, Han Xiao was really saving the world this time. From the time he returned to the present, the number of people whom he had saved was probably in the millions.

While she had known him for a few years, Hila realized that she had never truly understood Han Xiao. This person was like a closed book, making it difficult for anyone to actually know what he was thinking.

On the screen, watching Han Xiao's show of force by using one person's strength to stop an army of beasts, she definitely could not achieve that. In just a few years, she had already been left far behind.

Hila could not help but tighten her fists.

Only by following the Dragon Emperor to cultivate will I be able to catch up with him, right?

The attention of the Six Nations was also focused on Han Xiao, their hearts tightening with anxiety.

Only when Han Xiao destroyed this Mutation Source would the disaster truly end. Only today did they finally see a ray of light in this bleak and dark world.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations all stopped their work, staring fixedly at the image transmitted by the satellites. Even the heads of the Six Nations did the same.

Everyone hoped in their heart for Han Xiao to succeed.

As for the DarkStar squad that were hidden in Planet Aquamarine, they also discovered the scene of the battlefield.

Chapter 562: Destruction

The DarkStar team stationed on Planet Aquamarine had originally thought that it would be completely pointless for the forces on Planet Aquamarine to search for the Mutation Source. However, they had managed to find the Mutation Source in a single day. This truth dumbfounded those in the team.

The new research equipment had only been put into use for a few days, and DarkStar had been kept in the dark. They did not know that Godora had developed a device to locate the Mutation Source but assumed that it was because of luck.

"Black Star is fighting the Mutation Source in the Western Continent," a member of the team reported. "From the images shown, the Mutation Source does not have the ability to fight back. Black Star's strength is far superior to that of those on the planet, and it will be impossible for the Mutation Source to win against Black Star."

"I know," the captain said in a deep voice. "The detection equipment must have detected the Mutation Source's radiation reaction. The Mutation Source isn't mature yet, and it is currently weak. Even if it has obtained a body, it may not be a match for Black Star.

"However, it is extremely difficult to kill the Mutation Source. Most attacks are useless against it and will allow it to accumulate energy instead. While Black Star is powerful, he won't be able to kill the Mutation Source."

While they were surprised at the fact that the Mutation Source was found, the DarkStar team was not anxious. The Mutation Source had a stubborn life force, and it would not be easily destroyed. However, it was best that they report this matter to their higher ups.

Just when the captain was about to contact his superiors, one of his team members gasped. "Wait, what did Black Star do‽ The Mutation Source seems to be injured!"

"What‽" The captain immediately looked at the screen, only to see Han Xiao injecting the Mutation Source with a needle before seeing the state of the Mutation Source taking a turn for the worse. That attack of his had caused true damage!

The face of the captain turned dark and immediately understood what was going on. No wonder Planet Aquamarine had suddenly started searching for the Mutation Source! It turned out that Black Star had found a way to deal with the Mutation Source!

He immediately realized how serious the situation was.

"Send an emergency report to the headquarters!"

A gigantic DarkStar fleet was currently moving in space and nearing Planet Golden Gate.

It was only two days until their assault on Planet Golden Gate, and their forces were now rushing toward Planet Golden Gate. Degulish had placed all of his attention on this matter and handed all other affairs over to the intelligence department to handle. However, right at that moment, the intelligence department rushed into the room with an emergency report. The Head of Intelligence's tone was filled with anxiety, and Degulish's puzzled eyes gradually turned into shock.

"Impossible!" Degulish stood up abruptly with a face of disbelief.

Black Star was currently fighting the Mutation Source and Planet Aquamarine seemed to have the ability to solve the Mutation Disaster at its roots!

The organization that had sold DarkStar the Mutation Source had shown the upper echelons of DarkStar a set of complicated data and ensured that it would take at least a year before the Mutation Source would be dealt with. However, only a few months had passed! How could Godora come up with a solution so quickly‽

The Head of Intelligence had an ugly expression. "Godora kept the matter a complete secret, and my intelligence network wasn't aware of their research details."

Bang!

The alloy table was smashed into pieces; Degulish was furious.

He had never expected that the first thing to go wrong with this plan would be the foundation of his entire plan! It was akin to his backyard being on fire!

If Black Star or Godora truly had the means to deal with the Mutation Disaster at its roots, all of DarkStar's plans would be affected! Without Godora's forces being tied down in the calamity planets and the many political restraints that Godora faced internally, the latter part of their plans could not be carried out. This plan that they had spent many years preparing for would have to come to an end.

To think that things would go wrong at this crucial moment!

If it was truly the worst-case scenario, their attack on Planet Golden Gate would be forced to stop, and they would have to alter their plans.

"Just what is..." Degulish grit his teeth and suppressed his rage. "Tell the team on Planet Aquamarine that I want them to give me a live report of the battlefield!"

Outside the door, Ember passed by coincidentally. Glancing at Degulish, his eyes narrowed for a moment, and a queer look could be seen in his gaze.

Bang bang bang!

The Mutation Source did not have the strength to fight back before Han Xiao and was beaten black and blue. The Mutation Source was sent flying all around and was like a human-sized sandbag. Not only was it very durable, it felt extremely good as well. Han Xiao could not even bear to use any long-ranged weapons, and the Mutation Source was truly a premium product in the world of sandbags.

How wonderful it would be if he could give the Mutation Source a few punches when he was bored.

It was a pity that the Mutation Source would definitely have to be killed. Not to mention Godora's firm stance, the Mutation Source was a biological weapon that could control other living beings, and it was a huge threat to many species in the galaxy. The lawful civilization would not allow such a weapon to be in the hands of an outsider.

The scene of Han Xiao beating up the Mutation Source was broadcast to all the players on Planet Aquamarine. All the players had a queer feeling in their hearts. The Main Storyline Boss was currently being furiously beaten up by a familiar NPC. Why did it seem as though Black Star was more like the Boss?

Seeing the Mutation Source being beaten up so badly, some of the players could not help but pity it. Voices of encouragement could be seen on the forums with many joking about it.

"Give it your all! Don't give up!"

"Run! You won't be able to win against the great demon Black Star!"

Swoosh!

Han Xiao chopped down on the Mutation Source's head, but there was no feeling of striking a target. Han Xiao's hand cleaved through the Mutation Source and split it in two. More accurately speaking, the Mutation Source had chosen to split its body in two to avoid Han Xiao's chop.

Following which, the two halves began spitting out a black, gluey substance like a fountain, and that black stuff began swimming away in the muddy water like snakes.

While the Mutation Source's thoughts were still immature, fear was a natural instinct. In its short confrontation with Han Xiao, it had always been on the losing end. Han Xiao's strength made it feel completely helpless, and the Mutation Source did not wish to continue this battle. As such, it split up its body to confuse its opponent, allowing its main body to escape.

The rain provided the Mutation Source with an avenue of escape. With the beasts fighting the mechanical army, the entire battlefield was a complete mess, and it was beneficial to the Mutation Source's escape. Amid the copious black sticky substance, only one part of it was the main body.

"Want to escape? Do you think that's possible?"

Upon saying that, Han Xiao suddenly felt as though he was the antagonist.

The thrusters on his back and feet were activated, and Han Xiao shot toward a black sticky gel that was currently escaping. When they were battling, Phillip had recorded the data of the Mutation Source, and the radar clearly displayed the position of the main body.

The Mutation Source was currently in the shape of a snake and upon sensing that Han Xiao had locked onto it, its body transformed into a water like state, seeping into the soil.

Swoosh!

Han Xiao waved his arm, and two gigantic mechanical arms scooped up the soil, catching the Mutation Source together with it.

The Mutation Source then shot itself toward an eagle and dug into its body.

The eagle shot toward the sky and flew away.

Tuk tuk tuk!

The next moment, more than ten cannon towers in the surroundings turned around and locked onto the eagle. In an instant, the eagle was reduced to a lump of burnt meat.

With a loud thud, the Mutation Source fell back onto the ground. It still wanted to escape, but a large mechanical hand suddenly appeared and grabbed it tightly.

"You won't be able to escape from both the skies and ground. Stop struggling and take your injection." Han Xiao clenched his fists, and a needle could be seen on his finger. The second needle was injected into the Mutation Source.

Pa!

An explosion similar to the first time could be heard, and the interface displayed a notice of the Mutation Source being weakened again. This time, the Mutation Source took a longer time to regain its human form.

The beasts in the surroundings regained their clarity again, and they managed to maintain their clarity for a longer period of time before falling under the control of the Mutation Source once more. At the same time, the beasts were obviously less crazy, and some of them even showed signs of retreat.

The Mechanic Army was like a meat grinder, and the thousands of beasts were ground into meat paste by these metal beasts. The dark, muddy waters were dyed completely red. In the face of the frightening enemies that did not seem to know fatigue, the beasts under the control of the Mutation Source could not suppress their fear.

Right at that moment, a commotion erupted.

Han Xiao turned around and saw hundreds of players charging into the battlefield.

Without even thinking, Han Xiao knew that those players were attracted by the Boss and wanted to snatch the last hit from him.

The intention of the players was far too obvious. They wanted to make use of the gap that had been created by the Mechanic Army and beasts to charge to the boss. In other words, they treated his Mechanic Army as a form of cover.

"How crafty."

Han Xiao's mouth cramped up a bit, and he instructed Phillip to pull back the Mechanic Army as long as the players moved forward. The effects of his actions were extremely obvious, and the plan of the players was foiled. Without the cover of the Mechanic Army, they were quickly overwhelmed by the herd of beasts, and their deaths were truly a wonder to behold.

Want to snatch the last hit? You must be dreaming.

Shaking his head, Han Xiao charged toward the Mutation Source and injected the last needle into the Mutation Source.

With the three injections done, the Mutation Source was on the verge of collapse and showed signs of melting. However, his guess was not wrong, and the Mutation Source did not get destroyed.

Godora were truly pig like teammates!

Thankfully, the Mutation Source has less than half of its strength, and it's extremely easy to kill.

The Mutation Source was currently at its weakest, and Han Xiao did not wish to allow anyone to snatch the last hit. He waved his arm and let out the Halo Array. A golden shield was immediately formed around him and the Mutation Source. With the strength of the players and beasts, it would be impossible for them to break this light shield.

The Mutation Source's body began to change shape, and it could only maintain the shape of the upper torso. Part of its main body began to disintegrate and disappear, which meant that the Mutation Source was on the verge of destruction. It became extremely difficult for the Mutation Source to even maintain its human form, and it was already on the verge of death.

The Mutation Source suddenly opened its mouth. "I don't wish to die..."

While its tone was monotonous, Han Xiao could hear the pleading in it.

Pausing for a moment, Han Xiao opened the helmet of his mechanical suit and sighed. "I am here to kill you. It is useless for you to say this to me."

"I don't understand... I only wish to survive like all of you..."

Han Xiao shook his head and replied, "You have already brought a huge calamity to this planet, and while this may not have been your original intention, your very existence is in conflict with too many species. Your survival would mean the death of others. Even without me, there are others who would kill you."

The Mutation Source treated other living beings as its sensory organs and aimed to assimilate other living beings. In its world, controlling its sensory organs was its innate ability, and there was nothing wrong with it.

Looking from another perspective, it could be said that the Mutation Source was a type of special life form that could control different sensory organs to become part of its body. Its innate ability was to expand its own 'body', and it would naturally stand on the opposite side of many living beings.

When the Mutation Source was sufficiently strong, it would be able to control all living beings on a planet, and the living beings on the planet would become its body. This meant that the entire planet would become its 'consciousness'.

If an outsider stepped onto the planets and entered its range, they would also become part of the Mutation Source's body.

At this level, the Mutation Source was no longer a type of virus or weapon. Instead, it was like a divine being that could grasp all consciousness!

Thus, the existence of the Mutation Source was too much of a threat.

"Why...? Why am I the only one who can't be alive?" the Mutation Source muttered to itself.

Hu!

Right at that moment, Nagakin's spaceship arrived and was rapidly reaching the battlefield. They arrived at the very end and came with the majesty of the cops.

"It's time for you to be on your way." Han Xiao's mechanical arm transformed into a large cannon and aimed at the Mutation Source.

The Mutation Source looked at Han Xiao and said, "Is it really impossible for you to let me go?"

Han Xiao shook his head, and his cannon accumulated strength.

"Am I going to die? Just what is death like?"

The Mutation Source knew that its life was about to come to an end and could not help but think about the time when it was just born. It did not have any sensory organs and could not observe the outside world. The entire world was in a state of darkness, and it was like primal chaos. Would death be just like when it was born?

For some reason, the Mutation Source suddenly thought about the time when it first awakened its ability to control sensory organs. At that time, it had only been able to share the view of infected individuals. It could remember the many smiling faces all around, but those smiling faces seemed to have decreased over time.

At the very end of its life, its fear disappeared completely, and the Mutation Source transformed its face into the smiling face in its memory. "Thank you for telling me all that... Thank you for accompanying me in a conversation..."

The Mutation Source was actually extremely pure and was like a blank sheet of paper. Han Xiao also knew this.

Boom!

His cannon was shot, and the Mutation Source was reduced to dust.

Retracting his cannon, Han Xiao let out a sigh, and his mechanical suit transformed back into a compressed orb.

"I'm sorry. I understand you, but I'm your enemy."

Keeping his protective shield, Han Xiao looked around him.

The beasts had all regained their clarity, and fear could be seen in their eyes. The herd of beasts immediately scattered in all directions and only left behind a ground littered with corpses.

The rain was still pouring, and it got heavier and heavier.

Chapter 563: Feidin, Son of Luck

Hu!

The Godoran spaceship landed, and Nagakin walked up to Han Xiao.

"How's the situation? Did you take care of the Mutation Source?" Nagakin asked anxiously.

"I got rid of it," Han Xiao replied casually while his mechanical suit was retracting.

"New command, begin to collapse the Mechanical Beast Guards Army."

The next moment, the few thousand mechanical beasts transformed back into their compressed orbs and rolled over to Han Xiao's side through an electromagnetic force.

Han Xiao then shot out a compressed orb, which transformed into a long dark red metal box that was about two meters tall. All of the compressed orbs then rolled into the box and filled it up. Following which, the box shut itself automatically, and an engraved '001' could be seen on the box.

The box was a 'mobile army camp', which was a necessity for those who pursued the Army Style. Different Mechanical Armies would be placed in the different army boxes, and each army box represented an army.

The serial number of the Mechanical Beast Guards Army was 001 as it was the first complete army that Han Xiao had constructed. An army box contained the compressed orbs of a single army, and the lock of the box was made from a powerful electromagnet together with the control of an AI. It was difficult to open it through any other means, and only Han Xiao was able to control it.

When the box was completely filled with compressed orbs, the box would not be able to be compressed into a compressed orb. While it would not be convenient to bring the box around, it was not too troublesome to use it. With Phillip controlling the box and the high-speed module being attached to it, Han Xiao did not have to carry the box around with him. With a single command, the army box would quickly be transported to the battlefield.

The bottom of the army box began spitting out flames, and it rapidly ascended into the sky. A door on the belly of the BlackLight Stealth opened up, and the army box was swallowed up. There was a simple maintenance room in the spaceship, and it could calculate the losses and damage to the machines. With the opponents being beasts that were far beneath Han Xiao's strength, the losses were negligible.

The beasts were escaping in all directions, and the battle was already over. Nagakin ordered his subordinates to clean up the battlefield while he took out his detector and confirmed that the Mutation Source had disappeared completely.

"That's great. I shall inform the upper echelons immediately that the antidote is successful!" Nagakin was overjoyed.

At that moment, the mercenary group's spaceships also arrived, and Herlous appeared together with the rest. Han Xiao instructed them to clean up the battlefield and bring back the beast carcasses. Those carcasses were precious materials, and Emerald Grass could use them to create Genetic Medicine. While it was not of much use to him, Han Xiao would be able to earn a small fortune by selling it to the players.

Jupiter and the others did not manage to snatch the last hit and had even died once or twice instead. All of their faces were depressed as they stood nearby.

However, the other players were all extremely excited on the forums.

Right when Black Star killed the Mutation Source, the progress meter of the Main Storyline Mission on their interface had shot up, and a Mission Complete notification had popped up on their interfaces.

All the players of Planet Aquamarine received a bountiful reward from the Main Storyline Mission. While their reward differed according to their contributions, the reward that they received on average was far more than a side mission.

However, what excited the players the most was not the reward of the mission. With the Main Storyline Mission of Planet Aquamarine completed, this meant that it was time for them to enter the Galaxy!

After spending so much time on Planet Aquamarine, the only thing that could attract them now was the galaxy. In the past, they could only watch Bun-Hit-Dog's videos to understand the galaxy, but they could personally experience it now. With the [Mutation Disaster] mission behind them, many players looked forward to the future plot and were all extremely excited.

In contrast, it was a completely different sight with the citizens of Planet Aquamarine.

Ten minutes after the end of the battle, the Sanctuary and Six Nations received news from Godora that the Mutation Source had been destroyed. Without any delay, they immediately announced this piece of news to the entire planet. All the refugees sitting in front of a television or radio received the news.

In the cities of the Six Nations and Black Phantom Sanctuary, countless individuals revealed looks of disbelief. Their faces became agitated before they began shedding tears of joy.

They had survived the calamity!

They were still alive!

The entire planet erupted into cheers!

All the cities were drowned in the joy of surviving the calamity. Some of them cried out at the top of their lungs, some danced on the streets, while others bawled with tears of joy.

The cheers of the people formed a huge wave, rushing into the sky, echoing in the horizon.

They could finally see the light at the end of the tunnel. Thinking about the calamity that their planet had faced, it had been akin to a living hell. Everything was finally over.

The citizens of Planet Aquamarine could not help but burn with hope for their future.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations and Bennett worked together and announced that Black Star was the one who had killed the Mutation Source. They tried to create the image that Black Star was the noble savior of the entire planet.

With the citizens of the planet being overwhelmed with joy, the effects of the advertisement were extremely obvious. Almost all of the refugees were filled with gratitude to Black Star.

With the calamity over, the Six Nations had to begin thinking about their future. They would still maintain their respect to Godora on the surface but had already accepted Black Star's conditions in secret. They decided to stake it all on Han Xiao.

Han Xiao, who was still on the battlefield, naturally was not aware of the situation. While the others were cleaning up the battlefield, he walked to the side and opened up his interface.

_____________________

[Destroy the Source] has been completed!

Mission Rating: Perfect

_____________________

Killing the Mutation Source had allowed him to get the [Perfect] rating.

Han Xiao received 2,400,000 experience points, and the high rating allowed him to draw a Random Reward. Furthermore, the bonus reward gave him another chance to draw a Random Reward, making it a total of two chances. Apart from that, Han Xiao also gained a few Legendary Points.

_____________________

Planet Legendary Points (Planet Aquamarine): You put an end to the Mutation. The Mutation Source brought a calamity to Planet Aquamarine. It ruined the order of the planet and caused countless civilians to lose their lives. You killed the source that caused hatred and pain in abundance. You chased away the calamity and brought light to the planet. You saved the planet!

_____________________

Han Xiao's current mission reward limit was extremely high, and the effect of a single Legendary Point was extremely obvious.

After taking a look at the mission reward, Han Xiao directed his attention to the first kill reward, which allowed him to draw two of the Mutation Source's abilities. This was the greatest reward to him.

Han Xiao did not take action immediately. He first looked around and found Feidin. Without even asking for permission, he touched Feidin to his heart's content.

"Yes, I can feel the effect of luck."

Han Xiao rubbed his palms in excitement and began to draw his reward under Feidin's helpless gaze.

_____________________

You have received the opportunity to draw two of the half-mature Mutation Source's abilities.

Note: The Mutation Source is a special life form, and you are unable to draw its innate abilities. The abilities that you can draw will be adjusted accordingly.

_____________________

The abilities are adjusted indeed, Han Xiao thought to himself.

This was a common occurrence when drawing abilities. If the target was too special, some abilities would not be replicated. For example, shapeshifting, sensory organs, and emotional control were all innate abilities of the Mutation Source.

It was just like if a human player wanted to draw for the abilities of a demon. Even if a demon had a tail whip ability, a player would not draw such an ability since they did not have a tail. The hardware just was not compatible with such an ability.

When two species were too different, even if the abilities could be extracted, there would be a change in the effects. All the race specific elements would be removed, and it would be changed into a more general skill. For example, the tail whip attack of a demon might be changed into something like a heavy kick attack. It definitely would not be changed into an attack that made use of whips.

_____________________

Randomizing... Draw complete.

Please select two of the five reward:

[Harden] Skill: +65% Physical Resistance, -30% DEX. Stamina Usage: 300, Duration: 14 seconds, Cooldown: 30 seconds.

[Middle Grade Cell Proliferation Control] Talent: Make use of energy to proliferate cells, heal wounds, and convert energy into HP at the ratio of 1:5. Recovery rate capped at 28% of total HP per second.

[Grinder] Skill: Close combat skill. Make use of grips and locks to deal damage. Capable of causing damage eight times, and 40 to 60% of the damage will ignore the enemy's defense. Has a chance of causing status inflictions such as [Fracture], [Numbness], and so on. Energy Usage: 60, Stamina Usage: 140, Cooldown: 15 seconds.

[Energy Storage] Skill: Obtain an extra energy bar that is 25% of total energy. When exhausting the extra energy bar, it won't affect one's own energy bonus. Duration: 2 days, Cooldown: 3 days. (Additional energy obtained won't count toward the energy level.)

[Energy Absorption] Talent: When subject to any physical, energy, magical, or other attacks, 60% of the damage offset by resistance will be converted into energy.

_____________________

After adjustments, the effects of the skills and talents could be stronger or weaker. The cell proliferation and energy absorption talents of the Mutation Source had been weakened after removing the special effects of the Mutation Source.

However, the appearance of those two talents was a huge surprise for Han Xiao.

The way he saw it, those two talents were the most valuable abilities of the Mutation Source. If he could obtain a single one of them, it would be considered pretty good. However, if he could obtain both together, it would be a perfect combination!

Simply put, he would be able to regain energy by being hit, and using energy would be able to recover HP. While the regeneration rate would not be as perverse as that of the Mutation Source, he had the natural advantage of having high HP! With his HP being 38,000, even a mere 28% of his HP was a huge figure. The amount of HP that he would regain was twice that of the Mutation Source!

While the other three skills were not bad, he did not even remotely consider them after seeing the other two.

Even if the two talents were weaker, they were only weaker when compared to the original. Neither of the two talents could be considered weak, and they had both reached the level of a Molding Ability. Han Xiao could not have been happier.

He had originally thought that getting one of the two talents would be a huge win and had mentally prepared himself for being unable to get even one. Who would have thought that he would actually be so lucky! Was touching Feidin really that effective?

Han Xiao could not help but look at Feidin with a burning gaze. He had the sudden urge to extract a few hundred bottles of Ability Potions from Feidin, and both Feidin and Chen Xing could not help but tremble.

Retracting his gaze, Han Xiao made his choice without any hesitation.

_____________________

You have received [Middle Grade Cell Proliferation Control] talent!

You have received [Energy Absorption] talent!

Chapter 564: The Beginning of the Storm

The sensation of itchiness and soreness as though vines were growing spread rapidly and twisted around his limbs. It felt like there were numerous insects crawling through every inch of his flesh and bones. Han Xiao's ears seemed to be surrounded by the roaring of waves and thunder, and he could feel every cell in his body becoming active, undergoing an extraordinary change. His vision of the world was constantly shaking and blurring.

Every time he managed to obtain a strong talent, genetic mutations would occur in his body. The pain was difficult to endure, causing Han Xiao's face to change as he quickly fled into the BlackLight Stealth. Once he was out of everyone's sight, he found a practice room before sealing the door. The moment he did so, a stronger and more intense pain burst out from within his body, as though he was a wet towel that was being rung dry by a huge pair of hands.

Past experience had told him that, the greater the pain, the greater the resulting change. The pain that he was experiencing this time could be compared to when he underwent his Race Evolution to a Void Prowler. After all, the two new talents were the specialties of the Mutation Source, and not only did it bring him new abilities, it was a complete remolding of his life.

Han Xiao gritted his teeth, feeling the reorganization of his cells. He gradually discovered that he had obtained a newfound sense of control that could actively trigger cell division.

As the pain started to subside, he could feel that his body had totally changed. Through his perception, the cell membrane of each cell seemed to have become tougher but had a sponge-like texture. The internal microstructure also seemed to have changed to produce new functions.

He rubbed his thigh, carefully observing, and found out that a portion of the external impact would not be resisted and absorbed by his skin. The kinetic force would permeate into his musculoskeletal system and be converted by his cells into energy.

Bringing a knife to his arm, he drew out a thin line of blood. Han Xiao recalled the sense of control, urging his cells into action. The energy from his cells rapidly repaired the damaged cells around the wound, and the wound disappeared in the blink of an eye.

Wiping the sweat off his forehead, Han Xiao grinned.

This is indeed a strong specialized talent. My level of being rose another tier once again, and my flesh has become more solid.

With the two new talents on his interface, he possessed four Molding Abilities.

Han Xiao was in a jovial mood, but he suddenly noticed a problem, causing the corners of his mouth to twitch.

Oi, out of my four talents, three of them specialize in tankiness. One increases my HP, the other gives me damage immunity, and the last one speeds up recovery!

Han Xiao felt he was a huge iron pillar at this moment, his body being more durable than a machine. If he measured his progress on the path of a Main Tank, he would probably be a galloping warhorse.

The biggest weakness of the Army Style is that the users are normally afraid of their defenses being broken through and their commander being felled...

Han Xiao sniggered inwardly. With his heaven-defying tenacity, there was no one who would return alive after trying to assassinate him.

Increased tankiness was a good thing, but Han Xiao favored the skill [Energy Absorption] more. His Mechanical Army required him to use energy, and with the amount of energy used, it would accumulate to become a terrifying amount. However, now he could constantly recover his energy value, meaning his Mechanical Force bonus could be given out easily!

The most important part was, the higher his level, the greater his damage resistance, which meant that it would constantly rise along with him and not become obsolete. Thinking outside of the box, even if the enemy could not reach him, he could easily just ask one of his mechanical beasts to attack himself to absorb energy...

What was with that? This made him into a f*cking generator!

With Super stamina, he would never feel fatigue. Even if he did it consecutively for three days and nights, he would not feel any soreness in his lower body. He had truly turned into a Boss level character who had no fear of a depleted energy bar. Just thinking about this gave him a feeling of absolute power.

Just who can kill me‽

Han Xiao suddenly snapped out of his reverie, hurriedly knocking between his brows twice and restraining his arrogant and haughty outburst.

That was close. I almost went out of character.

While this Moulding Ability is on the level of a bug, there is an upper limit to the energy that it can provide. It's far lower than the amount of HP I have. Even with a five-times conversion rate, it can only recover probably a third of my total HP. The rate of recovery is too limited.

Furthermore, I can only absorb 60% of the damage that is resisted, so if I encounter opponents at the same level or higher with strong attacking power, I will lose HP proportionally to the amount of energy obtained. After all, my resistance is not as perverted as the Mutation Source's.

Han Xiao pondered for a while before coming to a conclusion. Unless it was a high-level Super with a Boss level template, while his Grade still remained at B+, it was almost impossible for a Calamity Grade Super to kill him. The longer the battle dragged on, the more advantageous it would be to him. Even the highly explosive and piercing combo used by Nagakin to defeat Anur could probably be shrugged off by him.

F*ck, can I still be considered a Mechanic now?

Han Xiao could not help feeling disgusted.

Shaking his head, he opened the mission panel. He had a different mission from the rest, with the [Mutation Disaster] storyline of his still showing that it was incomplete.

The mission requirements for the players were only relevant to Planet Aquamarine. However, Han Xiao's included all the planets affected by the mutation source. His condition to prevent failure was to ensure that one planet had been saved, and he had already fulfilled it.

However, the disasters on the other planets had not yet been resolved, so his mission had not ended, unlike the Planet Aquamarine players.

In my past life, after this matter subsided, Godora created a corresponding dungeon. When I complete the Main Storyline, I'll probably be able to get my hands on the rights to the dungeon.

While his main purpose was still within Planet Aquamarine, he had to display the proper conduct and put in some effort toward the other planets affected by the disaster. His own accumulations were an astronomical number that players could not even imagine, and even he himself could not guess how many rewards he would obtain after it ended.

After claiming all the rewards for this mission, Han Xiao went to the captain's room, overlooking the battlefield. The place was almost completely cleaned up, with Herlous and the others transporting all the beast corpses into the spaceship. The few hundred players also entered the spaceship. Previously, in order to search for the Mutation Source, they had dispatched players all over Planet Aquamarine, and they had to collect them one by one. However, this was a job for others; it was not his concern.

Having packed up, the group of spaceships proceeded to return to the base, with the BlackLight Stealth leading in front. They maintain a relaxed speed; after all, things had already been settled, and they had no need to rush... although Herlous and all of Han Xiao's officers were a little salty about this incident.

On the spaceship, Han Xiao did not relax but rather began to extrapolate the matters in the near future as he sank into deep thought.

Now that the Mutation Disaster of Planet Aquamarine had come to an end, according to the game plan, this signified the end of the Main Storyline. This was the time when the players would officially enter the interstellar region, becoming members of Black Star and stepping onto the true stage!

The players were the best force to allow his influence to quickly grow!

The Great Mechanic Han had always placed a lot of importance on players. His recruitment campaign had lasted for a good few months, leaving a strong impression in the eyes of the players as an interstellar guide. There was only one more step to go before his entire plan would come into fruition.

The agreement made between the Six Nations would also have to be taken care of. After all, this place was his 'hometown'. Then, the problem of Planet Aquamarine could be shelved.

The only problem remaining is that of DarkStar.

Han Xiao's eyes gleamed.

Since he had made such a dramatic change to the initial storyline, causing the early destruction of the core of DarkStar's plan, it would result in them not being able to proceed with their actions like in the past.

As such, watching the reaction of DarkStar would be more important. Would they forsake the plan, or would they change their strategy?

Han Xiao was also uncertain. If it was the latter, then he could only react to their moves. He had steeled himself for this; this was the butterfly effect caused by his extreme changing of the plot.

I'm not sure if DarkStar's next move will be the same as in my previous life anymore...

Rubbing his chest, Han Xiao fell into deep thought.

...

On one of the DarkStar motherships, many of the DarkStar upper echelons gathered, all of them staring at the translucent screen on the wall as the feedback of the Mutation Source being destroyed was transmitted to them for the fourth time. The silence in the meeting room was palpable.

The worst-case scenario had happened.

No matter how shocked the upper echelons were, they could not believe that in the short span of a few months, Godora had actually found a way to eradicate this Mutation Disaster.

"Now... what do we do?" Someone broke the deathly silence.

Everyone turned to stare at Degulish at once.

The person in question opened his mouth, his expression gloomy. However, he paused before finally speaking with much difficulty.

"Let's inform the leader."

He was the commander-in-charge of this plan, but now that it was falling apart, the severity of the situation ought to be raised with the leader.

The communication channel was quickly connected, and DarkStar's leader appeared in the vacant main seat, surveying the crowd.

"I'm not in the Hyde Star System. If it's nothing important, don't disturb me... eh? All your expressions look nasty. What happened?"

Degulish gritted his teeth before explaining the entire situation. His face was extremely ugly to behold as he felt that he had completely betrayed the trust bestowed upon him by the leader.

"This is... unexpected." The leader's expression twitched a little, and he fell silent for a while before continuing. "There's something fishy about this. I'm quite certain of the scientific research ability of Godora. While their magic arts are quite advanced, their technological ability falls quite short. They must have obtained some sort of external help."

"Are you saying..." Degulish seemed to have obtained some clues.

"Yes, your deductions are correct. The thing that disappeared contained the sample of the Mutation Source. Our intelligence network has shown that the Secret Message Bead fell into Godora's hands, but the goods inside had already disappeared. The greatest possibility is that it had been taken away by the Holy Stone Civilization, but... there's another possibility."

At this point, Ember, who had been completely silent, suddenly spoke with his eyes gleaming. "Floating Dragon."

He was the member who had been tasked with searching for the lost goods, so he understood this part the clearest.

"A mysterious man was mentioned in the report of Ember. When he was looking for the Secret Message Bead, there was once a person who used the name of DarkStar to inquire about the whereabouts of the Secret Message Bead. However, in the end, Floating Dragon was the one who found the Secret Message Bead. It was handed over to Holy Stone... then here comes the question, did the mysterious man not manage to find the Secret Message Bead, or did he take the contents, leaving only the shell?"

All the upper echelons in the room quietly listened. This was originally an unsolved case, but the leader seemed to have managed to obtain some clues, and this attracted the attention of everyone present, including Ember.

"The research results of Godora must be related to the missing sample of the Mutation Source." The tone of the DarkStar leader remained calm. "For Godora to solve the problem faced by Planet Aquamarine first, where a member of the Floating Dragon was also situated... there's no need for more evidence; the situation is clear."

Degulish burst into anger. "To think it was Floating Dragon! So, the whole process of passing it over to Holy Stone was a huge sham! Why did Floating Dragon want to target us? Wait, could it have been Black Star‽"

Everyone present received a huge shock, turning to Ember with an expression of shock and surprise.

They still remembered how, after the incident on Noriosse, Ember had insisted on paying whatever price possible to eliminate Black Star. However, not only did they ignore him, they had even scorned at him. To think that... Ember's intuition had been right!

"To think that all of you still remember the suggestion that I raised." A hint of schadenfreude passed through Ember's eyes as he coldly spoke. "To only awaken and realize it now, isn't it too late‽"

The expressions of everyone in the room changed, with no one daring to look Ember in the eye.

"At that time, we had no clues, and even if I was given another chance, I would still have made the same decision." The leader sighed. "What's done is done; now, the most crucial point is not Black Star but rather how to salvage our plan."

Everyone sat up straight. While they regretted not taking Black Star seriously from the start, their issues were now pressing, and no one had the time to waste on hindsight.

The leader solemnly looked at all the upper echelons, suddenly relaxing his tone. "There's no need to pull a long face. The situation is not as bad as expected."

"Ah?" Degulish and the rest were stunned.

The entire plan is about to collapse—how is that not bad‽

"While there were some hiccups, stopping the plan from being successfully carried forward, the main objective has still been achieved, has it not? Godora has been thrown into turmoil and up in a disadvantageous position. Even if we stop our plan now and hastily retreat, the cracks between the purebloods and hybrids will never vanish."

The eyes of everyone present gleamed. That was right; they were caught in a misunderstanding. Even if Godora managed to solve this Mutation Disaster and regained some control, the damage caused by this storm would take years to eliminate. Stopping the plan now was nothing more than reducing the damage that Godora had to clear up. What loss did they have?

"Then, do we still stop all our operations and go on standby?" Degulish asked.

"Why should we?" The leader shook his head. "Since it has already reached this point, let's just allow the mistakes to continue. Before stopping the operation, we shall hit Godora hard one last time. Since it is no longer possible to drag the time out for the Mutation Disaster, have the infiltration teams actively feed the Mutation Source. Push all of them to the maturity phase and deceive them into attempting to destroy the planet. This way, it will make the low-level civilizations attached to Godora to suffer greatly, causing Godora to waste more energy helping them.

"The moment that the Mutation Disaster is resolved, do you still think that the Godoran troops will still stay on the calamity planets? No! They will leave sooner or later, and that's when we send out our soldiers, destroying those low-level civilizations.

"We shall see if Godora plans to save them or not. If they do not, it would defeat the purpose of them trying to resolve the Mutation Disaster. However, if they choose to offer aid, Godora will be leashed to those low-level civilizations. How is that different from having the Mutation Disasters?

"They will be stuck between a rock and a hard place!

''Planet Aquamarine was the first to be saved from the Mutation Disaster. Before long, the Godoran troops will leave, and we can take the chance to attack the planet. Since we now know Black Star's crimes and the Dragon Emperor is not on Planet Aquamarine, we can take the chance to eliminate him. I said before that we'd make him pay for this sooner or later. This time, I don't want there to be any accidents."

Ember viciously stood up, hatred visible on his face as he exclaimed, "My pleasure!"

Degulish narrowed his eyes and added in a sinister tone, "Humph. He must be killed. I'll go and let Floating Dragon know that we're not to be trifled with."

"Then I'll tag along for the fun of it. The last time, Ember and Anur failed. If we add me, there will be three people, which is safer," a petite upper echelon added. This person was a senior combatant of DarkStar and also a Calamity Grade Super.

For a long time, their total members had been falling. Some members had been arrested and sent to the Rainbow Prison, causing DarkStar to be left with just five Calamity Grade Supers. Sending three of them already made it more than half, almost pulling out all of their resources.

The crowd seemed to have found their backbone once again and calmed down. The thought process of the leader was clear and precise. It was originally meant to be a protracted war, but since it was no longer feasible, they just had to change it to ensure the maximum losses for Godora in the short term.

Want to compete with us? Black Star, you're too young for that!

At this point, the leader suddenly interrupted them.

"This matter is not that important though; our next immediate objective should be to attack Planet Golden Gate."

Degulish lurched in shock. "That operation is to be continued as well?"

"Yeah, why not? We've already made the preparations and can attack in the next two days. Godora only managed to solve the Mutation Disaster for one planet—do you think it will have any impact on our attack?

"This is instead a good chance as they will definitely take the chance to spread the news of having resolved the disaster for the planets. In order to eliminate the contradictions within the country, won't it be good to take this chance to simply destroy Planet Golden Gate?"

Degulish's eyes lit up at this proposal.

Chapter 565: Unexpected Reinforcements

Two days soon passed.

As a Grade A colony planet, Planet Golden Gate had a large fleet stationed around it all year round. After the Long Arc incident, the alert status of the planet had risen, and the troops stationed on Planet Golden Gate often patrolled the vicinity.

According to their regulations, there were four layers to their reconnaissance range. The outermost range was a radar that scanned for energy signals. The second layer was a sentry spaceship patrolling far away. Those two layers were extremely far away from Planet Golden Gate, and if they detected an enemy attack, the main force would have sufficient time to prepare.

D-3018 sentry spaceship was patrolling in the outer region, and the members of the radar monitoring team stared at the screen unblinkingly as they analyzed and dealt with the data of the region. Occasionally, there would be a spaceship flying past the region, and the radar monitoring team would be on edge.

The job of monitoring the radar was an extremely taxing one, and thus, the members of the team worked shifts. Even so, repeatedly doing the same monotonous task made it difficult for the entire team to raise their spirits. Furthermore, the regulations prohibited them from chatting during a period of high alert.

The entire room was filled with silence, and only the humming sound from the machinery could be heard.

Right at that moment, bright red words were suddenly plastered all over the screen, and a screeching alarm went off. All the members in the team were startled and almost fell off their chairs.

"Alert! Alert! CR-20849 detected a large-scale spatial disruption!"

"Alert! Lost connection with CR-20489!"

The attention of the radar monitoring team was immediately drawn over, and they immediately checked the last few photos that CR-20489 had sent over before losing connection.

On the radar screen, densely packed spots of light could be seen with every single spot of light representing the energy reaction of a battleship. The spots of light were so densely packed that they could light up an entire region of the radar screen. With just a single glance, it was impossible to tell the number of battleships that had appeared.

This gigantic fleet was currently heading their way!

The faces of the entire team changed color.

The radar monitoring team blanked out with their limbs turning cold and lips trembling.

"Enemy... enemy attack!"

"Quickly, send a report!"

"Leave this region quickly!"

A thick beam of light suddenly shot toward D-3018 sentry spaceship from afar. This was the main cannon of the DarkStar mothership. It had a long attack range and was extremely powerful. It made use of a single high-energy reactor as its ammunition.

The protective shield of the sentry spaceship was instantly torn apart, and the light beam struck the sentry spaceship. The entire spaceship exploded into a ball of light and was reduced to floating space trash.

Very quickly, a gigantic fleet appeared and majestically floated past the wreckage of the sentry spaceship. The gigantic DarkStar mothership was surrounded by a huge fleet of spaceships. There were thousands of spaceships in the entire fleet, and the DarkStar spaceships were like ants protecting their queen with the DarkStar mothership being like a moving fortress.

The same scene was taking place in four different places.

DarkStar had sent out a total of five motherships in order to attack Planet Golden Gate!

In one of the DarkStar motherships, Degulish looked at the radar screen before him and said, "Godora's reconnaissance range is pretty good. When we arrive at Planet Golden Gate, the fleet stationed there will have gotten into formation. It is a pity that we weren't able to ambush them successfully."

However, he had not thought that the ambush would be successful. Godora was already on high alert, so it would not be so easy to ambush them again. Besides, they had sent out half of their organization's troops this time, so it would not make a difference if they failed to ambush Godora.

Not too long later, Planet Golden Gate appeared in their sights, and the other four DarkStar motherships also appeared near Planet Golden Gate. Godora had tightened its defensive formation and opened up a few dozen golden Weiss Magical Protective Shields. The Godoran fleet guarding the planet was only a fourth or fifth the size of the DarkStar fleet. It was as though they were surrounded by wolves.

Five DarkStar motherships were surrounding Planet Golden Gate from five different directions.

Every mothership had a commander, and the overall commander of the attack was Degulish.

"Attack!" Degulish commanded, not wasting any time talking to Godora.

The battle erupted!

There was no sound in the vacuum of space, and numerous light beams, homing missiles, and laser cannons lit up the dark space in a beautiful light display. The attacks continued wave after wave, and before the previous wave of attacks ended, a new wave of attacks started. Endless waves of explosions could be seen outside the atmosphere of Planet Golden Gate.

The dozens of protective shields vibrated violently, looking as though they would shatter at any moment.

Godora's fleet had adopted a defensive stance and tried their best to sustain the protective shields.

"Don't even dream of stalling for time to wait for reinforcements," Degulish sneered.

DarkStar had come extremely well prepared, and before taking action, they had already collected intelligence on the troops stationed on Planet Golden Gate. While Planet Golden Gate was a Grade A colony planet that had a large fleet stationed all year round, it was insignificant in the face of the troops that DarkStar had sent out. DarkStar could crush Godora in terms of numbers, and the battleships of both parties were extremely similar in terms of strength.

On the other side, DarkStar had also paid attention to the movement of Godora's fleet on the other planets. However, the troops guarding the other planets showed no signs of movement. Thus, even if Godora wanted to seek reinforcements from Juberly Hub, the reinforcements would take some time to arrive. As long as DarkStar unleashed all of their firepower without restraint, they would definitely be able to break through the defenses of Planet Golden Gate before the reinforcements arrived.

"Continue attacking, don't stop," Degulish said coldly.

With the numerical advantage, he was not planning to start a ground battle. He only planned to destroy everything with absolute firepower. The objective of their mission this time was not a massacre but to bathe Planet Golden Gate with cannon fire. They wanted to flatten the entire planet and destroy all the structures on the planet. They intended to completely destroy the entire colony planet.

At the same time, Planet Golden Gate fell into complete chaos because of this sudden assault. Countless individuals flooded the dock and wanted to escape in their spaceships. However, the army stationed at the dock received news from their superiors to lock down the dock and prevent any civilian spaceships from taking off.

This action had immediately enraged the populace, and a huge conflict had broken out in the dock. The entire situation was extremely chaotic, and everyone wanted to escape from the planet but was blocked by the army.

"What right do you have to prevent us from leaving!"

"A war is happening up there—do you guys want us to die with you‽"

"It's my right to choose to leave this planet!"

The soldiers guarding the dock remained unperturbed and had stern expressions on their faces. In truth, they were also extremely afraid of DarkStar wiping out the fleet guarding the planet. If that happened, they would also die. However, they had been through strict training and knew to calm themselves down in times of fear and carry out orders strictly.

The order from their superior was to prevent anyone from leaving the planet. First, the entire planet was being bombarded with cannon fire, and the civilian spaceships would definitely be destroyed the moment they left the protective shield. Second, the civilian spaceships might end up creating chaos in the battlefield. If those spaceships crashed into the Godoran fleet, it was very likely to set off a chain reaction that would spell their immediate defeat. Furthermore, there might be DarkStar spies hidden among the civilians who were planning on destroying Godora's defenses from within. Thus, while it was a little too much to forbid the civilians on Planet Golden Gate from escaping, it was necessary to do so. Only when the protective shield was about to break would they escape together with the civilians.

Being unable to break through the lockdown of the army, many people collapsed to the ground with fear plastered all over their faces. Many of them greatly regretted not escaping the planet like the others and taking refuge in the universe.

The media outlets on Planet Golden Gate also made use of their observatory equipment to broadcast the battle outside the atmosphere to the entire Star System. The news anchor trembled and suppressed the fear in his heart as he reported the situation on the planet.

The local news was quickly spread into the galaxy, and many news channels broadcast the situation on Planet Golden Gate. After the Long Arc incident, DarkStar had once again stretched out their demonic claws to another planet. The attention of many in the Shattered Star Ring was drawn to this event.

Godora had just announced that they had developed a working antidote for the Mutation Disaster, but this assault had brought a new wave of fear to Godora.

The situation outside the planet was extremely tense, and the fleet stationed on Planet Golden Gate had already lost more than two hundred battleships and more than ten Weiss Magical Protective Shields. The protective shield surrounding the planet seemed to be on the verge of collapse, and a portion of the attacks could already pass through the cracks in the protective shields.

Many cities had activated their own protective shields and did not suffer much damage. However, once the fleet protecting the planet fell, the protective shield of the cities would not be able to last for long. A series of cannons had also revealed itself from the ground and aimed toward the sky. Their missile systems had also been activated, and the atmosphere was extremely tense.

The moment that the DarkStar fleet broke through the atmosphere, Planet Golden Gate could only put up their final defense. However, if even the fleet guarding the planet was destroyed, these defensive structures would only be enough to tickle DarkStar.

"Increase firepower. They can't hold us back anymore," Degulish sneered as he observed the situation on the battlefield.

Right at that moment, a screeching alarm went off in the mothership.

"Alert! A large unknown energy source is approaching! The numbers are unknown!"

Before Degulish could even react, the light of battleships exiting from hyperdrive flashed around the edge of the battlefield. Plenty of battleships of all shapes and sizes began appearing on the battlefield and formed a gigantic alliance fleet. They were obviously not there to help DarkStar.

All of those battleships were painted with logos, and more than ten different logos could be seen on all the battleships.

"Sky Ring Army, Purple Gold Army, Blades Army... these are all the large Mercenary Groups in the region!"

Degulish was dumbfounded.

Wait a moment! Why have these mercenaries appeared all of a sudden? Where did they come from‽

Not just him, the leaders of the other organizations who were viewing the broadcast had also revealed looks of shock.

Did Godora actually prepare an ambush‽

In the flagship of the Sky Ring Army, the leader of the Sky Ring Army, Gureja, had just ended his conversation with the director-general of Godora's War Bureau. He then looked in the direction of Planet Golden Gate and stroked his needle-like beard while chuckling.

"Ha, Black Star has truly introduced me to a big job."

Chapter 566: Your Mothership Isn't Bad. It's Now Mine.

Two days ago, when the Mutation Disaster had been declared over, the citizens of Planet Aquamarine had been overjoyed. In the past half a year, the law and order of the planet had constantly been eroded by the calamity, and it had been a living hell. However, the tough times were over, and the refugees had the courage to start life all over again. In fact, all of them had a far stronger will than before.

They needed some time to recover from the losses suffered in the Mutation Disaster, and the refugees needed to adapt to their new living conditions. The Six Nations and the Sanctuary had plenty of things to be done. The majority of the refugees sheltered by the Sanctuary and the Six Nations had chosen to stay behind. With the Mutation Disaster over, the next thing they had to consider was development.

Bennett had been in discussion with his aides and advisors over the past few days, and they were preparing to expand the Sanctuary. They were going to officially change the Sanctuary into a regime and expand their territory. A city would be built, and the refugees taking shelter in the Sanctuary would become their citizens.

The changes of the Sanctuary had a profound meaning. This was the development of the Planet Aquamarine civilization. If they continued developing at their current pace, Planet Aquamarine would only be able to come into contact with the galaxy many years later. However, with the anomaly that was Han Xiao, that was no longer the case.

A short two days went by, and Planet Aquamarine was taking their first step toward recovery. Han Xiao did not pay attention to them.

Han Xiao's attention was completely focused on the recruitment of players. After the Main Storyline Mission of Version 2.0 was completed, the key part to the next step of his plan would be to lead the players into the galaxy en masse.

Part of the reason for Han Xiao ending the Mutation Disaster at an earlier time was so that the players could enter the galaxy earlier and work for the benefit of his Black Star Mercenary Group.

Currently, all of his plans were set, and he was only lacking that final push. As long as he announced the time of departure to all the players and made them feel that they had a mission on their shoulders, their sense of belonging to the mercenary group would definitely increase.

Following which, he only needed to gather all the players and head toward the galaxy. At that time, his goal would be accomplished.

Currently, there were about three to four hundred thousand players in the Black Star Mercenary Group, and Han Xiao did not intend to recruit all the remaining players in a single breath. It was still important for him to maintain a certain benchmark. If not, the players who got in through a selection would not feel too good. Thus, Han Xiao did not plan to take all the players along with him at once.

Instead, Han Xiao would leave behind a path for them to follow him. The Black Star Second Base was stationed on Planet Aquamarine, and he was prepared to leave some mercenaries, machinery, and transport spaceships behind. The remaining players would only be able to join the Black Star Mercenary Group after passing the selection and would be sent to the first base after that.

Han Xiao wanted to set up a tradition and let the players get used to the long-term recruitment. Joining the Black Star Mercenary Group was currently the easiest way for the players to enter the galaxy, and players would naturally scramble for the chance. All the future players who started off on Planet Aquamarine would be the same. In fact, not just the players, even the natives of Planet Aquamarine were included in Han Xiao's plans.

He was leaving behind a bridge to connect Planet Aquamarine to the galaxy. It was just like planting crops. It was important to consider the long-term sustainability of the crops. It was not enough to harvest the crops only once.

All of that was considered in his plans. After the completion of the Main Storyline Mission, Han Xiao did not immediately set his plan into motion but gave the players some time.

He was also prepared to rest for a few days.

However, news of DarkStar attacking Planet Golden Gate had ruined his rest.

In the workshop of the Black Star Second Base, Han Xiao stopped repairing his Mechanical Beast Guards Army, and his eyes were glued to the screen of his communicator. The galactic news was being broadcast at the moment. Just when Planet Golden Gate was in a precarious situation, more than a dozen large mercenary groups rushed over as reinforcements. The originally one-sided battle suddenly became an evenly matched one, and both parties began to engage in an intense war.

"The ambush on Planet Golden Gate really happened. It seems like resolving the Mutation Disaster crisis early did not affect DarkStar's plans. They did not give up on the ambush." Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief. Thankfully, his guess had not been wrong.

With the experience of his previous life, Han Xiao knew of DarkStar's plans. However, he was not sure of the exact timeline of their plan; he only knew the sequence of their plans.

The ambush on Planet Golden Gate was a key event in the storyline, and Han Xiao had not been certain that DarkStar would carry out the same plan as in his previous life. But after a series of careful analysis, he had felt that the attack on Planet Golden Gate was a key part of DarkStar's strategy, and it would not be changed.

A month ago, when Han Xiao provided a sample of the Mutation Source, Han Xiao did not hide what he knew about DarkStar's plans and raised it with Godora's War Bureau as an opinion. He said that this was something that he found out from analysis and prediction. With his knowledge of DarkStar in his previous life, Han Xiao's argument was extremely convincing.

Because of the sample that he had provided and Han Xiao's close ties with Godora, the War Bureau decided to take a gamble and formed a trap based on this intelligence.

Ever since the outbreak of the Mutation Disaster, Godora had always been on the losing side and needed a huge victory to prove their strength, stabilize their internal situation, and regain their citizen's confidence.

In order to ensure that their trap remained a secret, Godora did not send any of their troops. The War Bureau knew that DarkStar was definitely keeping tabs on their military. The moment that Godora gathered their forces on Planet Golden Gate, their plan would be exposed. In order to bait their prey into the trap, Godora needed to make use of an external force and thus thought of the mercenaries.

The ones willing to accept such a mission would only be the large mercenary groups.

The risk of such a battle was large, but the rewards were also tempting. This single mission was comparable to a few hundred thousand small-scale missions. Apart from the remuneration of the mission, the mercenaries were also allowed to deal with the spoils of war from the battle.

Han Xiao had not spent the past few years in the Shattered Star Ring in vain. He had worked with a few hundred different mercenary groups and had close ties with them all. The influence and connections of the Black Star Mercenary Group were nothing to be scoffed at.

Han Xiao formed the bridge this time and introduced Sky Ring, Blades, Purple Gold, and many other large mercenary groups to the War Bureau.

DarkStar naturally did not know that their plans had already been exposed by Han Xiao long ago. They had thought that ambushing Planet Golden Gate would catch Godora off guard but did not know that Godora was actually looking forward to them attacking Planet Golden Gate.

As the middleman, Han Xiao had a referral fee of 150,000 Enas. Naturally, the various mercenary groups that participated in the battle also charged sky high remuneration. Only an entity like Godora would be able to afford to hire that many large sized mercenary groups.

To be hired for an intergalactic war, the size of the mercenary group isn't the only factor. One also needs to have a sizeable fleet of battleships. When I lead the players into the galaxy, the Black Star Mercenary Group will be comparable to those large mercenary groups in terms of numbers. However, we will still be lacking in terms of battleships. Thus, I still have to earn more money.

Han Xiao collected his thoughts, and his mouth curled up as he watched the broadcast on his communicator. Leaving the workshop, he went into the cockpit of the BlackLight Stealth and knocked on the control panel.

"Risda, I need your help."

The next second, a figure of light appeared. "Black Star, what do you need me to do?"

"You are an AI lifeform and should be able to travel through cyberspace, right?"

Risda nodded and said, "This is my way of survival. Even if you are able to destroy the shell that I am living in, I can still survive in cyberspace."

"I will get Phillip to open up a path for you to go to the first base," Han Xiao said with a deep voice. "I will have the members of Sky Ring work with Phillip to construct a movement channel for you. They will try to attack a DarkStar mothership and help you infiltrate the system of the mothership. I need you to avoid or even replace the original AI system of the mothership and remain hidden in DarkStar."

Risda was a virtual lifeform who lived in cyberspace. Apart from aiding one in hacking, he could still lie dormant in the main frame system, just like how Risda occupied BlackLight Stealth and had swallowed the original AI system of this spaceship.

If Risda wanted to go undercover, he would be able to easily avoid the majority of firewalls with its processing speed. However, the condition for that is that his target had to have opened up a virtual connection to the outside world. Also, being connected by hardware was much easier than infiltrating through virtual space.

The DarkStar mothership made use of a mother AI and would not be able to cut off its connection so easily. If Risda could fool the mother AI, he could remain hidden and come into contact with DarkStar's database.

"I can try, but I have a condition," Risda said.

"Speak."

"I know that you want to borrow my strength to deal with the enemy, and I am willing to help you. However, I wish that you will help Aroshia to regain her memories quickly."

"Alright." Han Xiao nodded. He had never tried to actively complete the mission as it was too troublesome a mission. However, with the help of the players, this mission would become much simpler.

After convincing Risda, Han Xiao contacted the commander of the Sky Ring Army, Gureja.

With their battle strategy finalized, Han Xiao knocked on his communicator and said, "Phillip, connect to BlackLight Stealth and open up a data path to the first base."

"Roger that, hum..."

Phillip controlled both the bases, and as long as he opened up the path, Risda would be able to reach Planet Golden Gate in an instant.

This was the specialty of an AI life form. As long as it was not destroyed in the virtual world, any physical attack was useless against it.

Risda nodded, and the figure of light disappeared the very next moment.

"It passed through my data path, hum..."

Han Xiao looked at Gureja's projection and said, "I shall trouble you."

Gureja burst out into a hearty laughter. "Just take it as me thanking you for your recommendation."

After the communicator was cut off, Han Xiao let out a long sigh.

"I wonder if this will work..."

Planet Golden Gate was not only Godora's trap but also his.

DarkStar's whereabouts had always been extremely mysterious, and from the very start, Han Xiao knew that the only way to take care of DarkStar for good would be to lock onto their location!

...

The battle on Planet Golden Gate was at its peak. Despite the DarkStar fleet being large, they were not able to gain the upper hand over the various mercenary groups. DarkStar was a terrorist organization that scared many out of their wits, but being scary did not mean that they could fight. In terms of battle prowess, the mercenaries were the professionals.

That was especially so for mercenary groups such as the Sky Ring Army that had a resounding reputation in the Shattered Star Ring. Their battle strength had been honed through trials of fire and blood.

Originally, Planet Golden Gate could only remain on the defense. However, after the arrival of the reinforcements, they went on the offensive, and an intense battle broke out between the two parties. From time to time, battleships would be engulfed in flames. DarkStar was caught off guard, and their losses were immense.

In fact, there were a few times when the Sky Ring Army managed to break through DarkStar's formation and arrive before the nearest mothership. They had even managed to crash into the interior of the mothership and board the mothership. In the end, DarkStar had only managed to force the enemy back after deploying a couple of Calamity Grade Supers.

While both forces were equal in numbers, DarkStar was slowly losing.

"These darn mercenaries!" Degulish was enraged. He looked at the timer and gnashed his teeth. "We will not be able to destroy Planet Golden Gate before the arrival of Godora's reinforcements. Relay my orders, retreat! Our operation has failed!"

Since they would not be able to achieve their mission objective, Degulish could only give the order to retreat. They had intended to launch a blitz assault on Planet Golden Gate, but the battle had turned into one of attrition. If the battle continued, the risks would increase. Since they were not able to fulfil their mission objective, there was no need to increase their losses. All five motherships had some form of damage, but thankfully, they had not been destroyed. However, that might not be the case if they continued the battle.

Many of the DarkStar upper echelons felt it to be a huge pity. They did not expect Godora to become intelligent, and it seemed like they could only follow their leader's plan to attack the calamity planets.

DarkStar condensed their battle formation and rapidly retreated. The various mercenary groups gave chase for a short while before stopping. They had accepted the job to fight off the enemy, not eradicate them. The mercenaries were an extremely practical bunch and would only work for what they were paid for. 'Overtime' was not a word that was in their dictionary.

DarkStar retreated and disappeared into the galaxy.

In the eyes of the Godorans, despite coming with ferocity, DarkStar had been sent running with their tails tucked between their legs.

The citizens of Planet Golden Gate were overjoyed and forgot all about the unhappiness from being stopped when they tried to escape. The drastic change in attitude truly dumbfounded the guards.

This victory brought Godorans all around the galaxy joy, and all the news outlets in the Garton Star System were full of praise for Godora's victory. The fear caused by DarkStar had also diminished greatly.

They only needed a single victory to bring their citizens out from the dark and help many of their citizens regain confidence in them. This was why the War Bureau had so desperately needed a victory.

...

Han Xiao had always watched the news and waited patiently. Even until DarkStar retreated, his communicator had still been silent.

Han Xiao tapped on the table rhythmically while letting out a deep sigh.

The worst-case scenario would naturally be Risda being found and forced to escape. The AI of the mothership would not be able to block Risda, and Risda would definitely be able to escape. However, this would mean that he would lose contact with Risda. Han Xiao was still extremely concerned about such a good hacking partner.

"I'll wait a while longer. Risda should need some time to deal with the AI of the mothership."

Han Xiao paced around the room, and after waiting for a long time, his communicator rang.

Taking a look at it, his furrowed brows and expression eased up.

A bright smile could be seen on Han Xiao's face as he scrolled through the communicator.

"I wonder how much the Godorans are willing to pay for this information."

Chapter 567: The Endless Potential of Selling Intelligence

Han Xiao received from his communicator that Risda had successfully infiltrated the AI system of a DarkStar mothership. By making use of the authority that he had obtained, he was currently breaking into DarkStar's database. With Risda's abilities, as long as he could infiltrate the AI system, breaking into the database was a certainty.

As long as Risda could infiltrate the bottommost layer of the database, Risda would be able to replace the AI system of the mothership. When the other motherships exchanged information with this particular mothership, all of their coordinates would be exposed. Currently, only the coordinates of this particular mothership were exposed.

The extremely concealed DarkStar truly made one feel helpless. They hid in the dark while stirring up trouble with their mothership base moving around. Han Xiao was not aware of their exact location, and before Risda's appearance, Han Xiao did not have many ideas.

This was an idea that he had thought of after working together with Risda to deal with the sudden ambush on Planet Aquamarine previously. It was a feasible plan, and after some estimates, Han Xiao had arrived at a conclusion that excited him. This might be a way for him to take care of DarkStar for good and was extremely enticing.

Because he had set himself against DarkStar time and time again, DarkStar's enmity toward him would only continue to deepen, and it was a matter of time before they dealt with him.

Han Xiao would not have been afraid if he was alone. After all, during his previous life, it was an extremely common thing for him to be chased all around. While he would be perfectly safe, his comrades would be in danger. His foundations were still weak, and it would be extremely easy for DarkStar to destroy them.

With such a dangerous enemy, Han Xiao definitely would not let go of a chance to eradicate them. Even if he would not be able to activate a future mission, he would get rid of DarkStar at the first opportunity. Missions were endless in the galaxy, and it was more important for him to get rid of his enemies.

He needed Godora's help for this, and Godora would not let go of such a chance either.

With that thought in mind, Han Xiao left the room and went to the Godoran camp to find Nagakin.

"Black Star, you're here."

In the Godoran camp, the Godoran troops were currently packing up their items and moving them all onto the spaceship. The entire camp was bustling with activity, and Nagakin was supervising them from the side. Seeing Han Xiao arrive, Nagakin walked forward with a smile. It was obvious that he was in a good mood.

"Are you guys preparing to leave?" Han Xiao looked around.

Nagakin nodded with a face full of smiles and slapped Han Xiao on the back. "Yes, with the problem on Planet Aquamarine having been resolved, our mission is over. Our fleet and disaster relief squad will leave today.

"I still have to thank you. The higher ups are very satisfied with my efficiency and hinted that they will promote me after everything is over. This is all due to you."

His current Favorability with Han Xiao was over sixty points, and he had also hopped on a free ride with Han Xiao's contributions.

Han Xiao looked around before bringing Nagakin to a more concealed spot and saying softly, "I have some new intelligence. You will definitely be extremely interested in this. Help me contact the upper echelons of the War Bureau."

More benefits‽ Nagakin's eyes lit up.

"Drop me some hints so that I can describe it to the higher ups." Nagakin also suppressed his voice but had an expectant look on his face. Black Star was like a treasure trove to him. As long as he worked together with Black Star, he would definitely be able to gain benefits.

Looking at the way that Nagakin was acting, Han Xiao's face twitched slightly. Nagakin would not reveal his prestige and might when he was in front of Han Xiao. With the level of Favorability increasing, Nagakin would reveal his true character when they were in private. While being committed to his mission, he did not conceal his desire to go up the ranks. The image of a Calamity Grade expert in his mind collapsed completely.

Grade B formed the middle rung in the galaxy, and the Calamity Grade belonged to the upper rung. The War Bureau naturally attached great importance to Nagakin. However, the population of Godora was far too big, and there were still more than ten Calamity Grade experts. All of them were like imperial experts and the royal guard. Thus, Nagakin still had to face some competition.

"My intelligence this time is about DarkStar," Han Xiao said with a mysterious tone.

"What about them?"

"Their location," Han Xiao said briefly.

Nagakin's eyes widened in shock, and his breathing became heavy. He naturally understood the significance of those words.

"I need to ask you solemnly. You aren't lying to me, right?"

"I would lie to anyone but you." Han Xiao rolled his eyes.

"Follow me. I will inform the upper echelons immediately."

The both of them then walked into a secret meeting room and locked the door. Without saying another word, Nagakin took out his communicator to contact the higher ups.

The call went through, and the secretary of the War Bureau head appeared.

"Nagakin, the director-general is currently in a meeting. This is a meeting that the highest leader called. Wait until after the meeting if you have something."

The battle on Planet Golden Gate had just ended, and the upper echelons of Godora were discussing their follow up plans.

"I have something urgent!" Nagakin said.

"Then tell me first. I will pass the message to the director-general after the meeting."

"Tell him to forget about the meeting. It is a really big intelligence!" Nagakin's voice was filled with agitation. "Black Star has DarkStar's location!"

The expression of the secretary changed drastically, and he yelped, "Don't hang up!" before running toward the conference room. The conference room was filled with many people, with some being present physically and others just projections. They all turned to look at the secretary with doubtful expressions.

The secretary hurried over to the director-general of the War Bureau and explained the situation briefly. The eyes of the War Bureau's director-general widened, and he abruptly stood up. Picking his communicator up, he walked over to the highest leader and explained the situation.

The expression of the highest leader changed slightly, and he immediately bellowed in a deep voice, "The meeting is paused. Those who aren't called, please go out and rest."

Those present were all startled. Anyone capable of sitting at that conference table was a leader of an integral departments. Even the lowest ranked officer there was part of a core department that had access to the strategic plans of Godora. If Godora was an empire, this room would consist of the organs of the empire.

Just what would cause the highest leader to stop the meeting and even want some of the upper echelons to leave the room? Just what kind of intelligence was it that even they could not have access to it‽

The majority of the upper echelons left the room, and only the core group of the upper echelons remained. This matter was far too important, and the highest leader only kept his closest aides behind.

"Black Star, I am the highest leader of Godora, Serbia the Fifth."

Godora was a magical civilization, and their governance structure had the style of a magical planet. They did not rule over the civilization with a federation, and there was no need to talk about having a democratic election.

The highest leader was chosen by the traditions of an ancient monarchy. The superiority that purebloods felt was also because of this tradition. However, Godora did make some changes in this Galactic Civilization era to ensure that the governance structure could keep up with their productive capacity and technological standards. Their highest leader was no longer a lifelong title, and his authority was restricted. Much of his authority had been split up.

The noble families and royal bloodline were not as precious and sacred as in ancient times. The royalty had the majority of their special rights taken away from them, and only their status and honor were left behind. This was something that the Godoran citizens who had seen the many different ruling systems of the galaxy could barely accept. As a Galactic Civilization, the intelligence of their citizens was directly correlated to the progression of their civilization. Even if they had to go against their traditions, they had to continuously improve.

The moment their progression fell behind, it would be very likely for a change in governance to come about.

In fact, there were many civilizations that were more advanced in technology than ruling system. For example, Harmon's hometown was a boorish civilization that heavily emphasized combat prowess and did not use much of their brains. However, such a civilization was actually able to construct spaceships!

In the Galactic Civilization era, there were many different kinds of skills and technology. As such, the ruling system of a civilization was no longer as important to the productive capacity of the civilization. Thus, despite the three great civilizations of the galaxy having different ruling systems, their strength was equal.

Facing the highest leader of Godora, Nagakin bowed solemnly. On the other hand, Han Xiao only nodded casually as a greeting. This was the best part about being a mercenary—there was no need to perform any formal salutations.

"This is the third time that we've negotiated." Han Xiao smiled.

The first time was the Mutation Source sample, second about revealing DarkStar's plan and forming a bridge to the mercenaries. This was the third.

The previous two times, the ones negotiating with him had been the upper echelons of Godora. This time, it was the highest leader talking to him directly.

Without beating about the bush, they went straight to the point. Han Xiao proved that his intelligence was reliable, and Risda's ability was one that could not be replicated. To Godora, this intelligence was a hundred times more valuable than the Mutation Source. DarkStar was like a parasite to the entire civilization, and Godora yearned for the opportunity to get rid of DarkStar every single day.

Both parties had been fighting for many years, and if they could get rid of DarkStar thoroughly, they would be able to erase one of their biggest enemies. Be it in terms of the conflict between the pure and mixed bloods or their status and security, there would be many benefits.

"This is the third time that our Godora has made a transaction with you. Your intelligence is extremely important. Are you completing this transaction as an individual, or are you representing Floating Dragon?" Serbia The Fifth asked.

"Representing Floating Dragon, I guess," Han Xiao said. This meant that he was using his status as an assurance, and it was extremely official.

"What do you want?"

Godora would definitely want to obtain the intelligence that he had, and Han Xiao was not planning on holding back his demands.

Narrowing his eyes, Han Xiao slowly said, "Fifty middle sized battleships and one large sized mothership. I don't want Godora's models and want pure technological products. Second, I want to gain access to your knowledge bank and allow me to make a copy of a portion of the knowledge. Third, after the matter is over, reveal my contribution to the galaxy. Fourth, I want 20,000,000 Enas."

Those conditions of his were more than ten times harsher than the previous transaction with the Mutation Source. Every department had a limited budget, and this amount was not at all small. Not too long ago, they had just hired the many mercenary groups, and they were truly burning money too quickly. Serbia the Fifth frowned for a moment and fell silent.

"Okay, we will first pay you 5,000,000 Enas. The rest of the payment and the battleships will be paid after everything is over. At that time, we can allow you to make a copy of five different knowledges. As for announcing your merits, you want to raise your reputation, right? Alright, as long as we are successful, we can make an official announcement."

Woah, he accepted it without even bothering to bargaining. I should have raised my price. Han Xiao coughed dryly and hesitantly said, "Is it too late to change the price?"

"It's too late," Serbia the Fifth said with a darkened expression.

Han Xiao shook his head. This was the largest transaction that he had made to date. While this intelligence was valuable, Godora would have to mobilize their own forces at the end of the day, and it would not be too good for him to extort them. Even if it was an extremely important piece of intelligence, Godora would definitely try and suppress the price and not casually agree to his exorbitant price.

Han Xiao was about to bring the players into the galaxy, and he needed a lot of money for the early stages of his plan. With this new injection, his capital should be enough to last him a long time. If he only considered the cost price of a spaceship, 20,000,000 Enas would be sufficient to purchase a fleet of almost a hundred spaceships.

"Let's have a pleasant time working together," Han Xiao said.

"Hmm, we will await the good news. Nagakin, stay behind on Planet Aquamarine for now; you will be in charge of communication."

"Yes." Nagakin nodded.

...

A few days after the assault on Planet Golden Gate, in some corner of the Garton Star System, a fleet of DarkStar battleships was moving at high speed.

This fleet was currently on their way to Planet Aquamarine, and Degulish was the commander of the fleet. Ember was also part of the squad together with a high ranked officer named Terry. There was a total of three Calamity Grade Supers present in the squad. In order to get rid of Black Star, Degulish had sent out more than half of their high-end combat force.

With their ambush on Planet Golden Gate failing, the leader of DarkStar was only slightly surprised and did not have much of a reaction. He only got Degulish to follow their plan and attack Planet Aquamarine. Currently, DarkStar's plan had gone completely off-track, and they could only seize every opportunity they had to create losses for Godora. At this moment, their aggro toward Han Xiao was extremely stable.

Taking into account the fact that Black Star had the BlackLight Stealth, which was best at escaping, they knew that they had to force Black Star into a battle if they wanted to kill him. Thus, they had chosen to ambush Black Star's home planet so that Black Star would stay behind and fight.

"We shall wait for Godora's fleet to leave before attacking Planet Aquamarine. Make use of the space disruptor to cover the atmosphere of Planet Aquamarine. While it won't be useful in dealing with the BlackLight Stealth, we will be able to prolong the time needed to open up a space channel to Planet Aquamarine and prevent reinforcements from the other calamity planets. I have already checked. Ames left the Garton Star System a few days ago, and Black Star's backer isn't around.

"Ember will lead a portion of our forces as the spear head, and the rest of us will hide. We will only make our appearance after Ember ties Black Star down. We cannot reveal all of our strength, or we will scare Black Star away."

Degulish had a solemn expression.

Terry did not voice any disagreements.

"I will not make the same mistake that I did in Noriosse," Ember said coldly. "My ability is capable of massacring the commoners. As long as he cares, I will be able to force him to fight me. You'd all better appear quickly. If not, I may end up massacring the whole of Planet Aquamarine."

Chapter 568: Imminent Danger!

The 'Galaxy Times' had released a new program for the week.

As usual, the players on the forums were bustling, eager to know about this week's program.

The familiar faces of the two hosts once again appeared in front of the camera, saying the same familiar catchphrase opening sentences.

"Hello players, this is Galaxy Times, dedicated to sharing first-hand game information," the male host said. "Your gaming career is our top priority."

"Based on an anonymous response from our player friends, the station has decided to cancel the joke section. We're a serious news channel, and our principle has always been to deliver the most accurate and detailed news, not gain viewers through the usage of humor... hehe." The female host solemnly read out from the script but started laughing halfway.

"Be serious." The male host was seated upright, his gaze not shifting, and his lips did not even open when he was speaking, as though the words came directly from his throat.

A number of the viewers cheered, and the entire screen blurred with all sorts of chatter[1].

"Hey hey, what's this about cancelling? This program was originally for lame jokes!"

"Hahaha, this is even funnier than their original lame jokes!"

The program continued as the female host regained her composure. "This week's program was delayed for two days. This was because its content was originally about the Main Storyline for Version 2.0 on each planet. However, with the recent happenings on Planet Aquamarine, we had to change the content. Let's look at the content for this week..."

This week's 'Galaxy Times' episode was about the Version 2.0 Main Storyline for each of the novice planets. At this point, the majority of novice planets were already somewhat aware of the storyline and were just about to enter the most exciting phase.

But the actions on Planet Aquamarine had resulted in the Galaxy Times changing their report. This was because they had managed to end the Mutation Disaster; thus, their prepared content had to be updated.

While the players on the other planets were still happily progressing along the plot, the players on Planet Aquamarine had already completed their task.

This caused the players from the other planets to feel envious and jealous.

The last feature of the program was about Planet Aquamarine.

"In Version 1.0, Planet Aquamarine was also the only planet that managed to have players enter the interstellar area. If we look across the board, each novice planet has a certain specialty, and the specialty of Planet Aquamarine is to allow their players to enter the interstellar stage earlier.

"This time, Planet Aquamarine ended the Main Storyline of Version 2.0 way ahead of schedule. This also means that the players will enter the interstellar maps earlier than the other novice planets. Based off the current circumstances on Planet Aquamarine, it seems like the NPC guide to the interstellar path is Black Phantom, now known as Black Star. This is a legendary figure, with many channels dedicating themselves to understanding his past deeds. I will not waste time introducing him here."

While the Main Storyline of the planet had ended early, the players had also gotten the opportunity to enter the interstellar region earlier. To all the players, this was many times better than the storyline in Version 2.0!

All the players on Planet Aquamarine were overjoyed, and the Chinese clubs were even happier. This meant that they had correctly chosen their starting planet to be Planet Aquamarine, as it allowed them to pull forward from all the other esports clubs all over the world.

"From Black Star, we found out that the other novice planets will all have a faction with a guide. We will now focus on the introduction of Black Star and his Mercenary Group's actions on Planet Aquamarine..."

The two hosts recited their lines, analyzing the actions of Han Xiao in the Mutation Disaster from various angles. This was followed by analysis of the merits of joining the Black Star Mercenary Group, and they eventually gave a high evaluation.

Based on the knowledge given by the professional players under Black Star in Version 1.0, they knew that the privileges offered by the Black Star Mercenary Group were numerous. Furthermore, it was still a faction in its infancy. This meant that with the players fighting for the mercenary group, they could further increase its value, adding more benefits for themselves.

Thus, the Galaxy Times felt that the faction was something to be considered in the long term, and it was even possible for Black Star himself to be a hidden Main Storyline.

The players of Planet Aquamarine had long understood this from the start and thus did not show much response. Instead, it was the players all over the other novice planets that sighed in envy. Why did they not manage to get such a good NPC?

"They really did a great job inflating me."

Han Xiao was also viewing this program. The 'Galaxy Times' contained a lot of complicated content, and it was unlike the video channels made by Bun-Hit-Dog that were only meant for viewership. The 'Galaxy Times' had a colossal audience, and they mainly reported on events that had wide reaching impact. By talking about him, they had indirectly helped raise his reputation, attracting many potential players to this planet.

Turning off the forum, Han Xiao focused on the scene before his eyes. Right now, he was in the refugee area outside the Second Sanctuary. Bennett's Sanctuaries were no longer just shelters but rather urbanized cities. While the Mutation Disaster had just ended, a few of the stronger willed refugees had already begun to eke out a living once again and come out with their own little businesses and shops. They could not be termed refugees anymore but rather just residents.

Han Xiao sat outside a small street stall on the roadside. He had heard that the owner of this humble stall used to be a senior executive chef and had fled to seek refuge when the disaster struck. While he only used cheaper ingredients now, the taste was superb. The meat broth bubbled merrily on a stove, the rich fragrance wafting out, and the chef was even searing meat by the side using a metal pan. His wife was his kitchen aide and was stir-frying vegetables. The aroma of cooking food caused many passersby to glance back a second time.

There was a long queue in front of this booth, with people by the roadside wolfing down their food. There was a person who almost swallowed his fingers as well while eating. In the last few months, there was barely anyone who had eaten a proper meal. While the fare provided was simple, the combination of food with oil heightened their impression to that of a delicacy, allowing these people to soothe their strained heartstrings.

This street had originally been a dirty refugee camp, but now, it was so much cleaner. The atmosphere was no longer as depressed. A few of the refugees who had decided to stay had begun demolishing the tents and building simple houses, causing the streets to appear like a construction site and become a hubbub of noise and chatter.

"Sister, this is very nice!"

Seated opposite on the small table, Aurora cradled a bowl, making slurping noises as she ate. Her cheeks wobbled with every bite, causing her to resemble a tiny squirrel.

Hila only ate a few mouthfuls before she stopped. She stretched out a hand, tucking the stray strands of hair behind Aurora's ear, softly patting her back at the same time to ensure she did not choke.

The Great Mechanic Han was not so solitary that he would go shopping alone. He had asked the two sisters along with him, to observe the situation around the Sanctuary, as well as to talk about any issues they would have with the Dragon Emperor.

Although the Mutation Disaster had ended and the problem of Planet Aquamarine was resolved along with the leaving of the Godoran spaceship, Nagakin had surprisingly stayed to be in charge of communications.

Han Xiao estimated that the players would have probably gotten used to the fact that the Main Storyline had ended, and thus decided to wrap things up and formally take the players away. In the meantime, Ames had instructed him to take the two sisters over to Floating Dragon. Having asked the two of them, he did not receive any objections.

As they ate, Han Xiao transmitted his thoughts over to Risda. Risda had been attempting to hack into DarkStar mothership for a few days but still had not managed to completely break into the database.

However, according to the update sent by Risda, the estimated time should be near. As long as the hack was successful, the locations of all the DarkStar motherships would be revealed, which would spell their death.

Recently, news has spread about the increase in development of the Mutation Source on the calamity planets. The Godoran rescue teams are getting frustrated. It seems as though the infiltration teams of DarkStar on each planet have found the Mutation Source and fed it enough energy to accelerate its development. They have not given up just yet.

Han Xiao sat there silently contemplating before shaking his head. Most likely, Godora's current attention was no longer on providing disaster relief. He had to wait for his own intelligence to completely destroy the tumor that was DarkStar.

Wiping his mouth, Han Xiao stood up and prepared to pay. Seeing this, the chef hurriedly wiped his hands, rejecting the payment.

"Your Honor, you're the savior of our planet; everyone here owes you their life. How could we accept your payment?"

The attitude of the stall owner was determined, and this attracted the chorus of the surrounding crowd.

Hearing this, Han Xiao did not insist, instead patting Hila on the head and saying, "Then you pay."

"Did I allow you to touch my head? Do you think I'm Aurora‽"

Hila grumpily smacked off Han Xiao's hand, glaring at him, before talking out her purse.

Du! Du!

At this time, his communicator sounded. It was a message from Risda.

"I've succeeded in hacking into their database and have located the coordinates of all the DarkStar motherships. I've discovered that there is a mothership that's moving toward Planet Aquamarine. It's extremely close, and there are three Calamity Grade Supers within. You have to be careful."

The first half of the sentence left Han Xiao in joy, but the latter half caused his expression to sink.

A DarkStar mothership is approaching Planet Aquamarine‽

It went without saying, the three Calamity Grade Supers definitely did not come here for sightseeing!

"Could it be that DarkStar wishes to eradicate the calamity planet that has managed to resolve the mutation disaster‽"

Han Xiao's thoughts flashed, and he came up with a conjecture that was close to the mark.

However, their motive should also be to deal with him, or else they would not have brought out three Calamity Grades.

Could it be that DarkStar had discovered his involvement and schemes‽

Han Xiao groaned inwardly. Since the Godoran frigate was not present, he alone was unable to withstand the attacks from a mothership.

The circumstances were dire!

He immediately contacted Nagakin. The first issue now was to remain rational and seek for help.

"I've discovered a DarkStar mothership in the vicinity of Planet Aquamarine. They most likely wish to eradicate this planet, and thus, danger is imminent. We have to request for assistance!"

"What‽ I'll report it up now!" Nagakin exclaimed.

Since they were still within their honeymoon period of cooperating, Godora would definitely come to his aid.

Han Xiao did not stop to rest, immediately contacting Bennett and the Six Nations. He requested for them to arrange staff to guide the people in the cities to take shelter in the underground air defense facilities.

DarkStar would be launching a global strike, and without the frigate from Godora to protect the planet, the danger would be a hundred times higher. This would be akin to throwing a delicate pretty girl into a group of sex-starved men. They could only try to minimize the losses before the reinforcements came.

This was the greatest crisis that Planet Aquamarine had ever faced. DarkStar was an enemy that this planet could not afford to face. If they did not handle the situation properly, their civilization would end there and then!

Just like the Sunil civilization of the past.

"What's wrong?" Hila caught Han Xiao's expression and furrowed her brows.

"There's a fleet that's about to attack us. Don't tarry here any longer. Take your sister to the Sanctuary to hide. I'll activate the protective shield later," Han Xiao replied swiftly.

"Aurora will return. I can stay to protect you," Hila replied in a solemn tone.

"Help my *ss, this battlefield is way too early for you to be participating in!"

Han Xiao was not courteous at all. When faced with three Calamity Grades, even he would feel the pressure. If not for the fact that he had received the two Molding Abilities that made him into something of a power generator, he would not take the risk of facing the enemy at all. To think that Hila, who was far from having the qualifications to participate, wanted to join in!

Hila's face turned stiff as she angrily gritted her teeth. However, she knew that Han Xiao was not someone who would pretend to be strong. If he said that she was not suitable, then she was really ill-suited for it. She did not hesitate, hurriedly taking her sister to run toward the inner portions of the Sanctuary, her speed extremely quick.

Given Han Xiao's current status, he was fully capable of commanding the whole of Planet Aquamarine. Having received his news, the Six Nations and Bennett were alarmed and immediately mobilized people to help the civilians evacuate.

Alarms rang throughout the Sanctuary, and the city immediately turned chaotic. Groups of refugees were guided toward the air defense facilities.

The residents in the street also left, jostling with each other.

Hu!

Just as Han Xiao was preparing to go up to the command center to coordinate the overall situation, a whistling sound came from the sky.

More than a dozen spaceships from DarkStar entered the atmosphere, heading toward the shelters. They swooped at high speed and, without warning, immediately began firing their laser cannons. Clusters of beams hit various locations in the Sanctuary, and dozens of areas immediately exploded.

Boom!

Flames and smoke rose up into the sky. The next second, the peaceful Sanctuary turned into a visage of hell!

This did not stop at the Sanctuaries. At the same time, the Six Nations were also attacked by the DarkStar ships.

Planet Aquamarine had come under enemy attack once again!

"How did they arrive so quickly‽" Han Xiao had a grave expression. He had only received the news a few short minutes ago and only just begun to evacuate the civilians. How did the enemies appear so quickly?

A DarkStar spaceship shot over his head, bringing with it a screaming gust of wind. Han Xiao glanced up at it, and his eyes suddenly focused.

That's right. The mothership should not have arrived yet. This group should be the vanguard!

We have to immediately bring these spaceships down!

Han Xiao contacted his mercenaries to deploy the protective shield at the base while starting up the ground-to-air Electromagnetic Rail Cannon. He also ordered the officers such as Herlous to utilize the assault ships seized the previous time to fight against the DarkStar vanguards.

With a protective shield above the Sanctuary, the situation was better there compared to the Six Nations. They were the ones that required more help at the moment.

As he was issuing his orders, Han Xiao suddenly sensed danger and immediately leaped to the side. A black arrow that was tens of meters long was deeply embedded where he had previously stood.

Bang!

The street split apart from the impact!

The next second, the dark arrow collapsed and turned into countless particles, hovering around a figure in the sky.

Ember lowered his head to look at Han Xiao. His face was expressionless as he snapped his fingers.

Pa!

His move is not targeted at me... Han Xiao's heart tightened, and he quickly turned back to look. Behind him, the refugees that were running away from afar all turned into piles of ash in an instant. The stall owner's family was one of the affected. Just a second ago, he had still been running away in large strides, and in the next second, he had turned into a pile of ash on the ground.

Those who were fortunately spared from the attack all collapsed to the ground, scared silly. A warmth could be felt around their crotches.

At this point, Ember looked down from high above, coldly speaking.

"Did you miss me, Black Star?"

Dammit, this guy's ability to cause damage to civilians is too scary. I have to hold him down!

Han Xiao furrowed his brows before reining in his stare. He looked at Ember as he sarcastically replied, "Of course I did. You lost to me so many times previously. Do you wish to taste defeat once more?"

Hearing this, a hint of anger appeared on Ember's face. However, he realized that his mission was to force Black Star to stay and battle him, and his anger was immediately replaced by a cold sneer.

"Haha, do you think I came to deal with you this time?"

Ember raised his head to look at his surroundings. The Sanctuary was set ablaze, with spaceships constantly bombarding the area. The streets had turned into debris, with waves of refugees constantly running around.

His gaze swept across the muddled crowds before locking onto the escaping figures of Hila and Aurora.

"I've already checked you out thoroughly. Those two women are probably friends that you value highly. So, you can collect their corpses! If there's still anything to collect after this!"

Ember activated his ability, grasping outward with his fingers.

From afar, Hila and Aurora's bodies began turning to ash!

[1] Similar to the bullet comments you can see on WN's comics. Back

Chapter 569: Army Appear!

Cr*p!

Han Xiao immediately activated Void Travel, and his figure appeared before Ember. He did not have enough time to put on his mechanical suit but sent a kick toward Ember's crotch.

Boom!

How despicable! Ember's face turned ashen. His little brother was almost kicked, but he quickly blocked the attack. Han Xiao was not able to cause much damage without his mechanical suit, but he managed to cut off Ember's Esper ability.

Only then did Han Xiao have time to put on his mechanical suit. Turning around to take a look, he realized that Hila had lost her leg, and Aurora had lost an arm.

A brilliant golden light then burst forth from Aurora's palms and swallowed Hila up. Hila's leg then grew back out rapidly. Only after doing so did Aurora regrow her own arm.

Hila immediately grabbed Aurora and continued to escape. The previous attack had allowed her to understand the difference in strength. She knew that she would only be a burden to Han Xiao if she stayed behind.

What a frightening ability. To think that he has always been dealing with such dangerous enemies...

A look of anxiousness could be seen on her face.

...

With both the sisters being safe, Han Xiao heaved a sigh of relief.

Thankfully, Aurora is able to regrow broken limbs. It seems like her strength has grown.

Hila and Aurora's abilities complemented each other. While they were currently weak, it was not so easy to get rid of them. Back when they were trying to break out of the Germinal Organization's encirclement, a hole had opened up in Hila's stomach, but she had still managed to survive with her talent. With Aurora by her side now, it was like carrying a gigantic HP potion.

"Will you be able to block me?"

Ember did not bother chasing the sisters but diverted his attention to Han Xiao. The civilians were only his bait; he had only attacked the others to force Black Star to fight him.

Ten or so black snakes then shot toward Han Xiao like speeding arrows. This was not the first time that he had fought Han Xiao, and he knew that it was not so easy to deal with Han Xiao. Thus, he immediately went all out.

The compressed orbs that Han Xiao always carried with him burst into action, and the Halo Array covered Han Xiao in a protective shield. The black snakes smashed into the shield ferociously, and sparks burst forth from the friction of the collision. The shield glowed brightly and expended a great amount of energy. Han Xiao was forced back by the powerful impact, and two ditches were made from his feet being dragged along the ground.

An open terrain in advantageous to him. He is of a higher grade than me and has better attributes. I will only be able to tie him down. Han Xiao's face was solemn.

The situation was extremely bad. Ember was only the advance party, and there were still two Calamity Grade Supers and a mothership behind him. This was a force capable of destroying Planet Aquamarine.

The only choice he had was to wait for reinforcements to arrive. If Godora wanted his intelligence, they would certainly show up.

Right at that moment, he activated a mission.

_____________________

You have triggered an Urgent Mission [Planet Aquamarine's Crisis]!

Mission Hint: DarkStar has launched a sudden attack on Planet Aquamarine. This planet needs your protection, and you must try to block the enemies.

Mission Requirements: Block the DarkStar forces and protect Planet Aquamarine until the reinforcements appear.

Current destruction: 167/3,000

Failure Condition: Full destruction meter

Mission Reward: 620,000 Experience, +2 Garton Star System Renown, +1,500 Six Nations Favorability

_____________________

An unexpected event would usually trigger an Urgent Mission. Not just Han Xiao, but all the players on Planet Aquamarine had triggered this Urgent Mission. In the Sanctuary, all the players stopped what they were doing and looked up at the sky with shock. The DarkStar battleships were cutting through the clouds and firing upon the planet.

The protective shield of the second base opened up and the rail guns also revealed themselves. At the same time, the spaceships of the mercenaries also took off into the sky and launched their counterattack.

Why would there be a sudden attack on the planet? The players couldn't understand why and were extremely puzzled. However, it was more important for them to deal with the enemy and they all got to work quickly.

All of them activated the [Planet Aquamarine's Crisis] mission but Han Xiao activated another special mission.

_____________________

You have triggered an Urgent Mission [Assassination Target]!

Mission Hint: Your actions have caused great losses for DarkStar, and the hatred has been accumulating. Finally, DarkStar has found a chance. They sent out three Grade A Officers and decided to kill you.

Mission Requirements: You will be surrounded by three Grade A Supers. Hang in there until reinforcements arrive.

Failure Conditions: Death or escaping from Planet Aquamarine

Mission Reward: 12,100,000 Experience, +30 Garton Star System Renown, +1,000 Godora Favorability, +1 Legendary Point

_____________________

"Their spaceship is already right at my doorstep, and this is still called an assassination‽" Han Xiao had a strange look on his face.

The mission hint had confirmed Risda's intelligence.

Through the radar, Han Xiao could clearly observe the situation of the battlefield in the Sanctuary. Everyone was currently working together to fight off the enemies, so there was no need for him to get distracted.

Han Xiao focused all his attention on Ember.

Han Xiao could only rely on the others to deal with the other enemies. He had to block Ember personally; if not, the casualties would be immense.

Dong! Dong!

The black sand continued to smash against his golden shield, and Han Xiao was almost forced into the ground. Han Xiao immediately opened his interface, and without even looking, he put all his accumulated experience into leveling up.

In the past month, he did not push out any new skills or knowledge to the players, and the experience that he had earned was not enough to push him up to level 140. However, in the face of a powerful enemy, every little bit of strength counted. It would be extremely difficult for him to deal with a single Calamity Grade Super, not to mention the fact that there were two more on the way. He had no choice but to convert all his resources into combat capability.

His experience points were used up rapidly.

_____________________

[Virtual Mechanic] was raised to Lv.11.

+150 Energy, +3 END, +6 INT.

You have received 6 Free Attribute Points and 1 Potential Point.

_____________________

His accumulated experience was sufficient for him to go up by six levels, and his total level was now 136!

This time, he did not throw his Free Attribute Points into Intelligence. His Intelligence was already more than 1,100 points and was remarkably high already. Ordinarily, he would have added it all to Intelligence for sure. However, he was currently facing the biggest crisis ever, and it was not appropriate for him to increase his Intelligence further.

Han Xiao threw all his points into Endurance to ensure his survival. He was extremely clear that even if he made use of his Mechanic Army, it would be difficult for him to defeat a Calamity Grade Super head on. Furthermore, the other party had three Calamity Grade Supers. All he could do was tank the damage with his body.

The Aurora Character Summon Card in his hands still had a few usages left. Furthermore, the two new Molding Abilities that he had gained from the Mutation Source would serve a great purpose. Under such circumstances, the higher his HP, the more obvious the effect of those trump cards.

After adding all his points into Endurance, Han Xiao's health increased by 5,643 points!

His total HP had broken the 40,000 mark!

The higher his level, the bigger the difference. The increase in HP from his six levels was more than the overall HP of a level 60 player.

A warm surge of energy spread out from within his body. Han Xiao felt his mind freshen up, and he placed his palms together.

Clank!

Eight large mechanical arms appeared together and transformed into drills to retaliate.

Han Xiao bent his knees slightly, and the thrusters under his feet spewed out flames at maximum capacity to block off the incoming black tide. He then threw out a large number of compressed orbs, which formed various floating artillery towers. Ember was immediately showered with an endless stream of bullets.

The street was completely flattened by their battle, and Han Xiao did not have the extra energy to be concerned about the exterior region of the Sanctuary. Han Xiao then threw out another two compressed orbs, and the two Oathkeepers that he always carried with him, Warrior and Blaster, appeared beside him.

Boom boom boom!

The two of them were locked in a stalemate.

Ember wanted to control the carbon particles to destroy the interior of the machines. Han Xiao had fallen for this trick before and was prepared to deal with this technique. He let out a large number of Hovering Shield Shuttles and covered his machines with a simple energy shield to block the carbon particles from flowing in.

The two of them were engaged in an intense battle, and it was as though a gigantic black snake was fighting a metal army. Their battlefield shifted around the outer region of the Sanctuary, and destruction followed them wherever they went.

Right at that moment, a golden shooting star like figure shot over from afar and crashed into the black snake beneath Ember's feet.

Ember's eyes narrowed, and he hurriedly avoided the incoming golden fist.

Nagakin, who was wreathed in golden flames, landed beside Han Xiao and glared at Ember angrily.

Nagakin's entrance had temporarily broke the two up.

"Black Star, are you alright?"

"Don't worry, he won't be able to harm me. Are the reinforcements here yet?"

Nagakin shook his head with a solemn expression. "I have already informed the War Bureau, and the fleets stationed at the other calamity planets are already rushing over. Originally, they would only take three minutes or so to arrive, but because DarkStar set up a space disrupter outside the atmosphere of the planet, our reinforcements will take more time to get here."

If the fleet protecting Planet Aquamarine had not been pulled back, they would definitely have been able to survive this short period. However, the War Bureau had placed all their attention on wiping out DarkStar for good. Upon seeing that the calamity on Planet Aquamarine had been resolved, they had followed their original plan and pulled back their forces.

Furthermore, they had thought that the huge victory at Planet Golden Gate would slow DarkStar down slightly; never had they expected DarkStar's next move to be so swift.

"Thankfully, there is only a single Calamity Grade Super. He is Ember, who massacred millions in Long Arc. I will work together with you and get rid of him quickly."

Nagakin glared at Ember and was eager to battle.

Ember's expression turned into one of wariness and anger. The two before him were the ones who had gotten rid of Anur, and this was still fresh in his mind.

With the protective fleet being pulled back, why would Godora leave one of their experts behind?

Ember began to frown. His mission was to tie down Black Star, and he was confident in doing so. However, with Nagakin in the picture, his arms would be tied up.

We will only be able to have some chance of victory when Degulish and Terry arrive. Thankfully, they aren't aware that we have another two lying in ambush. Perhaps we will be able to get rid of a Godoran powerhouse.

Ember glared at the two coldly with confidence.

Right at this moment, Han Xiao grabbed Nagakin's arm and said, "Don't, let me tie him down. You should deal with the assault forces in space. Tell Herlous to take some Inhumans to reinforce the Six Nations. The Sanctuary has the both of us, protective shields, and surface to air weapons. However, the Six Nations are in grave danger and require immediate reinforcements!"

Nagakin was taken aback and frowned. "What do you mean by that? With the two of us joining hands, we will be able to take care of him quickly. Just like we did back in Noriosse."

"It wouldn't be so simple." Han Xiao waved his hands.

He had used the Dragon Emperor Character Summon Card previously to create the opportunity for Nagakin to go all out. This time, he no longer had the Character Summon Card, and they would not be able to get rid of Ember quickly.

Since that was the case, it would be better for him to tie Ember down and get Nagakin to protect the base to minimize losses. In just a short while, the destruction meter had gone up by more than 400 points. They had to immediately stop the assault fleet.

Furthermore, there would be another two Calamity Grade Supers ambushing him later. He would be able to pull open the battlefield and tie down three of the opponent's experts single-handedly. With Aurora's Character Summon Card and his Molding Abilities, it would be extremely difficult for the other party to kill him.

However, things would be different if Nagakin was beside him. If the three from DarkStar chose to suddenly surround Nagakin, he would definitely be in danger. Despite Nagakin being a Grade A Pugilist, his skin was not as thick as Han Xiao's.

"Alright, I shall leave him to you!" Nagakin gritted his teeth and nodded. Since Han Xiao insisted, he could only choose to trust his comrade. He looked at Ember before sprinting toward the base.

Upon seeing that, Ember looked at Han Xiao with a look of mockery.

Mission accomplished! Black Star was baited!

To think that you would actually reject Nagakin's help and face me alone. You are truly asking for trouble!

When Degulish and Terry arrive, you won't be able to escape even if you want to!

In his eyes, Han Xiao did not know that there was an ambush.

Ember was secretly delighted. He truly wanted to see what Black Star's expression would be like when the ambushing troops appeared!

Currently, the Sanctuary was consumed by flames and was in a complete mess. The sound of cannon fire, anxious shrieks, and miserable groans could be heard all around. DarkStar had brought a more direct calamity to the planet. Stopping the Mutation Disaster had resulted in revenge from DarkStar.

Han Xiao took a deep breath and suppressed the frustration in his heart. He ignored the chaos happening in the outside world. He threw everything to do with destruction, casualties, and death out of his head.

Ember stepped on the black current and floated in midair. Looking down on Han Xiao from above, killing intent emanated from his face.

If Black Star was alone, he would not be wary.

"You aren't at the Calamity Grade yet, right? Without the traps that you set up last time, how will you deal with me?"

Upon hearing that, Han Xiao's voice sounded from the helmet. "It's been more than a year since we last fought, but your strength hasn't increased much. However, I am different from you. Phillip, release all the armies!"

"Roger, hum..."

Hu!

Since Risda was not around, Phillip was now in charge of piloting the BlackLight Stealth. The BlackLight Stealth weaved through the battlefield between the assault spaceships and mercenaries and appeared above Han Xiao. A few boxes were then ejected from the belly of the spaceship, and the boxes flew toward Han Xiao with the use of thrusters.

Han Xiao's eyes lit up with a bolt of electricity, and he pointed his right palm toward the sky. Overflowing Mechanical Force burst forward and formed countless lightning whips to connect to all the Army Boxes.

"Army appear!"

Chapter 570: Siege

The arcs of Mechanical Force connected several Army Boxes. With a wave of his right hand, Han Xiao triggered the lightning to move downward.

The Army Boxes were slammed open, and out rolled numerous compressed orbs that shot like bullets toward Ember, as though a hail of arrows.

Clank!

The machines clanked as they moved around, the noise suppressing all other sound. All the compressed orbs unfolded in midair, turning into countless mechanical creations that covered the sky, raining down like a deluge of metal.

Ember's expression changed, and he controlled his black current in a head-on collision.

Boom boom boom!

The black current was forcibly ripped apart, and the mechanical soldiers landed on the ground one after another. There were different models, different appearances, with their heights and sizes varying. They covered the entire area, with Ember trapped within, looking extremely helpless.

There was a total of four Army Boxes, and the one numbered 001, the Mechanical Beast Guards Army, had several thousand mechanical beasts encircling Ember, as though they were observing prey.

Box 002 contained the Strike Artillery Regiment. This was a long-range force, meant to support the troops. It was located behind the formation and boasted long-ranged artilleries, including rapid-fire turrets, large-caliber turrets, self-propelled turrets, mini-rail guns, and more. All their nozzles were aimed at Ember.

As for box 003, the G-1 Steel Army Corps, this is a hybrid army with the largest personnel, a total of 6,400 mechanical warriors. Among them were the larger attack units, clad in heavy armor that reflected a cold metal luster. They shielded the front of the formation, each holding an alloy tower shield that glowed with energy arcs.

There were also harassment units composed of the 4th Generation Rangers, equipped with high speed rocket-powered machinery to serve as the vanguard. Some were suspended in the air, able to conduct aerial combat with their lasers or trap and separate enemies.

The last was box 101, the Oathkeeper Personal Guard. Separated by 'fighters' and 'gunners', there was a total of eight of them standing around Han Xiao.

Han Xiao possessed four armies with their own unique numbers. Other than the elite troops comprised of the Oathkeepers, the other three armies were conventional models of an army, utilizing human wave tactics.

The first number for the serial numbers in the regular armies was '0', while the elite troops were labelled '1'.

The construction of the Army Style was time, money, and energy consuming. To create those four legions, Han Xiao had thrown in quite a bit of money. Even with the assembly line aiding him, he had also spent quite a bit of time constructing his machinery.

The mechanical warriors configured were all carefully selected by him after scouring through many blueprints. Not only did they possess strong fighting capabilities, they could be quickly repaired after receiving damage.

In theory, as long as one had enough money, they could build as many legions as they wanted, given that the operating speed of the Artificial Intelligence in charge of controlling the legion could keep up. If one Artificial Intelligence could not handle the operations, then just build another! This was the advantage of money.

However, Han Xiao had only built four legions, which had taken him almost three months. He had originally planned to only expand his army on a large scale after he reached Grade A.

It would be a qualitative leap forward for him, allowing his manufacturing speed to be further boosted, which could save him a lot more time. Furthermore, the machines created would also have stronger properties, and he would also have a lot more powerful blueprints by then.

This was also the first time that Han Xiao had fully activated his entire mechanical army.

The mechanical army surrounded Ember tightly, their alloy armors reflecting the sunlight.

Han Xiao fired a Void Jet Spray in the direction of Ember.

Where the muzzle was pointed, the army advanced!

Boom!

The next second, the mechanical army pressed forward, reminiscent of a metal tsunami!

The artillery fire was almost endless, and with each passing second, more than a thousand lasers were fired toward the black current. The diamond barrier constantly shattered and regenerated, and Ember was immediately placed under a great amount of pressure. He gritted his teeth.

Even with the natural resistance afforded to him by his Calamity Grade, if he was hit by so many attacks, he would definitely suffer a serious injury!

Ember could only sense that a division was surrounding and attacking him. He was drowned in the sea of machinery, and he felt at a loss.

His face revealed an expression of shock. Every time he faced Black Star, the speed of his opponent's growth would always leave him fearful. The gap between their abilities seemed to be shortening, with him being caught up.

Could it be that I'll never defeat him in my life‽

Ember's eyes turned bloodshot at the thought.

Fog-like particles rose from their surroundings, merging into the black current. The size of the black current constantly expanded, and soon, the cloud of black particles covering hundreds of meters condensed, changing its shape. The outer layer turned into diamond to resist the attacks, while several huge python-like carbon creatures stuck their heads out from within, piercing into the mechanical army and continuously swallowing the broken mechanical warriors.

"A Calamity Grade is indeed difficult to go against." Han Xiao continued to release his mechanical force, providing a large amount of machinery bonuses to his army.

He did not need to worry about his energy being depleted. He just had to rush into the black current and receive a few hard blows, and his energy tank would be refilled. A generator was just this law-breaking and unbridled.

The Army Style was about being a gangster and using human wave tactics. It was even more overpowered than the summoning system. The summoning system at least required mana consumption, but this Army Style only required the machinery to be prepared in advance. Both sides had their advantages and disadvantages, but just speaking in terms of raw fighting strength, the Army Style was the most domineering.

Just like how the summoner was required to burn their mana, the Army Style required burning money, just like the divine skill of legends 'Tossing out the Heaven and Earth[1.It's an idiom meaning to go and stake everything. Think 'All In' for poker.]'. Money was in some ways equivalent to the combat capability of a Mechanic.

The Army Style can be used to crush someone of the same level and could also be used to consume the strength of Supers of a higher level. Ember being reduced to a passive state was a good example. Back when they were on Noriosse, Han Xiao could only try to avoid a direct fight with Ember by any means. However, he could now go head to head against him and even suppress the other party. The effects were obvious.

Even if Ember could withstand the concentrated gunfire and slowly swallow and chip away at his forces, he still had a limit to his energy. If he continued to waste it as such, it was unknown who would be the biggest loser in the end. This showed that the probability of Ember losing was not low at all!

For a Calamity Grade to face off against a Grade B Super, winning was inevitable. Very few could surpass the gap that divided both sides.

The battle between both sides only grew fiercer. After the mechanical army joined the battle, the resulting activity could be described as earth shaking. It was difficult not to notice it even if one did not wish to. Even the players far away from the Sanctuary could see the great war between Ember and Han Xiao, and they had expressions of surprise.

Compared to the power that Black Star was showing, the strength that he had used to deal with the Mutation Source was almost trivial!

Bun-Hit-Dog's eyes shone, and he rushed to the scene without fear of his death, recording the entire scene in the meantime.

By this point, Hila had brought Aurora back to the protective shield region. As she turned back and saw the battle between both parties, a hint of worry flashed across her face. Han Xiao was right; she did not possess the qualifications to take part in a battle of that level.

In the sky, Nagakin had brought his own troops to attack and destroy the offending DarkStar motherships. As for Herlous and the rest, they heeded Han Xiao's instructions, taking a group of players to assist the Six Nations.

At that moment, a few batches of DarkStar spaceships appeared in the sky, quickly drawing near. The number was many times greater than the first batch.

The DarkStar's main forces had arrived!

Everyone's expression dropped.

The situation has just gotten worse!

Two other threats quickly approached. Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and he commanded the mechanical army to halt their attacks and pull away, protecting himself in the center.

Ember was breathing heavily. He had resisted the mechanical army for quite some time and had begun to feel the fatigue. He was extremely aggrieved in his heart, as he realized that if he continued fighting, his life would be in danger. His abilities were well-suited for killing carbon lifeforms but not so powerful against the group of machines comprised of different alloys. If it was merely ordinary machinery, it would not have been so bad, but all the machines present were buffed by Black Star and increased his consumption to ward them off.

However, at this point, Ember burst into laughter with great confidence—his reinforcements had arrived!

From the other two positions, Degulish and Terry each occupied a spot, forming a triangular formation with Ember. In a twist of fate, Han Xiao was now the one being surrounded.

"Well done, Ember. He's trapped now." Degulish nodded, his body brimming with energy. He was a pugilist.

Ember looked at Han Xiao, breathing a sigh of relief as he sneered, "My mission was not to kill you but to restrain you. The moment we engaged, you had already fallen for my ploy. Bet you didn't expect it!"

Ember was hoping that Han Xiao would reveal some panic or maybe even try to escape. However, Han Xiao did neither, instead moving into a fighting posture.

Han Xiao had always intended to tangle with the three of them but at the same time did not wish for them to realize that he had known about the ambush in advance. As such, he had followed along. Besides, his mechanical suit covered his face as well, not allowing anyone to observe his expressions.

Looking at the three of them, Han Xiao started to calculate.

This ambush was created for me. Three Calamity Grade Supers, looks like DarkStar really wants me dead. It's good that I sent Risda out, or else I would have been facing the same headache as Godora...

Right now, I need to restrain these three with all my might, not allowing them to have any energy spare to deal with others. Among them, the Pugilist gives me the most pressure. I estimate that he is slightly stronger than the other two. I'm not sure if I can endure the damage given by the three of them. Oh well. For now, it should be fine!

Those thoughts shot by in an instant, and Han Xiao took a deep breath. Activating his [Medium Cell Proliferation Control], he exhausted a portion of his energy to recover his HP. Then, he cracked a smile.

"Only the three of you? That's too little!"

Unable to witness what he expected, Ember gritted his teeth in hatred. Stubborn!

Seeing how Han Xiao wished to resist to the end, Degulish revealed a cold smile.

A Grade B Super, when faced with three Calamity Grade Supers, still wishes to resist?

Is Black Star relying on his mechanical army? Ha, do you think that can ward off three Grade A Supers? It will not take long to demolish all of them, and they will definitely not be able to block us. I am a Pugilist and can rush straight in and kill you instantly!

You're overestimating yourself!

Terry patted his chest, and a thin, light combat suit covered his body. From his arms came out a few pieces of soft metal of an unknown alloy. Sweeping his hands out like a maiden throwing out flowers, the metal pieces suddenly elongated over tens of meters, easily destroying the surrounding machinery.

He was a Mechanical Pugilist.

"I have no idea how long the space disruption device can ward off the reinforcements from Godora. Stop wasting time and get rid of him," Terry replied.

The moment he finished his words, Ember, Degulish and Terry rushed straight into the mechanical army from different directions, utilizing their full strength and sending scattered machinery flying into the air. The metallic parts filled the air as the three of them cleared out a path, throwing themselves straight toward Han Xiao.

Three immense pressures barreled straight into Han Xiao, causing the Mechanical Force around him to jump around excitedly in arcs.

His eyelids snapped open, and his voice was resounding.

"Come, let's have some fun!"

Chapter 571: Is This Guy a Cockroach‽

At the same time, the Six Nations were also attacked by the DarkStar spaceships. Without the protection of Han Xiao, the cities were ravaged by the projectiles, with charred corpses lying everywhere in the streets.

The tanks fired toward the spaceships in the sky, the artillery shells bursting out into black smoke as they bombarded the energy shields of the spaceship. However, even an armor-piercing round could not penetrate the shield made from interstellar technology and would only cause a few ripples. The DarkStar spaceships remained unaffected, only leaving behind a cloud of smoke in the area of impact before they turned to fire directly at the tanks.

The laser cannons effortlessly punched through the armor of the tanks, blowing them up from the inside. The tanks were quickly annihilated.

The civilization tiers of both parties were too far apart; the Six Nations had no way to resist.

However, the fighter planes continued to bombard the DarkStar spaceships. Even at the cost of being destroyed, none of the planes chose to retreat. They were akin to moths flying toward the flame in this one-sided battle.

Even though they knew it was impossible to break the defense of the spaceship, the planes still stubbornly launched their suicidal attacks.

The aliens wished to destroy the whole planet, so escaping would not be of any use. There was no path of retreat for them, and this disaster seemed to have awakened the tenacity of the Planet Aquamarine people. The Six Nations swore to guard their homeland till their very last breath.

Even if they knew that this was like a mantis trying to stop a cart, they would still put in all their strength to resist, despite being weak!

As the upper echelons of the Six Nations watched DarkStar ravage the city and the soaring levels of casualties, they felt a sadness within.

The Old Era had been a turbulent time, and because they had experienced countless wars, everyone had long become accustomed to it. However, they had to continuously consume the lives of their soldiers now, letting them die without any means of damaging the enemy. This was the first time that resistance had been futile.

The upper echelons of the Six Nations all had expressions that were as calm as a lake, but their fists were clenched so tight that their knuckles had turned white. In the past few months, they had continuously felt the sorrow of being a backward civilization. It was akin to being a child that continuously got trampled by the adults around it.

At this moment, the reinforcements from the Sanctuary arrived. Many of the players had also been brought over. While the enemies' spaceships outnumbered the reinforcements, a portion was successfully restrained, allowing the Six Nations to somewhat negate the threat of annihilation.

"Black Star's men have arrived." The clenched fists of the upper echelons loosened slightly.

Thank goodness... on this weak, backwater planet like ours, we still have someone like Black Star.

Only through him do we have some form of retaliatory strength.

...

Above the Sanctuary, there were vastly more DarkStar spaceships. They rained concentrated fire on the protective shield of the Sanctuary. Tremors and rumbling could constantly be felt. With Nagakin's troops continuously harassing the spaceships, they were unable to focus on breaking the protective shield.

This was especially so for Nagakin, who did not need other means to deal with the spaceships in the atmosphere. Blasts of flames from his body would be able to shatter a spaceship's energy shield, and a few punches would be enough to decimate the whole ship!

He had a worried expression on the whole time, constantly glancing at the battlefield where Han Xiao was. He had noticed the appearance of Degulish and company, and only then did he realise that their target was Black Star.

Nagakin wanted to turn around and provide assistance to Han Xiao, but the latter had informed him through his communicator that there was no need for assistance. Black Star himself would handle the three Calamity Grade Supers, whilst Nagakin would be in charge of attacking the spaceships.

The guy was mad!

Nagakin did not wish to imagine how Han Xiao was going to entangle with three Calamity Supers. If it was him, it would be equivalent to a death sentence!

Only after Han Xiao told him that he would definitely call upon him if he could not handle it any longer did Nagakin throw away his thoughts of reinforcing him. He had viewed Black Star's interactions with the upper echelons a few times and knew that this mercenary was extremely practical.

He would never sacrifice himself for a noble cause and would definitely have some assurance before he carried out his plan. Thus, he could only restrain his anxiety even though he did not know how Han Xiao was going to deal with the three of them.

Inside the protective shield, countless residents gazed with expressions of fear at the shield above their heads, which looked like it would shatter at any moment. This was their last line of defense. Everyone was so afraid that they were shaking and praying nonstop.

A portion of the DarkStar spaceships suddenly opened to release ground troops, which bypassed the protective shield to land on the ground. The tens of thousands of players immediately rushed forward to get a kill, and the inserted troops were drowned in the sea of players like pebbles, hardly even making a ripple.

With tens of thousands of Supers, all of whom were immortal, this sort of combat capability scared DarkStar into no longer carrying out a ground attack. The ground combatants of DarkStar all hugged on the doors of the spaceships, refusing to get off.

D*mn, how good it is to be in the air. I'm not going to send myself to my grave!

The DarkStar troops also could not be bothered to deal with those immortals, only focused on laying siege to the city. Because only a few of the players had the privilege of entering spaceships to fight in the aerial battle, the majority could only helplessly crane their necks up to look at the scene. A couple of people who had gotten bored out of their minds had already begun using their recording functions.

However, those people quickly found something else to do and all turned their heads to observe the earth shaking battlefield that Han Xiao was a part of.

...

Boom!

Degulish sent a fist through one of the tower shields of the G-1 Steel Army Corps warriors. The pugilist force radiated outward, and the surrounding mechanical warriors were also caught in the impact and blasted off.

Meanwhile, Terry rotated like a gyro, with a killing range of more than a hundred meters in diameter. The mechanical soldiers caught within his range were all cut into pieces.

With another two companions to suppress the firepower, Ember's black current could finally showcase its killing potential. The black current swept across like a tsunami, swallowing everything in its path. He alone destroyed over two thousand machines on his own.

The attack of three Calamity Grade Supers contained a terrifying destructive power. The number of machines in the mechanical army was reduced by a third in a short period of time. The losses were serious.

To use my current mechanical army to go against three Calamity Grades seems to be a little forced. Han Xiao had a solemn expression.

Those losses, however, were still within his expectations. A Calamity Grade was not that easy to deal with. With his current machines' performance, he had to sacrifice tens of thousands of cannon fodder before he could grind the energy of a Calamity Grade to zero. He also had to see what sort of ability the opponents had. If it was someone with an AOE skill such as Anur, then the difficulty would rise.

Thankfully, Ember's ability was better suited to go against carbon-based lifeforms. While it afforded both offense and defense, the consumption of energy was huge. Degulish was a pugilist, and while his single target offense was insanely high, he lacked an AOE skill. As a Mechanical Pugilist, Terry was the same. Thus, the mechanical army had some sort of effect on them, dragging out more time before the three of them could reach him.

However, Han Xiao only managed to dodge for a while before being pounced upon. At close range, he still fell into a passive state.

Degulish and Terry were both good at melee battles, so their offense was like a storm. Han Xiao could only defend. His energy shield was constantly being broken, and the Hovering Shield Shuttle had also been sliced in two. His giant mechanical hands had been blasted into smithereens, and he was only relying on the hardness of his Mechanical suit, with his HP slowly dwindling.

Whenever he commanded his mechanic army to rain fire, Ember would control his black current to withstand the gunfire and allow his teammates to focus on attacking Han Xiao.

The black current separated the mechanical army from Han Xiao, with the army outside and Han Xiao on the inside. While the mechanical army wished to rush inside to aid Han Xiao, they were all repelled by Ember. Because their numbers had dwindled, the pressure on Ember was a lot weaker as well, and he now had the energy to occasionally fire a shot at Han Xiao.

Only the eight Oathkeepers constantly guarded Han Xiao's side. They assisted in his battle but were broken one by one. The Oathkeepers were elite machines, and under the mechanical bonus given by Han Xiao, they had the ability to fight against a Grade B Super alone. However, this time, the opponent was Calamity Grade, and there were even three of them!

Bang!

The last Oathkeeper was viciously kicked by Degulish, and its mechanical parts spilled out like intestines. This was closely followed by Degulish grabbing its head and yanking it off, splashing its surroundings with motor oil. There were still a few sparking wires on its neck

"Whatever else you still have, call it all out." Degulish threw away the Oathkeeper's head, speaking arrogantly.

The eight Oathkeepers had all collapsed, and Han Xiao was half kneeling on the ground, coughing nonstop. His mechanical suit was quite damaged and was spraying sparks.

In his surroundings was the black current, blocking all his mechanical army through the control of Ember.

Han Xiao took a breath as he checked his status. His HP was still at eighty-two percent, his energy having just returned to full. However, his mechanical suit had sustained quite a bit of damage and was already at eight percent durability, activating its skill [Indestructible Toughness]. This gave him some immunity, but he needed to receive damage to his body to activate [Energy Absorption].

The Void Dragon Mechanical suit was decent equipment, and he had used it for a long time, with it being able to keep up with his promotion in Grades. Han Xiao did not wish to lose this Mechanical suit, and seeing its durability hit rock-bottom, he quickly stowed the suit away, exposing his body to the three Calamity Grades.

Only then did the three of them finally see his face.

"Finally, you are willing to come out from your turtle shell." The corners of Ember's mouth curled up.

Once a Mechanic abandoned his mechanical suit and revealed his true body, it meant that he had been forced down the path of no return.

"Stop talking nonsense. Hurry up and kill him." Terry looked impatient as he shook the metal pieces, turning them into a blade brimming with energy.

At this juncture, Han Xiao suddenly stood up straight. His expression did not have much nervousness, and his composure caused the trio from DarkStar to frown in response.

"Don't rejoice too early. The battle has only just begun!"

As he spoke, Han Xiao stomped using his foot.

Hum!

Endless Mechanical Force spread from his feet into his surroundings, akin to a large spider web. It easily bypassed the black current, covering the entire battlefield.

The scraps and broken parts lying around all connected to each other, buzzing with a loud noise.

The next instant, countless metal scraps floated up into the air, and the deformed scraps recovered their original shapes through the Mechanical Force. They were speedily re-constructed into the original mechanical warriors. The destroyed portion of the mechanic army returned.

Within the black current, the eight sets of Oathkeepers stood up once again, and one of them retrieved its head that had been thrown away, reinstalling it on its head with a click.

[Waste Modification]!

The destroyed machines were all repaired once more!

Looking at the eight sets of reformed Oathkeepers, Degulish and the others' expressions dropped.

"This guy has a lot of tricks!" Terry snorted.

"It's futile. Without his mechanical suit, he's dead meat," Degulish retorted in anger.

Ember coldly glowered. The current strength of the mechanical army had been restored, and the pressure on him sharply increased. He could not afford to attack Han Xiao any longer and could only concentrate on resisting the mechanical army.

Han Xiao's face had blanched. Using [Waste Modification] on such a large scale was extremely taxing on his energy levels. His filled energy bar had already gone down by half in just a few moments!

The consumption of this skill depended on both the area of coverage and the number of machines. At the same time, it measured through a coefficient of 0.x, where x was a variable. After multiplying everything, that would be equivalent to his energy consumption. The higher the level, the smaller this coefficient would become. Thus, as a Mechanic's level increased, the cost of [Waste Modification] would naturally become cheaper.

Boom!

The next second, Degulish and Terry threw themselves forward once again and attacked with the force of a storm, reigniting the battle!

A fist harshly landed on Han Xiao's body, and the metal alloy blade slashed out wound after wound on his flesh.

Without his mechanical suit bonus, Han Xiao became more passive. He was continuously hit with heavy blows, spilling out mouthfuls of blood. It looked as though he was at his wits' end. The Calamity Grade Supers' attacks were powerful, and when landing on his body, they caused thousands of damage per second to him.

However, after beating him up for long period of time, Degulish finally discovered that something was amiss.

Wait a minute!

This guy has spat out so many liters of blood. How is he still so active‽

If Degulish could see Han Xiao's interface, he would see that his health and energy bars were constantly moving up and down. When the red rose, the blue fell, and when the red fell, the blue rose. While it looked scary, the total amount of HP never dropped less than half.

While Han Xiao looked bedraggled and terribly wounded, in actuality, he was as stable as an old dog without any sense of panic!

Every second he took several thousand points of damage, and with the crazy damage done, his energy bar likewise shot up crazily. While Degulish and Terry had great killing power, it could not keep up with the pace of Han Xiao's thought commands!

Han Xiao secretly relaxed. After this personal experiment, he finally discovered the tenacity of his vitality. Even the Aurora Character Summon Card that he had prepared in advance did not need to be used any longer!

[Middle Grade Cell Proliferation Control].

[Energy Absorption].

Those two Molding Abilities were just too OP!

Long live ol' buddy Feidin[1]!

While he was not in mortal danger, he still felt the pain from being beaten up. However, compared to the pain he felt when undergoing his Race Evolution, this was like scratching an itch, almost a sort of massage.

Degulish had beat him up for half a day, his expressions constantly changing from viciousness to surprise, surprise to shock, and finally from shock to dumbfoundedness.

No matter how much strength they put into it, causing Black Star to vomit blood, there was no sign of serious injuries from the other party. He could still run, jump, and open his mouth to trash talk.

Not just Degulish, but even Terry was also stunned.

What the f*ck? This guy is too f*cked up!

Is he a cockroach‽ Why won't he just die‽

Bang!

Another blow came, causing Han Xiao to fly back and slam heavily into the ground, creating a crater. Degulish and Terry, however, did not continue attacking. Instead, they stood back, suspicious as to whether they were actually fighting Han Xiao.

"Ah? Why are we not fighting anymore?"

Wiping the blood off the corners of his mouth, Han Xiao stood up once more. His clothes were covered in bloodstains, and after wiping off the dust off his body, he suddenly flashed a smile, as though he was full of energy.

"Are you done? I'm not comfortable enough yet. Put more effort into this. Did you guys not drink your milk?"

Ember's pupils shrank, and he had an expression of disbelief. He remembered the past when he had first fought with Han Xiao back on Floating Dragon Island. Han Xiao had showcased his incredible healing ability, eventually forcing him to retreat.

At that time, Ember had thought that Han Xiao's ability definitely had a limit; as long as the lethality was sufficient, it would be enough to wipe him out. At least, he had thought so until then.

However, Han Xiao had merely used his fleshy body to withstand the attacks of two Calamity Grade Supers, and even the earth had been levelled, yet he was still hale and hearty!

At this moment, Ember started to sway.

Could it be... that he was wrong from the start and that this guy's recovery ability had no limits‽

Then, was he... not an immortal freak that could not be killed‽

Just as the trio stared in shock, from afar came the rumbling of footsteps, as though tens of thousands of troops were marching. Even the ground started to tremor.

They only saw the tens of thousands of players rushing toward Han Xiao with great momentum. Since they could not reach the spaceships in the air, they had decided to join the fun.

While they were all low-grade Supers, with more than 10,000 of them, many of whom had broken past the level 60 mark and achieved their first Race Evolution, they could be considered a group of dancing devils.

"Seeking death. I'll deal with this group; you think of an idea to get rid of Black Star."

Ember restrained the fear and shock in his heart, his eyes flashing with a cold glow. He prepared to use his ability to decimate this entire group.

Idea? What ideas could they have?

Degulish gritted his teeth, finally opening his communicator and sending an order up to the mothership.

"Activate the mothership's main ray cannon!"

"Your Excellency, where should we aim?"

"Hit that d*mned Black Star!"

Not far away, Han Xiao's Cheshire grin suddenly froze on his face.

He had hit the motherload this time!

[1] For readers who have forgotten, Han Xiao touched Feidin all over before drawing these two skills. Back

Chapter 572: Tanking the Main Cannon‽ (1)

The mothership's main ray cannon!

Only then did Han Xiao begin to panic. The lethality of the main cannon far outstripped that of the laser cannons attached to the side of the ship. Based on the size of this DarkStar mothership, one shot toward the planet could create a new trench. Using it just to deal with him was like using a cannon to kill a mosquito!

Was I too vicious to Degulish earlier? Han Xiao could not help but reflect.

If he had known about this, he would have exercised more restraint earlier, screaming out in misery and pretending that he had been severely wounded. At the very least, that was showing respect to their hard work! For him to sneer at them, he had trampled on their pride!

The other party was a Calamity Grade—how could they not be shown some face?

Han Xiao had no idea how much a blast of the main cannon would damage him. While he had proven the tenacity of his flesh through proper battle, it was another question to take the blast from a mothership's main cannon head-on!

The nemesis of having fast recovery was an explosive burst attack. For example, if Ames unreasonably took the whole of Floating Dragon and threw it as an attack, the damage inflicted would far outstrip the rate of recovery; he would certainly die!

The main cannon of the mothership belonged to that of the high damage category. While it was far from being able to compare to a planetary destroyer, its killing power was able to disintegrate a Calamity Grade if they merely used their fleshly body to withstand it. If they were lucky, they might still have a few charred pieces of flesh remaining.

As such, only a fool would stay and accept the cannon blast!

Han Xiao did not say a single word, immediately donning his still persevering Void Dragon Mechanical suit and flying toward the sky.

The BlackLight Stealth dived down, ready to take Han Xiao in.

"Stay here!" Ember turned his attention away from the players, and with a wave of his hand, the black current soared out to capture Han Xiao.

However, the speed of the black current was far from comparable to the maximum speed of the Void Dragon mechanical suit.

At this point, Degulish's head popped out multiple veins as he bent his legs, stomping and destroying the ground in a hundred-meter radius around him. In an instant, he appeared above Han Xiao's head, and a swirling vortex gathered around his fist. A piercing light could be seen dazzling from within; that was a Pugilist skill that Han Xiao had suffered from more than once previously.

Han Xiao only had the time to raise his arms, and the glowing fist hit the direct center of his crossed arms.

Bang!

It was as though the sky had exploded into a purple sun!

A forceful shock rushed toward Han Xiao, and being in midair, he had no way to transfer the impact. His vision blurred, and he only saw the BlackLight Stealth rapidly moving away from himself, followed by a heavy impact coming from his back. His entire body was slammed into the ground, and rubble covered him. Only a tiny pinprick of the sky was left in his vision.

This explosive fist had knocked Han Xiao straight from the sky into the ground.

His arms were weak and full of pain, with the interface showing the [Fractured] state on his panel. Han Xiao secretly lamented about how the fist strength of a Calamity Grade Pugilist was indeed extraordinary, even while he urged his energy to increase cell proliferation, swiftly healing his wounds.

The fractured bones were held in place through the contractions of his muscles, and with the increased proliferation of cells, the bones were connected in the blink of an eye.

Cell proliferation could repair damage inflicted to any part of the body. So long as it was repaired consciously, the negative conditions such as fractures or handicaps would also be recovered while recovering HP. This was a side bonus that Han Xiao had discovered when he was being beaten up, or else all his bones would have broken by now.

Dong! Dong!

Before he could even take a breath, the rubble above his head was blasted open as Degulish directly smashed through the ground. With his fists continuously hitting the ground, he resembled a human bulldozer.

Han Xiao did not wish to be buried alive, so he knocked away the falling rubble and flew out. However, Ember's black current shot forward at this point, blocking him for a moment.

"I've got you!"

Degulish rushed up with big steps, grabbing Han Xiao's waist in a bear hug. He quickly changed his position to move behind Han Xiao, his hands forming a lock as he wanted to use his strength to suppress Han Xiao's movements.

Comparing by Strength, Han Xiao was definitely not a match for the Calamity Grade Pugilist, and thus did not wish to tango with him at all.

Swoosh!

At that moment, Terry also took the chance. Several metal pieces elongation, piercing toward Han Xiao's eyes, throat, heart, and other vital areas.

Clank!

The two Oathkeepers shielded Han Xiao from the deluge of metal. Each time he used [Waste Modification], the quality of the machinery would be reduced by a level. Thus, the Oathkeepers did not manage to block off much of the metal projectiles before they were pierced into beehives. However, they managed to buy Han Xiao some precious time.

Han Xiao fully activated his mechanical suit propulsion module, bringing Degulish with him as he rushed toward the sky to avoid the assault from Terry.

Even after struggling twice, Han Xiao was still unable to disengage himself from Degulish's lock. Thus, he changed his method. The legs of the mechanical suit suddenly split open, and Han Xiao slid out from his suit, easily escaping. At the same time, he utilized the Mechanical Force to disintegrate the Void Dragon Mechanical suit, allowing it to form up around him once again.

Degulish was left hugging the air and immediately fell back to the ground.

The threat of the mothership main cannon gripped his heart, and with every additional second of delay, Han Xiao felt the danger increase another notch. However, with Degulish and Terry eyeing him, any attempt made to fly toward the sky would be blocked.

The BlackLight Stealth could only hover above his head and did not dare get too close to the Calamity Grade Supers because it would be torn apart if it did.

The time taken for the battle had already past five minutes, and the cooldown for his [Void Travel] was over. Han Xiao wanted to use the skill to rush toward his spaceship, but once he entered the void travel state, he would phase through all matter, unable to affect any matter. Even his mechanical suit would be useless, and he would only be able to float using his mechanical force. The duration afforded by [Void Travel] was insufficient for him to fly manually into the spaceship.

Things are not looking so good...

Han Xiao felt a sense of helplessness in his heart and turned to rush toward the tens of thousands of players.

So long as those 'foot soldiers' could buy some time by delaying the three Calamity Grade Supers, he would be able to escape the battlefield. The saying was true, 'one trains soldiers for thousands of days just to use them during an opportune moment'.

Ember snapped his fingers a few times.

Pa pa pa...

The tens of thousands of players saw their HP get reduced to 0, and they turned into white motes as they were sent to revive.

Ember's ability was just that overpowered. If one did not have the ability to resist true damage, so long as they were weaker than him, they were not qualified to fight against him. Numbers did not mean a thing to him, which was why he was regarded as a killing machine by DarkStar. He could effortlessly slaughter millions in the blink of an eye.

...

The tens of thousands of players simultaneously revived in the square, stunned in place.

"F*ck, I died just like that!"

"Carbon dissociation? True Damage‽ This Boss is broken!"

"I'm out of here. It's obvious that Black Star's battlefield is not something that we can affect."

"That was part of the storyline killing us."

The storyline killing quickly spread, and the majority of players present believed in it, not going over to join the activities. In the game, they could only die ten times every six days, so the players did not wish to spend their limited death entries on such a pointless storyline action. Thus, they simply chose to crane their necks and watch Han Xiao's fight.

This was also not the first time that they had watched a storyline plot. The period in Version 1.0 when the Six Nations warred against the Germinal Organization, as well as the resolving of the Mutation Source earlier, had already prepared the players for it... Come to think of it, it seemed like Planet Aquamarine had quite a number of storylines. Wow.

Everyone felt that this time was also a personal storyline of Black Star and was curious as to the development of the plot.

In the eyes of the players, to have Planet Aquamarine meet with such a crisis, it signified the transition that they were about to leave the novice planet, which should be part of the plot.

As the leader of the Guiding Faction, Black Star would be their head for a long period of time. Therefore, many of the players hypothesized that Black Star would likely shine in this event, leaving an even deeper impression. However, they were unable to predict what would truly happen.

...

Seeing the tens of thousands of players brushing their butts and sauntering off, Han Xiao could not stop the corners of his mouth twitching.

Tut, looks like I can't rely on this group of players. The gap between them and the Calamity Grade Supers is too great.

Degulish and the other two encircled Han Xiao in a triangular formation but did not proceed to close in on him, maintaining some distance.

The three of them did not wish to allow Han Xiao to escape, but they also did not wish to take the cannon blast together with him. The cannon blast was not going to differentiate between friend or foe.

"Risda, is there any way to stop the firing of the mothership cannon?" Han Xiao asked softly into his communicator.

"I have no way to go about it. I infiltrated another mothership and can only help you to check the situation... Oh no, the charging of the main cannon is complete, and the target has already been locked on. You have roughly 8.6 seconds left."

"Seems like I can't avoid the blast. Ok, let's go. I can tank this..."

Han Xiao could only attempt to motivate himself. He threw out a few compressed orbs, which expanded into layers of alloy covers. This was a portable tactical defense fortress that could be used for protection. It had no other effect than that being extremely durable.

This was closely followed by the mechanical soldiers throwing themselves on Han Xiao, on top of the portable defense fortress, using their bodies as shields. They also activated their own shields and faced the sky.

Degulish and the others did not wish to enter the blasting radius of the cannon and would turn a blind eye as long as Black Star did not escape. Thus, they turned around and attacked the mechanical army around them. While only a small portion passed through the three of them to reach the defense fortress, the defense line constantly got thicker.

The remaining shuttles and mechanical hands also flew up into the sky and activated their shields.

Han Xiao had released almost all his machinery for defense, and he did not know how much they could offset. Thus, he recovered his HP back to the maximum and concentrated his energy, readying himself to use Aurora's Character Summon Card.

At that moment, Degulish, who was blocking the mechanical army, received a notification from the mothership. The three of them stopped their actions immediately, retreating far away.

"The deed is done. Black Star cannot avoid this!"

Degulish revealed a satisfied smile. They had chased after him and blocked Han Xiao from escaping, all in order to allow the main cannon to lock onto and hit Black Star. This was the method with the highest possibility of killing him.

At that moment, within the defensive fortress, Han Xiao raised his alertness to the highest, as well as activating the skill [Repel—Thorns], which he had obtained for the Germinal Organization Leader. The skill would offset thirty percent of the damage received from the next attack.

"It's coming!"

Chapter 573: Tanking the Main Cannon‽ (2)

The speed of the main cannon was undoubtedly fast, and now that he had been locked on to, there was no point in him trying to dodge. The entire process from the firing of the cannon to the time it hit was measured in milliseconds. Even Degulish and the other two had to move away before the cannon was fired.

Since he was unable to board the BlackLight Stealth, he could not hope to avoid the impact of the cannon fire with his own speed. His [Void Travel] skill might be able to avoid one shot, but so long as the main cannon remained active, they would just need to fire another shot if they saw him dodge.

Instead, it would be better for him to use the limited amount of time to stack all the defenses he had, then use the [Repel—Thorns] skill as a guarantee and find out the damage of the cannon. With so many measures, his chances of survival should be quite high, and if he survived, it would be able to work as a bluff to scare the enemy.

Having thought of this, a horrific energy was detected. He had just felt it when the entire attack had already arrived.

Han Xiao hunkered down in his fortress. He could not see the outside perspective of the cannon ray being shot down and could only feel through the feedback of his Mechanical Force when the various shields shattered, and his numerous mechanical soldiers were destroyed. A piercing white light filled his vision, and horrible heat covered his entire body.

Boom!

A huge force seemed to press down upon him like a mountain, slapping Han Xiao flat on the ground and wrapping him in the energy column of the main cannon. His field of vision was blank, and the energy ray rushed down continuously like a waterfall, forcing him to remain prone.

His HP levels rapidly dropped, and even with the thirty percent reduced damage from the skill, the first impact reduced his total HP by a third. The subsequent high temperature and energy shock caused continuous damage after that, rapidly sapping away his HP. Han Xiao could not move, and only felt his flesh and blood melt and evaporate as various negative statuses appeared on his interface.

If it was an ordinary person, just the cannon blast would have disintegrated them. Even dregs would not have remained.

Han Xiao gritted his teeth as he activated the skill [Middle Grade Cell Proliferation Control] to replenish his HP as fast as possible. Every tick would allow him to regain twenty-eight percent of his HP. This allowed him to break even with the falling HP level. The gauge continuously jumped up and down, giving him goosebumps, and he prepared to activate Aurora's Character Summon Card at any time.

To recover more than 10,000 HP every second would be equivalent to using 2,000 to 3,000 Onas of Energy. Luckily, with the cannon dealing damage to him, it provided him with an inexhaustible supply of energy, allowing him to fully display his HP recovery abilities.

The interface was flooded with notifications about receiving damage. While the attack from the main cannon also contained a portion of true damage, it was nullified by Han Xiao's talent of [Steel Body]. This point was critical, as it helped to reduce a large portion of damage taken by him, thus allowing him to only suffer the regular damage.

A few seconds earlier...

Yet another DarkStar spaceship was shot down, and wreathed in flames, Nagakin briefly paused in midair, looking down Han Xiao's battlefield, the surprise in his eyes evident.

Black Star really managed to withstand the attacks of three Calamity Grades! How has he achieved that‽

Nagakin was extremely surprised, as even he could not achieve that level.

At this point, he realized that there were changes to the battlefield. He only saw that Black Star was constantly imposing defenses on top of himself, whereas the three Calamity Grades had somehow scampered away, as though hiding from something dangerous.

"Why have they stopped fighting? What is Black Star defending himself against?"

Nagakin had a confused expression on. However, before he could think about the reason, the answer was presented to him.

Swoosh!

A huge beam of light shot down from the skies, connecting heaven and earth to strike Han Xiao's position. The word 'strike' might be a little inaccurate, as the beam was a good few hundred meters wide!

From the sky to the ground, the time taken for the beam to traverse the distance was quicker than the blink of an eye. Even with Nagakin's reaction speed, he did not have time to take any countermeasures and could only squint to resist the strong light.

Bang!

The cannon blasted out a new landmark!

It was akin to a spear of God stabbing straight into the earth. It gave off the illusion that it could penetrate this planet, striking an intense sense of shock in everyone!

The light was piercing, and Nagakin struggled to open his eyes as his expression constantly changed.

Were they nuts‽ To actually use the main cannon just to deal with a single target...

How did Black Star manage to rile them up so much‽

Boom!

The next moment, a violent explosion occurred. The shockwaves spread from the epicenter, and debris and soil was blown outward from the point of impact.

The DarkStar mothership's main cannon utilized a separate energy furnace that was dedicated to it. Thus, its killing power was many times higher than that of its light weapons. While the light weapons were focused on penetrative power, the main cannon was geared more toward 'single target' damage. Of course, if one was so crazy as to use the main cannon to hit an individual, then the effect was no different from an AOE.

The main cannon continued to release energy, the terrifying high temperatures distorting the air as shockwaves constantly blasted outward. The earth roiled, and the area covered by the cannon beam had turned into a ring-shaped depression while still continuously expanding.

Inside the protective shield, the faces of countless players were illuminated by the white light, and their expressions were slack, with only that beam of light in their vision.

Was that... Heaven's Judgement‽

Xiu!

The main cannon stopped firing, and only a final glare could be seen disappearing from the core of the crater, flickering.

Boom!

The accumulated energy within suddenly imploded, the resulting sound from the explosion louder than before. Flames and smoke spread out at a high speed, as though it was an opening umbrella.

Heated winds swept out, and the mountains trembled!

Even those hiding inside the protective shield felt the violent tremors.

It was only after a long while that the energy within eventually dispersed. Smoke obscured the vision of everyone present, and one could only see that there was a huge crater left in the outer sector of the Sanctuary, as though a meteor had struck there.

"What was that?"

The hearts of countless of players present shook.

Even Bennett felt a little lost for words.

Hila slammed herself on the protective shield, her pupils shrinking into tiny points as she stared.

Nagakin stood on top of the protective shield with a worried expression as he gazed at the position of where Han Xiao was, the center of the crater that was surrounded by smoke.

Degulish, Ember, and Terry stood up, their faces covered in soot. They had attempted running right before the cannon fired and were knocked off their feet by the incoming debris and soil waves, landing in different locations. After standing up, they simultaneously looked at the crater, wanting to know the outcome.

All the DarkStar and Godoran spaceships suddenly ceased firing, floating in the sky as they watched the outcome below.

After the smoke dispersed, one could see that the center of the crater was several meters deep. The slope was steep, and the soil got redder in color the lower it got. There were many areas that had crystallized due to the high temperature, with some rocks having melted into magma, gleaming as it flowed down the slope.

Countless mechanical fragments were scattered around, with some having been melted into molten iron, glowing red-hot.

At the middle of the crater, a figure slowly climbed up, his burnt body radiating smoke. He was blacker than the night sky, and after shuddering a few times, the burnt scraps on his body fell off, revealing pale skin. With a zap of the Mechanical Force from his hands, several pieces of machinery transformed into a pair of pants to cover his lower body.

Han Xiao stood there, his upper body bare, supporting the back of his neck with one hand as he stretched and revealed a smile.

"Huff... that was intense. I can feel my whole body becoming more comfortable!"

Everybody's gaze landed on Han Xiao, their mouths agape.

He... he didn't die‽

The energetic and spritely Black Star contrasted with the crater that was full of death.

This scene caused Degulish, Terry, Ember, Nagakin, Hila, and the players to suffer from near mental breakdowns, their eyes bulging open with an expression of shock.

Chapter 574: Tanking the Main Cannon‽ (3)

"Even the mothership's main cannon could not kill him‽"

Degulish opened his eyes wide in disbelief.

Ember's fists were clenched tight, his face pale.

Terry shuddered, with an expression of shock.

The battlefield was dead silent!

Han Xiao glanced at the machinery scattered around him, and a hint of pain flashed across his eyes. He was alright, but the majority of his Mechanical Army had been demolished. This time, his losses were huge. Right now, he had over 10 million Enas, and Godora still owed him another 15 million Enas, so money was not a problem.

The main problem was the time needed to rebuild the entire Mechanical Army. After this battle, he would probably have to spend a long time in the machinery modification room to restore the current size of his army.

The Great Mechanic Han counted the notifications on his interface, which indicated the duration of the main cannon shot and the damage inflicted. It was divided into several tiers, with the first impact the highest, gradually decreasing after. It accumulated to more than 50,000 damage in total, higher than his own HP. Most of it was soaked up by himself, with his machinery and shields having absorbed a portion of it.

Having experienced it once, Han Xiao had a good gauge now. If he did not have his defensive measures in place, directly receiving the impact with his body, he would have been hit by a total of more than 80,000 damage. His own HP would not have been able to keep up, and he would most likely have been required to use Aurora's Character Summon Card. There were three usages left. Plus, he still had his [Void Travel] skill.

I can hold on a few more times. There's no need to escape right now. I can give this mission another shot. Why not?

Han Xiao's eyes flashed, and with a wave of his hand, the hull of the BlackLight Stealth opened, spewing out dozens of compressed orbs. He used his Mechanical Force to draw them onto his body, unfolding the spare Amphiptere mechanical suit. Since he always had a habit of storing spare machinery, he had placed several sets of equipment in his spaceship's warehouse.

The original mechanical suit and compressed orbs that he had on his body were all smashed. Even his Void Dragon Mechanical suit could not withstand the impact. However, the void dragon bones were durable, and most of his core materials were not completely damaged, just scattered around the area. Moreover, with his current position in Floating Dragon, to apply for a few pieces of Void Dragon bones was an easy task for him.

Putting on his mechanical suit, Han Xiao leaped out of the deep crater, hovering in midair as he looked straight at a dumbfounded Degulish. He utilized his thick skin to teasingly say, "Heh heh, I tricked you. Actually, that hit was quite effective. Do you want to try again? Who knows? You might be able to kill me."

Degulish could hear the mocking inside his words and was so angered that his entire face turned purple. He lost control and bellowed into the communicator, "Continue firing!"

Since one cannon shot could not finish him off, make it two! I don't believe he can last that long!

Degulish leaped up, and like a cannon shell, he rushed straight toward Han Xiao. The mothership's main cannon required time to recharge, and he had to tie down Han Xiao to prevent him from escaping. Seeing the situation, Ember and Terry could only put aside their emotions to deal with the matter at hand and cooperate with Degulish.

"Black Star, the mothership's main cannon has begun the second round of charging." From his helmet, Risda's voice sounded.

"Show me the duration," Han Xiao replied.

On the upper left-hand corner of his tactical screen, a row of numbers appeared, counting down. The second blast of the main cannon would be fully charged and fire after forty seconds.

Han Xiao and the other three once again started to fight. The durability of Amphiptere was far below that of the Void Dragon Mechanical suit, and it was not long before it was reduced to scrap metal. However, he still had a few more compressed orbs containing different mechanical suits, and he merely kept replacing them after they were destroyed.

Thirty seconds soon passed. The moment the second shot would be fired was getting closer.

Having once again smashed Han Xiao into the ground, Degulish and the others moved away to avoid the blast.

However, this time was different. Han Xiao did not remain on the spot to prepare his defenses but rather lunged toward Terry who was nearest to him.

The fact that Han Xiao was aware of the timing was not surprising to them, because after the previous scenario, he could easily have inferred that the cannon strike was coming when they started to avoid him.

"He wants to drag Terry down with him?"

Degulish immediately understood Han Xiao's intention. He was not surprised and only snorted coldly as he muttered, "He'll never catch up to Terry."

As a Calamity Grade, Terry's speed surpassed Han Xiao's. Even at his full speed, the distance between the two was constantly widening. Based on this scenario, Han Xiao could never catch up to Terry.

Ember suddenly lurched to a stop, screaming out, "No, hurry and stop the cannon! Black Star has a teleportation ability!"

In his previous battle, Han Xiao had used his skill [Void Travel] once. It was to stop Ember from utilizing his Esper ability, and Ember had almost been kicked in the crotch. Thus, his impression of that was deep.

Having been reminded, Degulish's expression dropped as he grabbed his communicator and bellowed.

"Trouble! Cancel the lock on now!"

At that moment, Han Xiao activated [Void Travel] and flashed across the remaining distance to appear beside Terry, an evil grin on his face.

"Hehe, come, let's bet who can last longer this time."

"No!"

Terry's face drastically changed, a hint of fear appearing on his face together with a 'Don't-come-closer' look.

Boom!

The next moment, the second shot was fired from the cannon, and another mountain range appeared.

Explosions, debris, soil flew everywhere, just like the previous scene. Everyone inside the protective shield felt the tremors once more.

When the smoke disappeared, everyone discovered that the aim of the cannon was off, tens of miles away from where Han Xiao was supposed to be.

At the very last second, the commander of the DarkStar mothership had hurriedly shifted the muzzle of the cannon.

Terry stood rooted, his mouth agape, as he stared at the crater far away from him. His whole body was covered in cold sweat, and he immediately escaped from Han Xiao to a few thousand kilometers away.

Having escaped the jaws of death, Terry still felt trepidation at what had occurred, heaving and gasping for breath.

"Well, count yourself lucky."

Han Xiao remained where he was, his mouth twisted, thinking it a pity.

If DarkStar did not have the chance to react, he would have been able to give his enemies a taste of their own medicine. Through killing with this borrowed knife... no, cannon, he would get rid of a Calamity Grade Super, obtaining his repayment with interest and at the same time having one less enemy.

Even so, it served its purpose. Han Xiao shook his head, turning back to look at Degulish and company. He waved his hands, revealing a look of apology.

"What next? Are you still firing?"

"You..."

Degulish almost broke his teeth as he clenched his jaws, almost crushing his communicator as well. However, he did not dare use the same tactic on Han Xiao anymore.

Black Star had received the first shot, and they had almost killed Terry with the next shot. Those two shots proved that the main cannon was useless against Black Star and could even backfire on them!

The three Calamity Grade could not kill Black Star, and even the mothership's main cannon with the highest lethality could not stop him. This allowed them to discover a point—even though it was Black Star that could not defeat them, the advantage had fallen into his hands! Before this, they never would have thought that a little fellow who was not even Calamity Grade would be so troublesome!

He could not be beaten to death, nor could he be killed. Then, could they take him up to the ship?

Degulish immediately vetoed this idea. What a joke! Why would anyone take this malicious star onto their own spaceship?

At that moment, an urgent message came through the communicator.

"There's a strong spatial fluctuation detected nearby. Godora's fleet has broken through the lock down in space, and their reinforcements are approaching us through hyperdrive. We do not have much time and must retreat."

Han Xiao had also received news from Nagakin at the same time and heaved a sigh of relief. The Godoran reinforcements had arrived, albeit a bit late, but it was better late than never.

Degulish's face was extremely ugly to behold. He had no other choice but to accept that their mission had failed this time. Because they had been delayed too long by Han Xiao, they were not able to cause greater damage to Planet Aquamarine.

The DarkStar troops began to retreat, and Degulish and company retreated from the flight, boarding the spaceship to take over command.

At that moment, the three of them heard the light laugh from Han Xiao.

"Come and play when you have the time!"

Han Xiao smiled as he waved, adding another sentence in his heart—If you still have the chance to do so.

"Just you wait, I'll see if you still can laugh in the future!"

Degulish had a dark expression as he turned to enter the spaceship.

Ember deeply looked at Han Xiao... Next time, I'll definitely find a way to kill you.

The DarkStar troops began to retreat, and the mothership that remained in outer space also took its leave.

Because the reinforcements sent by Godora were overly huge this time, along with the escort teams from all the other Calamity planets coming over, DarkStar did not wish to exchange fire and hurriedly retreated.

After watching the DarkStar motherships depart, Han Xiao shifted his gaze, looking around at the devastated Sanctuary as his smile slowly vanished. He exhaled heavily.

This time, their losses were heavy.

The main base was still fine, but the outer sections of the Sanctuary had been wrecked, becoming a pile of debris. The death count had not been tallied, but it would not be far from their estimations. In addition to the losses of the Six Nations, the number of dead and injured would reach tens of thousands.

They had scraped through the Mutation Disaster, but the survivors had now experienced another calamity, causing their civilization to receive a big hit.

The only good news was that Planet Aquamarine's civilization did not completely die out.

"Bennett, count the losses and treat the wounded."

With a sigh, Han Xiao used the communicator to issue some instructions before he plopped down on the ground, facing the sky.

Once the pressure vanished, all the pain burst forth, and it attacked his body in waves, causing him to feel like not moving a single muscle.

This battle had truly tired him out.

Thankfully, though the losses were huge, the outcome was still reasonable. At least it was over.

Over on Nagakin's side, he gazed on with a complicated expression at Han Xiao, who was lying on the ground, with the horror in his heart still surging.

While DarkStar had taken advantage of the unprotected Planet Aquamarine and launched an attack with three Calamity Grade Supers, their siege was fruitless. Even the main cannon could not kill Black Star, and in contrast, because of Black Star's actions, they had prevented the planet from being destroyed and even forced them to retreat!

Nagakin could imagine, in the following period, how much this news would shake the Shattered Star Ring!

Chapter 575: Mission Reward, Plan Preparations

A series of notifications popped up on Han Xiao's interface.

[Planet Aquamarine's Crisis] has been completed!

You have received 620,000 Experience.

+2 Garton Star System Renown

+1,500 Planet Aquamarine: Six Nations Faction Favorability

[Assassination Target] has been completed!

You have received 12,100,000 Experience.

+30 Garton Star System Renown

+1,000 Godora Faction Favorability

You have received 1 Legendary Point.

Both tasks were completed in one go. Han Xiao glanced at the notifications. His renown in the Garton Star System had not been low to start with. When the news spreads, there would still be an additional increase in renown. After this battle, his renown would probably take another step forward and attain the tier of [Famous Far and Wide], allowing him to join the list of notable characters in the star system.

He even got a new Legendary Point.

Star System Legendary Point (Garton Star System): Battling against Three Calamities—You were besieged by three Grade A Supers, facing them alone, but you were not defeated in the end. This proves your strength! This is a legendary deed, enough to make anyone who hears of this feel surprised and intrigued. Those who know you will recognize your ability, and your deeds will be sung throughout the galaxy!

The Legendary Point of a Star System had wider coverage than Planetary Legendary Points. This would help to increase his rewards. While the Planetary Legendary Point gave an increase of five percent in rewards, the Star System Legendary Point gave twelve percent. This was also Han Xiao's first Legendary Point of the Star System.

Other than the mission reward, the NPC template was updated with a new dungeon along with a title.

[Warfare: Defense of Planet Aquamarine]

What an unexpected joy. Han Xiao's eyes sparkled.

Only the more sensational battles would result in the generation of a dungeon copy. A similar one to this dungeon would be the [Warfare: Power of the Dragon Emperor]. This meant that his battle had reached the level that was deemed worthy of being saved as a copy.

The rewards were easily dealt with. At this point, the Godoran spaceships slowly landed from the sky, and the commander brought a whole bunch of subordinates down as he briskly walked over.

"DarkStar installed a space disruptor. We're late because of that and allowed them to escape. How's the situation here?"

As he spoke, the gaze of the fleet commander slowly drifted toward the crater blasted by the main cannon. His heart sank as he thought that the mission had failed, and Planet Aquamarine had suffered from irreparable damage.

"The enemy did not succeed..." Nagakin briefly summarized the happenings, including the actions of Han Xiao. He heavily emphasized the fight between Han Xiao and DarkStar.

As he listened, the Godoran commander, alongside with his subordinates, changed the way they looked at Han Xiao. The disbelief in their faces was clear to see.

To resist three Calamity Grades, and even be able to tank the mothership main cannon blast, this was too overpowered. Just by looking at the surrounding battle scars, the Godorans could tell how intense the battle had been.

The upper echelons of Godora were still anxiously awaiting the results. They did not care about Planet Aquamarine, but they did care about Han Xiao's safety. As long as Han Xiao remained alive, their intelligence transaction could continue.

When they received the news that three high-level combatants from DarkStar had been sent out, the upper echelons had felt their hearts grow cold, thinking that Black Star had been caught stealing information and thus had been wiped. However, the report from Nagakin surprised them.

To think that Black Star could actually go against three without being defeated! One had to know that he was not facing off against weaklings but rather Calamity Grade Supers! As for tanking the main cannon, such a level of strength caused even the knowledgeable Godoran superiors to be shocked.

The performance of Black Star was enough to rank him as a first-rate combatant!

Because the Sanctuary and the Six Nations had been damaged to varying degrees, people were organized to deal with it. Since the Godorans had arrived and needed camp for a while in case DarkStar decided to make a return trip, they pitched in to help clear up the wreckage.

There were ruined structures everywhere, and flames and smoke still lingered. Many of the wounded were still being dug out by the guards from the ruins, screaming miserably. There were also people who were weeping at the loss of their family. It was a scene of tragedy. Although DarkStar had been repelled, they had caused countless deaths, and the wounds would forever remain in the survivors' hearts.

Fortunately, many of the surviving residents did not have time to be sad, instead taking the initiative to join the disaster relief effort, contributing their strength.

Han Xiao took a short rest before walking in the direction of the base. Along the way, the participants of the disaster relief effort rushed about, brushing past him to save people. While no one stopped in front of him, all of them would nod toward Han Xiao as a sign of respect, their expressions carrying a hard-to-express gratitude.

After entering the base, Hila came over and looked him over once. She paused for a while before asking uncertainly, "Are you really not injured?"

"If you're injured, you can tell me. I can treat you," Aurora hurriedly added.

"I've faced a lot of such incidents." Han Xiao waved his hands as he boasted with a straight face.

"... Whatever floats your boat." Hila paused for a while and decided not to say anything more.

"Hehe, Sis was really worried about you just now." Aurora giggled.

Without waiting for Han Xiao to look over, Hila hurriedly explained, "If you died, then we probably would have died as well."

Han Xiao rolled his eyes in response and commented, "Being able to help me is better than saying anything."

Hila had never accepted Han Xiao's invitation directly, but this time, she did not deny anything. She slowly said, "I'll practice hard with the Dragon Emperor and become strong as quickly as possible."

"Me too!" Aurora raised her hand.

At this time, Bennett walked over from the side, his expression one of sorrow.

"The outer areas of the Sanctuary have almost been completely destroyed and can only be rebuilt. The losses of the Six Nations were even greater, with cities being completely reduced to nothing.

They are currently busy with disaster relief efforts, so let me thank you on their behalf for the reinforcements sent. Otherwise, the losses would have expanded even further. It is estimated that a total of twelve million people have been killed on Planet Aquamarine, and the number of injured and crippled might be several times this number."

"That's better than expected." Han Xiao nodded.

DarkStar's assault had only lasted around ten minutes but had already caused millions to perish. Their efficiency was shocking, and if not for the mercenaries, Nagakin, and the players, the casualties would have been much greater.

As for the Godoran reinforcements, they had actually come very quickly, attributed to the hyperdrive station that Godora had installed early on. If DarkStar was given more time, it would no longer have been a problem of deaths and injuries but rather if there were any living people left.

The destruction of the cities was even more serious, basically becoming scrap, and they all had to be rebuilt.

"Were those attackers from DarkStar?" Bennett asked.

Han Xiao only nodded.

"Abominable..." Bennett's expression was filled with helplessness and fury. Even if he clearly knew who the enemy was, he had no way to deal with them. He did not even possess the qualifications to talk to them and could only swallow this bitter pill. His eyes were filled with vengeance and hatred.

"Relax. I'll settle the problem of DarkStar soon. You do not need to worry." Han Xiao smiled.

Patting the shoulders of Bennett, Han Xiao then moved past several people, walking deep into the base. He only left a dwindling silhouette in the eyes of Hila and the rest.

Those few people seemed to see an illusion where the departing shadow of Han Xiao leaving the planet intersected with his current departing shadow. Before they knew it, this old acquaintance had already grown to the point where they could only look up to him.

Returning to his room, Han Xiao took a bath before putting on a fresh set of clothes. The battle had greatly consumed his stamina, and the moment he relaxed, his stomach growled in hunger. He finished more than twenty high-concentration nutrition bars before he felt some form of stamina returning.

Knock, knock, knock.

Knocking was heard from the door. Herlous stood outside with a group of his officers.

Because the majority of them had gone to support the Six Nations, they had only returned a while ago. Upon hearing of Han Xiao's battle results, the group was stunned and even thought that their captain had been mistaken for someone. Only after confirming this fact did they then accept it and immediately ran over to find Han Xiao.

The moment the door opened, everyone rushed into the room in an instant.

"I heard that you repelled three Calamity Grades, and even the main cannon could not hurt you!" Herlous had an expression of surprise, looking up and down Han Xiao before speaking in confusion. "When did you become so powerful? Why was I unaware of it?"

"If we have time, we can fight a round. Then you'll find out."

"This... better not." Herlous shuddered out of reflex.

Their previous fight could barely be considered a spar, but now it would just be a one-sided beatdown. Herlous did not indulge in being abused, and it seemed like he could only beat his captain through playing cards.

Han Xiao smiled before turning around to see Sylvia staring at him with sparkling eyes.

"Teacher, I want to learn this!"

"Scram, why the f*ck do you want to learn everything?"

"No... I really want to learn!"

"You can stop thinking about it. That's something that cannot be learned."

The little face of Sylvia drooped down as she huffed. "Unfair. Why is it like this?"

On the side, Ginette batted her eyes and licked her lips. "Captain, turns out you were this strong. Should we one day... try it out?"

"You can find Harmon for that. I'm not interested." Han Xiao's lips twitched.

As though he had received a cue, Harmon scratched his head, turning over to look at Ginette as he snorted, "You want a fight? I can accompany you anytime."

"I'm not talking about fighting!" Ginette's face froze.

The oldest Volga curled his lips as he thought, Bullsh*t, how could that not be considered fighting?

All the officers were babbling on, and only Feidin smiled warmly as he asked, "Black Star, you're not injured, right?"

"Nothing too serious." Han Xiao nodded, sweeping his gaze across the room, before asking, "Where's Aroshia?"

Aroshia did not follow the rest of the officers over to view... ahem, to visit him.

"She overexerted herself and has gone over to the reaction furnace to recharge."

Han Xiao nodded in understanding. Because Aroshia was an energy body, the energy furnace was her best supply station.

The group of officers rambled on for a while, giving Han Xiao a headache. Thus, he eventually chased them out to help with the disaster relief whilst he stayed in his room to rest.

He did not need to stick his hands into the disaster relief as he had more important things to do.

The battle had resulted in him losing the majority of his machinery. The first task at hand was to rebuild his Mechanical Army, restoring the previous quantity. The second matter was to break through to the Calamity Grade as quickly as possible. He was already at Level 136, with his combat capability close to the great divide of Grade A. Most likely, when he exceeded Level 140, he would enter the realm of Calamity Grades.

The Level 140 Advancement happened to be the next Race Evolution, and this would result in a huge promotion.

It was just nice that his advanced class [Virtual Mechanic] was currently at Level 11, with the upper limit being Level 20. This meant that even if his total level reached 140, there would not be any Class Missions, only a Promotion Mission. Furthermore, he still had a leftover [Mission Completion Card] on hand, which could allow him to undergo his Promotion immediately.

However, while he was only separated from advancing by four levels, every increase in level at this point required a veritable ocean of experience. From Level 136 to Level 140, he required more than three billion experience.

The upper limit of Version 1.0 was Level 60, whereas the limit for Version 2.0 was Level 90. However, the experience required to upgrade would only increase. In the future, the upper limit increase during each version update would gradually decrease as players required more time to upgrade.

At the beginning of the battle, Han Xiao had allocated all his stored experience to upgrade himself. If he wished to obtain another three billion experience points in a short amount of time, he could only turn to the players.

Godora was already quietly preparing for the final battle, while DarkStar was completely unprepared. He had to quickly recover his combat strength in order to obtain the right to participate. After all, [Godora's Ally] was also a main storyline.

It seems like there's a need to refresh the batch of knowledge and skills for the players. Since I also have plenty of funds in my account, I can freely choose the professional knowledge for the Pugilist and Esper classes, then copy it and sell it. I just need to change the prices from money to experience. Oh, that's right. I also have the dungeon copy and can milk it for quite the sum.

Han Xiao had long become accustomed to such methods and conveniently opened the forums, looking at the current situation of the players.

Various posts on the forum came into view. In Planet Aquamarine's board, most of the posts were basically about him, and the forum had exploded into conversation about his battle. Numerous screenshots and videos taken depicted the historical scene where he took the main cannon head on. The players had exploded in excitement!

The trending posts were all dominated by him once again.

Casually opening a few of those posts, he got goosebumps from seeing himself inside the videos.

All the posts put up by the players could be summarized using the few phrases.

Strong! Fantastic! Earth shaking! Explosive! I'm in love!

For those who had already joined the Black Star Mercenary Group, they were the happiest. Because the stronger their boss was, the more positive an impression people would have of them. In addition, there was still Dragon Emperor Ames on top, and just thinking about it, the future of their faction seemed quite bright.

This event can be considered an opportunity, to allow players to feel that the storyline for Planet Aquamarine has already ended, and it is the time to enter a higher stage, to lead them into the galaxy...

Moreover, according to the needs of Godora and the galaxy's journalists, what had happened on Planet Aquamarine would be vigorously publicized. If he did not guess incorrectly, there would be many uninvited guests heading over to the planet soon.

Han Xiao's eyes flashed. This would be a good chance for him to carry out the next phase of his plan!

Chapter 576: Always Causing Sensational News

Godora's actions had always been observed by the media. Especially after the battle of Planet Golden Gate, the majority of the news reports had praised Godora for their victory. As such, many galactic residents were looking forward to the next piece of news regarding Godora.

However, most of them never would have expected that the next news of victory would come so quickly.

The battleground this time was a backward planet called Planet Aquamarine!

Many people could not help feeling bewildered. If was perfectly reasonable for Godora to push DarkStar back, but how was a backward planet able to fight DarkStar off?

No one knew exactly what had happened and only knew rough details of the incident.

To the majority of the galaxy, Planet Aquamarine was no more than a low-grade planet. If not for it being one of the calamity planets, many of them would not even have known that such a planet existed.

As for Black Star's reputation, the majority of the galactic citizens were not familiar with him. While Han Xiao was an individual to be taken seriously in the eyes of the various large organizations, who were able to guess that this incident was probably related to Black Star, Han Xiao was no more than a mercenary to the commoners. A mercenary was not a superstar, and they would not commit the name of a mercenary to memory. Han Xiao was only famous among the upper echelons.

On the galactic web, many people were extremely interested in the details of the entire incident. There were not many witnesses, and this was a juicy piece of news that all the galactic news agencies wanted to get their hands on.

After just a short few days, galactic news agencies from all over the Star System sent their spaceships over to conduct interviews and dig out the truth. Just how did Planet Aquamarine fight DarkStar off?

The backward planet of Planet Aquamarine, which was usually ignored by the entire galaxy, became the center of attention of the galactic residents for once. This was the first time that they had welcomed visitors from the galaxy who were also commoners.

Planet Aquamarine had also become bustling with activity.

With Godora's aid, the Sanctuary and Six Nations had cleaned up the mess from the battle, and there were plenty of things waiting for them to do. All the spaceships from the various news agencies were blocked outside the atmosphere by the Godoran fleet.

Godora was not planning to allow those reporters to enter Planet Aquamarine. While there were safety considerations, there was also a deeper meaning behind their decision.

The regime of the Six Nations was completely clueless about the visitors from the galaxy. After all, they did not have the means to contact the galaxy.

Since the reporters were not able to contact the regime of Planet Aquamarine, they quickly remembered that the Black Star Mercenary Group had been mentioned in the previous reports as well. As such, they decided to contact the Black Star Mercenary Group instead.

"They're finally here."

Phillip passed the message on to Han Xiao. Those reporters were a key part of his plan, so he contacted Nagakin to order the fleet to give way.

The fleet commander received the order from Nagakin. Despite him not wanting to let the reporters in, he had received orders from the higher ups to follow Nagakin's orders when they were on Planet Aquamarine. Furthermore, after thinking carefully, he realized that he would not want to provoke Black Star either, especially after seeing Black Star's display of strength. As such, he could only unwillingly move his fleet out of the way.

All the reporters rushed into Planet Aquamarine excitedly. Many of the reporters were old and experienced in this field and immediately knew that something was wrong. They wanted to meet the Black Star Mercenary Group, and the Godoran fleet had to give way obediently. There were many hints behind this simple action.

Godora had to give face to the Black Star Mercenary Group!

Many of the reporters instinctively realized that while Black Star was no more than an ordinary mercenary in the eyes of the Godorans, it was extremely likely that Black Star had played a key role in fighting off DarkStar.

This group of reporters showed their respect to the regime of Planet Aquamarine and all landed in the Six Nations. Only then did the Six Nations find out about the visitors from the galaxy. The Six Nations were filled with both excitement and nervousness as they welcomed their guests.

This was the first time that the Six Nations and inhabitants of Planet Aquamarine had seen so many aliens of different races. When the reporters stated their reason for their visit, the upper echelons of the Six Nations swiftly realized that this was an extremely good opportunity!

This was a good opportunity for them to build ties with the galaxy!

All this while, the Six Nations could only unilaterally contact Godora and knew very little about the galaxy. This situation had only improved slightly after Black Star's return.

DarkStar's assault on Planet Aquamarine had drawn the attention of the galaxy to the planet. To a backward planet like Planet Aquamarine, this was a significant event. The upper echelons of the Six Nations welcomed the reporters with the best hospitality they could provide, and they all felt that it was a blessing in disguise.

While the Six Nations were not familiar with the customs of the galaxy, they were extremely humble in the hospitality. At the same time, they showered the reporters with an endless stream of questions, and the reporters answered whatever they could without any arrogance. They would not look down on Planet Aquamarine. After all, this planet had just fought off DarkStar, and there was a need to show the most basic respect.

Very quickly, the upper echelons of the Six Nations found out that the reporters had initially been blocked outside the atmosphere and only managed to gain entry after Han Xiao's intervention. They were immediately filled with immense gratitude toward Han Xiao. Because of Black Star, this planet had not been destroyed, and now, Black Star had given them the opportunity to contact the galaxy.

It was indeed right to hug Han Xiao's thigh. The other party had already begun to fulfil his end of the promise to help them develop.

On the other side, the reporters also found out that the Black Star Mercenary Group was the main reason for the planet fighting off DarkStar, and their guesses were confirmed.

No wonder Godora had to give Black Star some face.

However, the Six Nations did not understand the details of the entire event. They could barely take care of themselves and had only found out after the entire incident.

The reporters then took pictures of the destroyed cities. It was all precious news footage. Following which, the reporters could not stop themselves rushing to the Sanctuary to interview Han Xiao.

Before the spaceships even arrived at the Sanctuary, they could see two gigantic circular mountains, which were obviously the outcome of the battle.

They had indeed come to the right place! The reporters became energized, and they took out their cameras to capture the footage of the battle.

The spaceships landed one after another, and the reporters walked out. Herlous was already waiting for them and calmly said, "Follow me to the conference room. Black Star will accept your interview."

The reporters all nodded and quickly followed behind him. Their attitude was completely different compared to when they were meeting with the Six Nations.

While these reporters were not arrogant and treated the Six Nations as their equals, the inhabitants of those from a backward planet were different, and there were no common topics between them.

However, before the Black Star Mercenary Group, these reporters humbled themselves even further. The Black Star Mercenary Group was an existence of a higher level, and this respect came from their hearts.

When they arrived at the conference room, Han Xiao had not arrived, and the reporters could only wait. However, they did not waste any time and began interviewing Herlous.

Herlous had already received Han Xiao's orders, and he purposely stayed behind so that the reporters could interview him. He then began to illustrate the entire event honestly.

"DarkStar sent out a large number of spaceships to assault the Six Nations and us. Our captain was DarkStar's target, and the enemy sent out a total of three Calamity Grade Supers to surround him!"

Black Star faced three Calamity Grade Supers single handedly? Since he was still alive, the outcome of the battle had spoken for itself!

All the reporters were dumbfounded and began scribbling down their notes.

"DarkStar sent out three Calamity Grade Supers to surround Black Star!"

Herlous then continued. "Our captain single-handedly tied down the three most terrifying enemies and bore the weight of the greatest danger. The three Calamity Grade Supers weren't able to break our captain's defense, and DarkStar was forced to use their mothership's main cannon to attack our captain..."

The reporters gasped in shock and continued scribbling.

"Three Calamity Grade Supers were beaten up and forced to use their spaceship's main cannon!"

"The two circular mountains on the outside are the result of the main cannon. Our captain used his own body to tank the cannon and emerged unscathed. Following which, DarkStar fired another shot, but they fell for our captain's trap and almost caused the death of their own Calamity Grade comrade. As such, they didn't dare fire another shot..."

This was truly some juicy news!

The reporters were all dumbfounded and hurriedly wrote.

"Tanking the main cannon with his body, Black Star arrogantly taunts for another shot!"

"Finally, the Godoran reinforcements arrived, and DarkStar wasn't willing to fight Godora again. As such, they were forced to retreat. That's what happened." Herlous then shut his mouth.

The reporters gave a warm round of applause and wrote frantically.

"Black Star's divine might, DarkStar's pitiful escape!"

After estimating that Herlous' interview should be over, Han Xiao entered the conference room.

All the reporters immediately jumped up with faces full of respect and cried out, "Sir Black Star!"

Han Xiao immediately felt as though he was the discipline teacher making his rounds in a school.

Han Xiao sat down, and the reporters began their interview. They first confirmed that what Herlous had described was the truth before showering Han Xiao with many other questions.

"Did you feel any pressure from facing three Calamity Grade Supers?"

"How did it feel to tank the main cannon?"

"What do you feel about the actions of DarkStar?"

The endless stream of questions made Han Xiao feel as though he was holding a press conference.

Han Xiao answered all the reporter's questions patiently as he needed to rely on them to spread his name. This was an additional Renown reward. After all, an event that could give him Legendary Points would definitely have many hidden rewards.

As the interview came to an end, one of the reporters asked a final question.

"Sir Black Star, for you to stay behind on Planet Aquamarine and aid the planet in fighting the calamity and fending off the enemies, is it because this is your home planet?"

Hearing that, Han Xiao's eyes glowed, and an idea popped up in his mind. "That is only one of the reasons..."

"Can you tell us the other reasons?" the reporter asked.

Han Xiao chuckled and said, "Of course. Planet Aquamarine isn't only my home planet. The Black Star Mercenary Group also plans to expand to Planet Aquamarine and set up a branch division on the planet. This will also be one of the bases of the Floating Dragon armed division. A while back, the Dragon Emperor came to Planet Aquamarine to assess the location, and my job is to fight off all incoming enemies."

The eyes of all the reporters lit up, and they were overjoyed! This was another juicy piece of news!

It turned out that Planet Aquamarine was a planet under the protection of Black Star and Floating Dragon!

From that day onward, Planet Aquamarine would no longer be a low-grade planet without anything special. The brand of Floating Dragon would be marked on it, and this brand would be a protective talisman for the planet. At the very least, ninety percent of those with ill intentions would be deterred.

After all, he would not remain on Planet Aquamarine forever, and this was beneficial to both Planet Aquamarine and his own base.

Apart from raising the level of security, the fame of Floating Dragon would attract merchants and investments to the planet. Some financial groups would invest in the planet, and this would speed up the process of Planet Aquamarine becoming connected to galaxy.

Since Planet Aquamarine was the territory of Floating Dragon, even if it was a backward planet for the time being, the financial groups would still be willing to carry out some investments and transfer some technological knowledge over to aid the Six Nations in their development. This way, he would be able to fulfil his promise to the Six Nations.

At the same time, stamping Planet Aquamarine with the brand of Floating Dragon was a precautionary measure. Even if the Six Nations developed in the future and became independent, they would not dare go against their contract with him. They would be extremely clear about the outcome of losing the brand of Floating Dragon.

As such, even though the regime controlling Planet Aquamarine was the Six Nations on the surface, the true ruler of the planet was actually...

Ames

It naturally was not him.

However, with Ames' lazy nature, he would have an extremely large say.

Of course, Ames would not reject. As for the Head Butler Jenny, who was in charge of operations...

Ha! Loving colleagues like them should clean up after each other!

This trip of theirs was filled with rewards, and they all returned with satisfaction.

The next day, the various news agencies of the Garton Star System released detailed coverage of the 'true story' of the battle on Planet Aquamarine. It was coupled with photos of the circular shaped mountains being the main headline.

After taking a glance at the article, Han Xiao almost puked blood as he strangled Herlous and roared with anger, "Didn't we agree to tell the truth‽ Just what did you tell the reporters‽ Did I ask you to brag? Did I‽"

Herlous was filled with grievances. "I really did tell the truth. Who knew that reporters would be so good at fluffing things up?"

This incident was spread far and wide in the galaxy. Not just the Garton Star System, even the other Star Systems of the Shattered Star Ring who were paying attention to the chaos created by DarkStar knew about a character called Black Star who fought three Calamity Grade Supers alone and tanked the main cannon of a DarkStar mothership.

Even a Star Cluster level civilization remembered Black Star's name.

The entire Shattered Star Ring was shaken!